<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apprentices on Gajab Jobs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apprentices on Gajab Jobs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:12:36 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/apprentice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Yantra India Limited Apprentice Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/yantra-india-limited-apprentice-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:12:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/yantra-india-limited-apprentice-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Yantra India Limited Apprentice 2026 notification released for 3979 Trade Apprentice posts. Eligible 10th and ITI pass candidates can apply online and check dates, fees, stipend and selection details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Maharashtra Apprentice Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:34:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Maharashtra has announced Apprentice Recruitment 2025–26 for 600 posts under the Apprentices Act, 1961. Graduate candidates can apply online for one-year apprenticeship with a monthly stipend of ₹12,300. Selection will be merit-based on 12th/Diploma marks. The online application process is open from 15 January 2026 to 25 January 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOCL Northern Region Apprentice Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iocl-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:12:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iocl-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>IOCL Northern Region Apprentice Recruitment 2025–26 has been announced for 501 state-wise vacancies for Trade, Technician, and Graduate Apprentice posts. Candidates with 12th, ITI, Diploma, or Graduation qualifications can apply online from 27/12/2025 to 12/01/2026 through the NAPS/NATS portals. The selection process is merit-based with no written examination, and the apprenticeship training duration is 12 months, as per the notification issued by Indian Oil Corporation Limited – Marketing Division, Northern Region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of India Apprentice Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 10:24:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Bank of India Apprentice Recruitment 2025 has been announced for a total of 400 apprenticeship positions across various states of India. The recruitment is open to graduate candidates who meet the prescribed age and eligibility criteria. The online application process will be conducted from 25 December 2025 to 10 January 2026. Selection will be based on an online written test followed by a local language proficiency test. The apprenticeship training duration is one year, during which selected candidates will receive a monthly stipend of ₹13,000. This program is designed to provide hands-on banking experience but does not guarantee permanent employment in the bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOB Apprentice 2025 - Exam Date Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:39:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Baroda has released the official notification for 2700 Apprentice posts under the Apprentices Act, 1961. The online application process started on 11 November 2025 and will continue till 01 December 2025. Candidates having a Graduation Degree in any discipline can apply through the official website bankofbaroda.in or via the BFSI SSC portal. Selection will be done through an Online Exam, Document Verification, and Local Language Test. Selected candidates will receive a monthly stipend of ₹15,000 during the 1-year apprenticeship training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCF Kapurthala Apprentice Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rcf-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:28:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rcf-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Rail Coach Factory Kapurthala has announced 550 Act Apprentice vacancies for various ITI trades. Eligible candidates from all states can apply online until 07 January 2026. Selection will be based on merit prepared from 10th and ITI marks, followed by document verification and a medical exam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Air Force Apprentice Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iaf-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:52:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iaf-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Indian Air Force Apprentice 2026 भर्ती में कुल 144 ITI ट्रेड पदों पर आवेदन आमंत्रित किए गए हैं। यह प्रशिक्षण Base Repair Depot, Chandigarh में आयोजित होगा। आवेदन की अंतिम तिथि 30 दिसंबर 2025 है। पात्र उम्मीदवार 17 से 35 वर्ष आयु सीमा के भीतर ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। चयन प्रक्रिया में लिखित परीक्षा, इंटरव्यू, मेडिकल वेरिफिकेशन और मेरिट लिस्ट शामिल है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC NR Apprentice Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-nr-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:32:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-nr-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Northern Railway has released the Act Apprentice Recruitment 2025 for 4116 posts across multiple clusters. Eligible candidates with 10th pass and ITI (NCVT/SCVT) can apply online. The selection will be based on a merit list prepared from 10th and ITI marks. The application process begins from 25 November 2025 and continues till 24 December 2025. No written exam or interview will be conducted. Interested candidates must check the eligibility, age limit, application fees, and required documents before submitting the online form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONGC Apprentice Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/ongc-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:56:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/ongc-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Limited (ONGC) has released the official notification for Apprentice Recruitment 2025 under the Apprentices Act, 1961. A total of 2743 vacancies have been announced across India in various sectors such as Northern, Western, Eastern, Southern, Mumbai, and Central.Eligible candidates with ITI, Diploma, or Graduate qualifications can apply for trades like Fitter, Electrician, Computer Operator, Lab Chemist, Mechanical Executive, Accounts Executive, and others. The online application process began on 16/10/2025 and will continue till 06/11/2025 through the official ONGC Apprentice portal – ongcapprentices.ongc.co.in. Selection will be based on merit of qualifying exam marks, and no examination fee is required. Selected apprentices will receive a monthly stipend up to ₹12,300 during the 12-month training period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAI Graduate &amp; Diploma Apprenticeship Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/aai-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:39:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/aai-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Airports Authority of India (AAI) has announced the AAI Apprentice Recruitment 2025-26 for 20 posts of Graduate and Diploma Apprentices under the Apprentices Act, 1961 at RCDU/FIU/CRSD &amp;amp; E&amp;amp;M Workshop, Safdarjung Airport, New Delhi. Candidates who have completed their BE/B.Tech, BCA, B.Sc, B.Com, BA, BBA, or Diploma (Mechanical, Automobile, EEE, ECE, Instrumentation, Material Management) after 2021 are eligible to apply. The apprenticeship duration will be 1 year, with a monthly stipend of ₹15,000 for graduates and ₹12,000 for diploma holders. Selection will be based on merit and document verification, and applications can be submitted through the NATS portal (nats.education.gov.in) till 24 November 2025. Preference will be given to candidates from the Delhi/NCR region.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
