<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest Jobs - Gajab Jobs on Gajab Jobs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Latest Jobs - Gajab Jobs on Gajab Jobs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:32:13 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MP Gram Panchayat Sachiv Online Form 2025-26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/mp-panchayat-sachiv-recruitment-nov25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:32:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/mp-panchayat-sachiv-recruitment-nov25/</guid>
      <description>MP Gram Panchayat Sachiv Bharti 2026 के तहत मध्यप्रदेश में कुल 23,011 ग्राम पंचायत सचिव पदों पर भर्ती प्रस्तावित है। योग्यता के लिए Graduation + Computer Diploma (DCA/PGDCA) और आयु 21 से 35 वर्ष निर्धारित की जा सकती है। चयन प्रक्रिया MPESB की लिखित परीक्षा, मेरिट सूची और दस्तावेज सत्यापन के आधार पर होगी। नियुक्ति जिला पंचायत द्वारा की जाएगी और वेतनमान प्रशिक्षण अवधि में ₹10,000 से शुरू होकर नियमित सेवा में ₹19,500–₹52,000 प्रति माह तक रहेगा। आवेदन और परीक्षा की तिथि आधिकारिक नोटिफिकेशन जारी होने के बाद अपडेट की जाएगी।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC CPO SI 2025 Online Exam City</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-cpo-si-capf-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 18:38:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-cpo-si-capf-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for CPO SI Recruitment 2025, offering 3073 vacancies for Sub-Inspector posts in Delhi Police and CAPFs. Eligible candidates with a bachelor’s degree can apply online from 26 September to 16 October 2025. The selection process includes a Computer-Based Test (Paper-I &amp;amp; II), Physical Tests (PST/PET), Medical Examination, and Document Verification. This recruitment provides an excellent opportunity for graduates to join Delhi Police and CAPFs with a pay scale of Level-6 (₹35,400 – ₹1,12,400).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPKVVCL Line Attendant Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/mppkvvcl-line-attendant-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 18:06:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/mppkvvcl-line-attendant-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Madhya Pradesh Paschim Kshetra Vidyut Vitaran Company Limited (MPWZ / MPPKVVCL) has released a notification for 4009 vacancies including AE, JE, Line Attendant, Test Assistant, Stenographer and various other posts. The online application will start from 20 December 2025 and the last date to apply is 21 January 2026. Candidates from all states can apply. Selection will be based on a written exam and document verification. Salary ranges from ₹18,000 to ₹42,700 per month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPGCL Plant Assistant Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppgcl-assistant-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:39:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppgcl-assistant-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>MPPGCL has released the notification for Plant Assistant Recruitment 2025 with a total of 90 vacancies for Mechanical (53) and Electrical (37) posts. Only male candidates with ITI qualification can apply. The online application process will run from 01/12/2025 to 30/12/2025. Selection will be based on a Computer Based Test followed by document verification. Salary will be provided as per Level-6 after successful training and probation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Panchayati Raj Block Project Manager Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-panchayati-raj-bpm-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 15:51:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-panchayati-raj-bpm-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Panchayati Raj Department has released the notification for 826 Block Project Manager (BPM) posts under the RGSA scheme. Eligible graduates with 60% marks and valid computer certificates can apply online from 01/12/2025 to 15/12/2025. No written exam will be conducted; selection will be based on merit, qualifications, and verification. Candidates are advised to read the official notification for detailed eligibility and instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMRS Teaching &amp; Non-Teaching Exam City 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/emrs-teaching-non-teaching-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 14:26:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/emrs-teaching-non-teaching-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The National Education Society for Tribal Students (NESTS) has announced the EMRS Recruitment 2025 (ESSE-2025) notification for a total of 7267 vacancies across teaching and non-teaching posts. The vacancies include Principal, PGT, TGT, Female Staff Nurse, Hostel Warden, Accountant, Junior Secretariat Assistant (JSA), and Lab Attendant. Candidates can apply online until 23rd October 2025, with application fees ranging from ₹500 to ₹2500 depending on the post and category. The eligibility criteria vary by position, requiring qualifications from 10th/12th to Graduate, Postgraduate, B.Ed., CTET, or professional degrees. The age limit is set between 30 to 50 years, with applicable relaxations for reserved categories. This recruitment provides a major opportunity for aspirants seeking teaching and non-teaching jobs in Eklavya Model Residential Schools (EMRS) across India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRLPS JEEViKA Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-brlps-jeevika-form-aug25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 14:22:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-brlps-jeevika-form-aug25/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Rural Livelihoods Promotion Society (BRLPS), under the Rural Development Department of the Government of Bihar, has released the official notification for JEEViKA Recruitment 2025. A total of 2747 vacancies have been announced across various posts including Block Project Manager, Livelihood Specialist, Area Coordinator, Accountant, Office Assistant, Community Coordinator, and Block IT Executive. The required educational qualifications vary by post, ranging from Intermediate (for female Community Coordinators) to Graduation, Post-Graduation, Diploma, or B.Tech. The minimum age for applicants is 18 years, while the upper age limit goes up to 42 years depending on the category. The selection process involves a Computer-Based Test (CBT) and a typing test for relevant positions. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://brlps.in&#34;&gt;https://brlps.in&lt;/a&gt; from 30th July to 18th August 2025. This is a great opportunity to contribute to Bihar’s largest rural development mission and support the empowerment of rural communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBI Officer Grade B Phase II Admit Card  2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officer-grade-b-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 14:03:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officer-grade-b-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has announced 120 vacancies for Grade B Officers in General, DEPR, and DSIM streams. The application window will remain open from 10 September to 30 September 2025. Phase I examination is scheduled on 18–19 October 2025, while Phase II will be held on 6–7 December 2025. Candidates must carefully read the official notification for detailed eligibility criteria, qualifications, age limit, and application fees before applying online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Computer Assistant Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-computer-assistant-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 18:07:48 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-computer-assistant-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Public Service Commission (UPPSC) has released a notification for the recruitment of Computer Assistant posts in 2025. A total of 13 vacancies have been announced for eligible male and female candidates across India. To apply, candidates must have passed 10+2 (Intermediate) along with either a valid “O” Level certificate from NIELIT or a Diploma in Computer Science. The minimum age required is 18 years, and selected candidates will receive an initial salary in the ₹25,500 – ₹81,100 pay scale (Level-4). The application process is online only and will be available soon on the official website uppsc.up.nic.in. Interested candidates are advised to regularly check the website for the release of the online form and notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Assistant Teacher Bharti 2025 Exam Date Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-assistant-teacher-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 18:03:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-assistant-teacher-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Directorate of Medical Education and Research (DMER) has announced a recruitment drive for 7466 Assistant Teacher posts. Candidates must hold a Bachelor’s Degree in the relevant subject from any recognized university in India. Detailed eligibility criteria and subject-wise qualifications will be released soon. Interested applicants are advised to stay updated with the official notification and prepare to apply online as per the given schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Jamadar Grade-II Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-jamadar-grade-ii-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 17:58:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-jamadar-grade-ii-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSMSSB) has released the official notification for Jamadar Grade-II Recruitment 2025 under the Public Works Department (PWD). A total of 72 posts are available — 64 for Non-Scheduled Area and 8 for Scheduled Area. Eligible candidates who have passed Senior Secondary (12th) and possess a valid computer qualification (like RSCIT, DOEACC “O” Level, COPA, or Diploma in Computer Science) can apply online. The online application process will be active from 17/10/2025 to 15/11/2025, and the OMR-based exam will be conducted on 27/12/2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Ayush Officer Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-ayush-officer-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 17:56:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-ayush-officer-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB), Jaipur has issued Advertisement No. 06/2025 for the recruitment of 1535 Contractual Ayush Officers (Ayurved, Homoeopathy, Unani) under the National Health Mission (NHM), Rajasthan. Eligible candidates can apply online through the SSO Rajasthan Portal from 10 October 2025 to 08 November 2025. The recruitment will be on a one-year contract basis, extendable as per the project duration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar Vidhan Parishad Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-vidhan-parishad-office-attendant-driver-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 17:48:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-vidhan-parishad-office-attendant-driver-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Vidhan Parishad Secretariat has released the official notification for 24 vacancies including 09 Driver and 15 Office Attendant posts. Eligible candidates with a minimum qualification of Matric (10th Pass) can apply online from 29/09/2025 to 20/10/2025. Selection will be based on a written exam, while Driver posts also require a driving skill test. Interested applicants are advised to read the official notification for detailed eligibility, age limit, and application process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Head Constable Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-head-constable-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 17:01:02 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-head-constable-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for Delhi Police Head Constable (Assistant Wireless Operator/Tele-Printer Operator) Recruitment 2025. A total of 552 vacancies are available, including 370 posts for male candidates and 182 posts for female candidates. The online application process will remain open from 24 September to 15 October 2025. Candidates must have passed 10+2 with Science and Mathematics or hold an NTC in Mechanic-cum-Operator Electronic Communication System. The age limit is 18 to 27 years, with applicable relaxations for reserved categories. The selection process includes a Computer Based Examination, Physical Endurance &amp;amp; Measurement Test (PE&amp;amp;MT), Trade Test, and Computer Proficiency Test. The pay scale is Level-4 (₹25,500 – ₹81,100) as per the 7th CPC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Head Constable Ministerial Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-hc-ministerial-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:56:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-hc-ministerial-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for Delhi Police Head Constable (Ministerial) Recruitment 2025. A total of 509 vacancies (341 male &amp;amp; 168 female) are available. Candidates with 10+2 qualification can apply online from 29/09/2025 to 20/10/2025. The selection process includes Computer Based Examination, Physical Endurance &amp;amp; Measurement Test (PE&amp;amp;MT), Typing Test, and Computer Formatting Test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Constable Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:50:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the Delhi Police Constable (Executive) Recruitment 2025 notification for 7565 vacancies. Both male and female candidates can apply online from 22 September to 21 October 2025. The recruitment process includes a Computer-Based Examination, followed by Physical Endurance &amp;amp; Measurement Tests (PE&amp;amp;MT). Eligible candidates must have passed 10+2, and male applicants must hold a valid LMV driving license. The pay scale is Level-3 (₹21,700 – ₹69,100). Reserved categories and women candidates are exempted from the application fee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Constable Driver Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-driver-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:44:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-driver-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for Delhi Police Constable (Driver) – Male Recruitment 2025 with 737 vacancies. Applications can be submitted online from 24/09/2025 to 15/10/2025. Candidates must have 10+2 qualification, a valid Heavy Motor Vehicle (HMV) driving license, and knowledge of vehicle maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB NTPC Inter Level Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-inter-level-recruitment-sep-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:13:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-inter-level-recruitment-sep-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has released the notification for RRB NTPC Inter Level Recruitment 2025 (CEN 07/2025) with 3050 vacancies under the 10+2 (Undergraduate) category. Eligible candidates who have passed Intermediate (Class 12th) can apply online for posts like Junior Clerk cum Typist, Accounts Clerk cum Typist, Train Clerk, and Commercial cum Ticket Clerk. The application process will start from 28 October 2025 and continue till 27 November 2025. The selection process includes CBT-1, CBT-2, Typing Skill Test (for Clerk/Typist posts), Document Verification, and Medical Examination. The pay scale ranges from ₹19,900 to ₹21,700 (Level-2 &amp;amp; Level-3 as per 7th CPC) with additional allowances. Candidates are advised to check the official notification for complete eligibility, age limit, application fees, and exam details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB NTPC Graduate Level Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-graduate-level-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:12:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-graduate-level-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has announced the RRB NTPC Graduate Level Recruitment 2025 (CEN 06/2025) with around 5800 vacancies under the graduate category. Eligible candidates with a Bachelor’s degree can apply online for posts such as Station Master, Goods Guard, Senior Clerk cum Typist, Junior Accounts Assistant, Commercial Apprentice, and Traffic Assistant. The online application window will remain open from 21 October 2025 to 20 November 2025. The selection process includes CBT-1, CBT-2, Computer Based Aptitude Test (for Station Master &amp;amp; Traffic Assistant), Typing Skill Test (for Clerk/Typist posts), Document Verification, and Medical Examination. The salary ranges from ₹25,500 to ₹35,400 (Level-4 to Level-6 as per 7th CPC) along with allowances. Candidates must check the official notification for detailed eligibility, post-wise vacancies, exam pattern, and other important updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MHA Intelligence Bureau ACIO Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mha-intelligence-bureau-acio-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:56:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mha-intelligence-bureau-acio-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau (IB), under the Ministry of Home Affairs (MHA), has announced the recruitment of 3717 posts for Assistant Central Intelligence Officer (ACIO) Grade-II / Executive. This is a Group &amp;lsquo;C&amp;rsquo;, Non-Gazetted, and Non-Ministerial post offering candidates a prestigious opportunity to work with India’s internal intelligence agency. Applicants must possess a Bachelor’s Degree in any stream from a recognized university in India. The selection process involves a written examination followed by an interview. Eligible candidates can apply online through the official MHA website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSSC Inter Level Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-inter-level-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:47:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-inter-level-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Staff Selection Commission (BSSC) has released the notification for the Inter Level Combined Competitive Exam 2025 with 23,175 vacancies across various departments. Eligible candidates can register online from 15th October 2025 to 25th November 2025, while the final submission deadline is 27th November 2025. The minimum qualification required is Intermediate (10+2) or equivalent along with computer knowledge and typing skills. This is one of the biggest recruitment drives in Bihar offering opportunities for thousands of aspirants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uttar Pradesh Home Guard Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-home-guard-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:39:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-home-guard-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Home Guard Recruitment 2025 has announced 41,424 vacancies for Home Guard (Male/Female) posts across all districts of the state. The online application process will run from 18 November 2025 to 17 December 2025. Candidates must have passed Class 10 (High School) from a recognized board and must be between 18 to 30 years of age as on 01 July 2025. The selection process includes Physical Standards Test (PST) and Physical Efficiency Test (PET), where male candidates must complete 4.8 km in 28 minutes and female candidates must complete 2.4 km in 16 minutes. The application fee is ₹400 for General/OBC/EWS and ₹300 for SC/ST candidates. The complete district-wise vacancy list and PET/PST rules are provided in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMD Project Scientist Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/imd-project-scientist-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:17:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/imd-project-scientist-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>India Meteorological Department (IMD) has released Advertisement No. 02/2025 for the recruitment of 134 Project Staff posts on a contractual basis under the Mission Mausam Scheme. The vacancies include Project Scientist (E, III, II, I), Scientific Assistant, and Admin Assistant. Eligible M.Sc. and B.Tech candidates from relevant fields can apply online from 24/11/2025 to 14/12/2025. No application fee is mentioned in the notification. The engagement will initially be for one year and may be extended based on performance up to 31 March 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IB Multi Tasking Staff Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-mts-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:11:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-mts-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau has released the IB MTS Recruitment 2025 notification for 362 Multi-Tasking Staff (General) posts across various SIBs in India. Candidates who have passed Class 10 and possess a valid state domicile certificate can apply online from 22/11/2025 to 14/12/2025. The selection process includes a Tier-I objective exam and a Tier-II descriptive exam. Application fees are ₹650 for General/OBC/EWS male applicants and ₹550 for all other categories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KVS NVS Teaching &amp; Non-Teaching Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/kvs-nvs-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/kvs-nvs-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>KVS NVS Recruitment 2025 offers more than 14967 Teaching and Non-Teaching vacancies under Kendriya Vidyalaya Sangathan and Navodaya Vidyalaya Samiti. Eligible candidates can apply online from 14/11/2025 to 04/12/2025 for posts such as PRT, TGT, PGT, Principal, Clerk, Stenographer, Librarian and others. The application fee is ₹1500 for General, OBC and EWS categories, while SC, ST, PwD and all female candidates are exempted from fees. Qualifications vary by post and include 10th, 12th, Graduation, Post Graduation, B.Ed, D.El.Ed and CTET. The selection process includes a computer-based test followed by document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSPCB JSO &amp; JEE Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan/rspcb-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:16:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan/rspcb-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>RSPCB has announced 100 vacancies for Junior Scientific Officer and Junior Environmental Engineer. Candidates can apply online from 26 November to 16 December 2025. The notification includes eligibility criteria, age limits, application fees and detailed instructions for uploading documents and completing the online form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOI Specialist Officer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/boi-so-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:09:02 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/boi-so-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bank of India has released the Specialist Officer Recruitment 2025 for a total of 115 vacancies in Scale II III and IV. Eligible candidates can apply online from 17/11/2025 to 30/11/2025. The recruitment includes various posts in IT Risk Finance Law Engineering Fintech Data Science and Security fields. Selection will be based on an online test and/or interview. Interested applicants must check the required qualification age limit and fees before submitting the form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PNB Local Bank Officer LBO Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/pnb-lbo-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:00:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/pnb-lbo-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Punjab National Bank (PNB) has released the official notification for LBO Recruitment 2025, offering 750 Local Bank Officer (LBO) vacancies across India. Eligible graduates with at least one year of banking experience can apply online from 03/11/2025 to 23/11/2025 through the official website pnbindia.in. The selection process includes an online written test and interview, and the appointment will be made in the Junior Management Grade Scale-I. Candidates are advised to check their eligibility, fees, age limit, and local language proficiency before applying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OICL Administrative Officer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/oicl-ao-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:01:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/oicl-ao-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Oriental Insurance Company Limited (OICL) has released the OICL AO Recruitment 2025 notification for 300 vacancies, including 285 Generalist and 15 Hindi Officer posts. Eligible candidates can apply online from 01/12/2025 to 15/12/2025. The selection process includes Prelims, Mains, and Interview. Candidates must check eligibility, age limit, and qualification before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIR CDRI Technical Assistant &amp; Technician Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csir-cdri-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:12:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csir-cdri-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>CSIR CDRI has released Advt. No. 10/2025 for the recruitment of 44 posts including Technical Assistant and Technician (1). Online applications will be accepted from 25/11/2025 to 26/12/2025. Candidates across India are eligible to apply. Required qualifications include B.Sc./Diploma for Technical Assistant and 10th + ITI for Technician. The selection process consists of a written examination followed by a skill test as per the post requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC Jr Engineer Online Exam City 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-junior-engineer-je-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:03:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-junior-engineer-je-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for the Junior Engineer (JE) Recruitment 2025. The vacancies are available in various departments such as BRO, CPWD, CWC, MES, NTRO, and others for trades including Civil, Electrical, and Mechanical. Candidates must have a Diploma or Degree in the relevant engineering discipline. Some departments also require two years of work experience. The application process is completely online, and the selection will be based on a Computer-Based Test (Paper 1), Paper 2, and Document Verification. This recruitment is open to both male and female candidates across India. Interested applicants can visit the official SSC website &lt;a href=&#34;https://ssc.gov.in&#34;&gt;https://ssc.gov.in&lt;/a&gt; for more details and to apply online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police CO Recruitment 2024 - Syllabus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-computer-operator-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:13:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-computer-operator-2024/</guid>
      <description>UP Police invited online applications for the recruitment of Programmer Grade-2 and Computer Operator Grade-A from 07/01/2024 to 28/01/2024. The last date for fee payment was 31/01/2024, and the correction window was open from 01/02/2024 to 02/02/2024. The written examination is scheduled for 01/11/2025, and the admit card will be available three days before the exam. Eligible candidates—12th PCM passed with O Level or a related Diploma—can apply through the official UPPBPB website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC Deputy Director &amp; Principal Grade-II Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppsc-principal-grade-2-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 11:56:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppsc-principal-grade-2-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The MPPSC Technical Recruitment 2025 invites applications for the posts of Deputy Director, Principal Grade-II, and Assistant Director (Technical). Candidates with an engineering degree and the required professional experience can apply online from 01 December to 31 December 2025. The recruitment includes a correction window from 09 December 2025 to 02 January 2026. Applicants will be selected through a written examination followed by document verification. Interested candidates should carefully read the official notification before submitting the online form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NABARD Assistant Manager Grade A Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nabard-assistant-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 12:02:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nabard-assistant-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The National Bank for Agriculture and Rural Development (NABARD) has released the Grade A Assistant Manager Recruitment 2025 notification for 91 vacancies across various streams including Generalist, Agriculture, IT, Finance, Legal, and Protocol &amp;amp; Security Service. Eligible candidates can apply online from 08 November 2025 to 30 November 2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nabard.org&#34;&gt;www.nabard.org&lt;/a&gt;. Applicants must hold a relevant Bachelor’s or Master’s degree depending on the discipline. The selection process includes Preliminary, Main, and Interview rounds. NABARD offers an attractive salary of around ₹ 1 lakh/month (including allowances) and a prestigious career in rural development and agricultural banking. Candidates are advised to read the official notification carefully before applying online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPCIL Deputy Manager &amp; Jr. Hindi Translator Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/npcil-deputy-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 11:30:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/npcil-deputy-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Nuclear Power Corporation of India Limited (NPCIL) has released the NPCIL Recruitment 2025 notification for 122 vacancies including Deputy Manager (HR, F&amp;amp;A, C&amp;amp;MM, Legal) and Junior Hindi Translator (JHT). The online application process will be open from 07 November to 27 November 2025 at npcilcareers.co.in. Candidates with MBA, CA, CMA, CFA, LLB, or Postgraduate qualifications can apply online. The selection process includes an Online Test and Interview for Deputy Manager posts and a Preliminary plus Advanced Test for JHT. Selected candidates will receive a salary of up to ₹86,955 per month along with various allowances and benefits. Posting can be anywhere in India under the Department of Atomic Energy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB REET Mains Primary Teacher Level-1 Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:28:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSMSSB) has released the Rajasthan Primary Teacher Recruitment 2025 notification for a total of 5636 Level-1 posts under the Primary Education Department and Sanskrit Education Department. Eligible candidates who have passed REET Level-1 can apply online from 07/11/2025 to 06/12/2025 through the official website rsmssb.rajasthan.gov.in. The recruitment includes General and Sanskrit teachers for both Non-TSP and TSP areas. Selection will be based on merit and eligibility as per REET qualification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB REET Mains Upper Primary Teacher Level-II Online Form  2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-upper-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:18:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-upper-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSMSSB) has released the REET Mains Level-II Upper Primary School Teacher Recruitment 2025 for a total of 2123 posts under the Sanskrit Education Department. Eligible candidates can apply online from 07/11/2025 to 06/12/2025 through the official website rsmssb.rajasthan.gov.in. This recruitment includes vacancies for subjects like Sanskrit, Hindi, English, Social Science, and Maths-Science. Applicants must have a Graduation degree with B.Ed/D.El.Ed or 4-Year Integrated B.A./B.Sc. B.Ed as per NCTE norms. The application fee ranges from ₹400 to ₹600, and the exam is expected between 17/01/2026 to 21/01/2026. Interested candidates should check the official notification for eligibility, syllabus, and document requirements before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCRH Staff Nurse, MLT, Stenographer &amp; ARO Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-mlt-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:08:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-mlt-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Central Council for Research in Homoeopathy (CCRH) has released the official notification Advt. No. 180/2025-26 for 42 Group B &amp;amp; C vacancies including Staff Nurse, Medical Laboratory Technologist, Junior Stenographer, Junior MLT, and Assistant Research Officer (Pharmacognosy). The online application process will be open from 05/11/2025 to 26/11/2025. Candidates must apply through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ccrhindia.nic.in&#34;&gt;www.ccrhindia.nic.in&lt;/a&gt;. The application fee is ₹500 for UR/OBC/EWS, while SC/ST/PwD/Female candidates are exempted. Selection will be based on a Computer Based Test (CBT) followed by document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCRH Research Officer &amp; Other Posts Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-research-officer-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 15:27:48 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-research-officer-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Central Council for Research in Homoeopathy (CCRH), under the Ministry of AYUSH, Government of India, has released the CCRH Recruitment 2025 Notification (Advt. No. 179/2025-26) for 48 vacancies across Group A, B and C posts. Eligible candidates can apply online from 05 November 2025 to 26 November 2025 through the official websites - ccrhindia.ayush.gov.in, ccrhonline.in or eapplynow.com. The recruitment includes posts like Research Officer, Junior Librarian, Pharmacist, X-Ray Technician, LDC, and Driver. Selection will be based on a Computer-Based Test (CBT) and an interview (for Group-A). Interested applicants should read the full notification for eligibility, qualification, age limit, and application fee details before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIDBI AM Grade A and B Phase II Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sidbi-assistant-manager-grade-a-b-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 12:18:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sidbi-assistant-manager-grade-a-b-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Small Industries Development Bank of India (SIDBI) has released the official notification for the recruitment of Assistant Manager Grade A (General) and Manager Grade B (General, Legal, IT) posts, with a total of 76 vacancies. This is a great opportunity for candidates holding a Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in fields like Commerce, Economics, Law, Engineering, Management, or related disciplines. A minimum of 5 years of relevant experience is required for all Grade B positions. The application process will be conducted online, and the postings will be pan-India. Interested candidates are advised to visit the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sidbi.in&#34;&gt;www.sidbi.in&lt;/a&gt; to check complete details and apply. For eligibility criteria, experience requirements, and selection procedure, please refer to the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPGCL Assistant &amp; Junior Engineer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppgcl-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 12:06:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppgcl-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>Madhya Pradesh Power Generating Company Limited (MPPGCL) has released the Phase-II Recruitment 2025-26 notification for 131 posts of Assistant Engineer, Junior Engineer, Chemist, and Office Assistant. Eligible candidates can apply online from 17 October 2025 to 15 November 2025 through the MPOnline portal at &lt;a href=&#34;https://chayan.mponline.gov.in&#34;&gt;https://chayan.mponline.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;. Selection will be based on a Computer-Based Test (CBT) followed by document verification. Candidates must hold the prescribed qualifications (BE/B.Tech/Diploma/M.Sc/12th + Computer Diploma) as per post. This recruitment offers a great opportunity for technical and administrative aspirants in the MP Power sector under a government enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Group-2 Sub Group-3 Various Posts Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppeb-group-2-sub-group-3-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 11:58:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppeb-group-2-sub-group-3-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The MPESB has announced Group-2 Sub Group-3 Recruitment 2025 for a total of 339 posts in multiple departments including Food, Dairy, Medical, Municipal Corporations, and Pollution Control Board. The online application process is open for eligible candidates, with different qualifications required depending on the post. Interested applicants can check the detailed notification for eligibility, age limit, fees, and post-wise vacancy before applying online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Junior Engineer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-je-recruitment-sep-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 11:42:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-je-recruitment-sep-2025/</guid>
      <description>Railway Recruitment Boards (RRBs) have released the indicative notice for RRB JE Recruitment 2025 under CEN No. 05/2025. A total of 2570 vacancies are announced for Junior Engineer (JE), Depot Material Superintendent (DMS), and Chemical &amp;amp; Metallurgical Assistant (CMA) posts. Eligible candidates can apply online from 31 October 2025 to 30 November 2025. Detailed information on application fees, qualifications, and selection process will be available in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Clerk (Junior Associate) Pre Result 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-clerk-junior-associate-vacancy-aug-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:56:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-clerk-junior-associate-vacancy-aug-2025/</guid>
      <description>State Bank of India (SBI) has released the official notification for Junior Associate (Customer Support &amp;amp; Sales) recruitment under Advertisement No. CRPD/CR/2025-26/06. A total of 5583 vacancies have been announced, including 5180 regular and 403 backlog posts, to be filled across various states. The online application process will be open from 06 August to 26 August 2025. Candidates must hold a graduation degree in any discipline, with final year students also eligible to apply provisionally. The age limit is 20 to 28 years as on 01 April 2025, with age relaxation applicable as per government rules. The selection process includes an online Preliminary Exam, Main Exam, and a Local Language Proficiency Test (if applicable). The Preliminary exam is expected in September 2025, and the Main exam in November 2025. The starting basic salary is ₹26,730/-, with gross monthly emoluments of around ₹46,000/- in metro cities. The application fee is ₹750/- for General/OBC/EWS, while it is exempted for SC/ST/PwBD/Ex-servicemen. Selected candidates will be posted in the state/circle they apply for, and no inter-state transfer will be allowed. Interested candidates can apply online through the SBI official website: &lt;a href=&#34;https://sbi.co.in/web/careers&#34;&gt;https://sbi.co.in/web/careers&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC 10&#43;2 CHSL 2025 Tier - I Admit Card Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-chsl-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:48:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-chsl-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>कर्मचारी चयन आयोग (SSC) द्वारा CHSL (10+2) भर्ती 2025 का नोटिफिकेशन जारी किया गया है। इस भर्ती के अंतर्गत लोअर डिवीजन क्लर्क (LDC), डाटा एंट्री ऑपरेटर (DEO), डाक सहायक (PA) व छंटाई सहायक (SA) जैसे पदों पर नियुक्तियाँ की जाएंगी। भारत के किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 12वीं (इंटरमीडिएट) उत्तीर्ण उम्मीदवार इसके लिए आवेदन कर सकते हैं। आवेदन प्रक्रिया पूरी तरह ऑनलाइन है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IAF AFCAT 01/2026 Batch Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iaf-afcat-01-2026-batch-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:31:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iaf-afcat-01-2026-batch-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Air Force (IAF) has announced the AFCAT 01/2026 Batch Recruitment 2025 for Flying and Ground Duty (Technical &amp;amp; Non-Technical) branches. The online application process will begin on 10 November 2025 and continue till 9 December 2025 through the official website afcat.cdac.in. Candidates holding a graduate or engineering degree with Physics and Mathematics at 10+2 level can apply. The selection process includes an online written test, AFSB interview, and medical examination. Successful candidates will join the AFCAT 01/2026 course commencing in January 2026 as Group-A Gazetted Officers in the Indian Air Force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBI Officers Grade A &amp; B Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officers-grade-a-and-b-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:28:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officers-grade-a-and-b-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has announced 28 vacancies for various Grade A and B Officer posts under the 2025 recruitment drive. The available posts include Law Officer, Manager (Technical – Civil and Electrical), Assistant Manager (Rajbhasha), and Assistant Manager (Protocol &amp;amp; Security). Candidates applying for these positions must meet the minimum educational qualifications such as LLB, BE/B.Tech, Master’s Degree, or have military experience, along with relevant work experience where required. This is a great opportunity for eligible candidates to join the RBI as an officer and contribute to the nation’s central banking system. Interested applicants can submit their applications through the official RBI website within the given deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBPS Probationary Officer PO 15th Mains Admit Card 2025 – Download Now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-probationary-officer-po-15th-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:23:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-probationary-officer-po-15th-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Institute of Banking Personnel Selection (IBPS) has released the notification for CRP PO/MT-XV Recruitment 2025 for the post of Probationary Officer (PO)/Management Trainee (MT). A total of 5208 vacancies have been announced across 8 participating public sector banks. Candidates who hold a Bachelor’s Degree in any discipline from a recognized university in India are eligible to apply. The recruitment process includes a preliminary exam, main exam, and interview. Applications must be submitted online through the official IBPS website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibps.in&#34;&gt;www.ibps.in&lt;/a&gt;. Selected candidates will be appointed across various locations in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB MP Police Constable Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mpesb-police-constable-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:15:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mpesb-police-constable-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Madhya Pradesh Professional Examination Board (MPESB) has announced the MP Police Constable Recruitment 2025 for a total of 7500 Constable (General Duty – SAF &amp;amp; DEF) posts. The online application process will start from 15/09/2025 and remain open till 29/09/2025, while the correction window will be available up to 04/10/2025. The written examination is scheduled to begin from 30/10/2025. Candidates applying for this recruitment must have passed 10th/12th (for UR/SC/OBC/EWS) or at least 8th standard (for ST candidates) from a recognized board. The minimum age limit is 18 years and the maximum is 33 years for general category male candidates, with age relaxations applicable for reserved categories and women as per rules. The application fee is ₹500 for UR, ₹250 for SC/ST/OBC/EWS (MP domicile), while departmental candidates need to pay ₹200 (UR) or ₹100 (reserved categories) along with applicable portal charges. This recruitment offers a great opportunity for candidates seeking a stable government job in the Madhya Pradesh Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IB ACIO-II/Tech Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-acio-technical-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:58:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-acio-technical-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau (IB), under the Ministry of Home Affairs, has released the official notification for IB ACIO-II/Technical Recruitment 2025. A total of 258 vacancies are available for disciplines in Computer Science &amp;amp; Information Technology and Electronics &amp;amp; Communication. Eligible candidates with valid GATE 2023, 2024, or 2025 scores can apply online from 25/10/2025 to 16/11/2025 through &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mha.gov.in&#34;&gt;www.mha.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;. The recruitment includes Level-7 pay scale (₹44,900–₹1,42,400), with additional security allowances and other benefits. Selection will be based on GATE score, Skill Test, and Interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRO SAC Group C Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobsisro-sac-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:52:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobsisro-sac-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>Space Applications Centre (SAC), Ahmedabad – Indian Space Research Organisation (ISRO) has released a recruitment notification for 55 vacancies of Technician ‘B’ and Pharmacist ‘A’ under Group ‘C’ posts. Eligible candidates can apply online through sac.gov.in from 24 October 2025 to 13 November 2025. The recruitment includes various trades such as Fitter, Machinist, Electrician, Electronics Mechanic, IT/ICTSM, Lab Assistant (Chemical Plant) and Refrigeration &amp;amp; Air Conditioning. The selection process consists of a Written Test followed by a Skill Test (qualifying nature). Salary: Level 3 (₹21,700–₹69,100) for Technician B and Level 5 (₹29,200–₹92,300) for Pharmacist A Age Limit: 18–35 years (as on 13/11/2025) Qualification: 10th Pass + ITI/NTC/NAC in relevant trade or Diploma in Pharmacy (First Class)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI SCO Wealth Management Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-sco-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:10:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-sco-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>State Bank of India (SBI) has released the official notification for Wealth Management Recruitment 2025 under the Specialist Cadre Officer (SCO) category. A total of 103 vacancies are available for posts like Head, Zonal Head, Regional Head, Relationship Manager, Investment Specialist, Investment Officer, and others. Eligible candidates can apply online from 27/10/2025 to 17/11/2025 through the official website sbi.bank.in/web/careers. The selection will be based on a personal interview only.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEBI Assistant Manager Grade A Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sebi-assistant-manager-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sebi-assistant-manager-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has released the SEBI Officer Grade A (Assistant Manager) Recruitment 2025 notification for 110 vacancies across various streams including General, Legal, IT, Research, Official Language, Civil, and Electrical Engineering. The online application process will be open from 30/10/2025 to 28/11/2025. The Phase-I exam is scheduled for 10/01/2026 and Phase-II for 21/02/2026. Candidates must possess a Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in relevant disciplines and be below 30 years of age as on 30/09/2025. The selection process consists of Phase-I, Phase-II, and Interview. The pay scale ranges from ₹62,500 to ₹1,26,100 with an approximate gross salary of ₹1.84 lakh per month (without accommodation). Eligible candidates can apply online through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sebi.gov.in&#34;&gt;www.sebi.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPHC Data Processing Assistant Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mphc-dpa-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:53:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mphc-dpa-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Madhya Pradesh High Court (MPHC) has announced the Data Processing Assistant (DPA) Recruitment 2025 under advertisement S2A/Exam/DPA/2025 for 41 vacancies. Eligible candidates with a BCA or B.Sc. (Computer Science/IT) degree and at least 60% marks, along with 3 years of data entry experience, can apply online from 29/10/2025 to 19/11/2025 through mphc.gov.in. The selection process includes a Preliminary Exam, Practical Test, and Interview, and the final merit will be based on Practical and Interview marks. The pay scale is ₹5200–20200 + Grade Pay ₹2400, and the application fees are ₹943.40 for UR and ₹743.40 for Reserved categories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHAI Various Posts Recruitment 2025 – Apply Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nhai-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:28:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nhai-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) has released a notification for direct recruitment 2025 under the Ministry of Road Transport &amp;amp; Highways. Eligible candidates can apply online for various posts including Deputy Manager (Finance &amp;amp; Accounts), Accountant, Stenographer, Library Assistant, and Junior Translation Officer. The application process starts from 30/10/2025 and continues till 15/12/2025. Candidates are advised to read the official notification carefully before applying at nhai.gov.in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB MP Police Constable Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mpesb-police-constable-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 12:38:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mpesb-police-constable-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Madhya Pradesh Professional Examination Board (MPESB) has announced the MP Police Constable Recruitment 2025 for a total of 7500 Constable (General Duty – SAF &amp;amp; DEF) posts. The online application process will start from 15/09/2025 and remain open till 29/09/2025, while the correction window will be available up to 04/10/2025. The written examination is scheduled to begin from 30/10/2025. Candidates applying for this recruitment must have passed 10th/12th (for UR/SC/OBC/EWS) or at least 8th standard (for ST candidates) from a recognized board. The minimum age limit is 18 years and the maximum is 33 years for general category male candidates, with age relaxations applicable for reserved categories and women as per rules. The application fee is ₹500 for UR, ₹250 for SC/ST/OBC/EWS (MP domicile), while departmental candidates need to pay ₹200 (UR) or ₹100 (reserved categories) along with applicable portal charges. This recruitment offers a great opportunity for candidates seeking a stable government job in the Madhya Pradesh Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC APO Recruitment 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-apo-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 11:32:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-apo-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Public Service Commission (UPPSC) has released the official notification for Assistant Prosecution Officer (APO) Recruitment 2025 with 182 vacancies. Eligible candidates with a Law degree (LLB) can apply online from 16 September 2025 to 16 October 2025 through the UPPSC portal. The selection process includes Prelims, Mains, and Interview, followed by document verification and medical examination. Applicants must be between 21 to 40 years of age as on 1 July 2025. The pay scale ranges from Rs. 47,600 to Rs. 1,51,100, offering a great career opportunity for law graduates in Uttar Pradesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDA Vacancy 2025 – Delhi Development Authority Jobs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/delhi-dda-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 11:02:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/delhi-dda-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Delhi Development Authority (DDA) has released its Recruitment Notification 2025 for a total of 1732 vacancies across various posts including Deputy Director, Assistant Director, Junior Engineer, Stenographer, Patwari, Mali, and Multi Tasking Staff (MTS). The online application process is scheduled from 06 October 2025 to 05 November 2025, and the Computer Based Test (CBT) is expected in December 2025 – January 2026. Candidates can apply online through the official DDA website. The recruitment includes category-wise vacancies (UR, EWS, SC, ST, OBC) and posts for ESM / PwBD candidates. Qualifications vary by post, ranging from 10th/12th pass to Graduate/Degree holders in relevant fields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan Police Constable Sports Quota Bharti 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan-police-constable-sports-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan-police-constable-sports-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Police has announced 167 Sports Quota Constable vacancies for 2025. Applications will be accepted online between 12th September and 1st October 2025. Selection will consider CET 2024 score, sports performance, and physical criteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Village Development Officer VDO 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-village-development-officer-vdo-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:31:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-village-development-officer-vdo-2025/</guid>
      <description>राजस्थान कर्मचारी चयन बोर्ड (RSSB) द्वारा ग्राम विकास अधिकारी (VDO) पदों पर भर्ती के लिए अधिसूचना जारी कर दी गई है। इच्छुक और पात्र उम्मीदवार जो भारत के किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त विश्वविद्यालय से स्नातक हैं और जिनके पास O लेवल, COPA, DPCS, कंप्यूटर डिप्लोमा या RS-CIT प्रमाण पत्र है, वे इस भर्ती के लिए ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। भर्ती से जुड़ी पात्रता, आयु सीमा, आवेदन तिथि, चयन प्रक्रिया और अन्य जानकारी के लिए आधिकारिक नोटिफिकेशन जरूर पढ़ें।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRRL Various Posts Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hrrl-various-posts-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:39:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hrrl-various-posts-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Hindustan Petroleum Rajasthan Refinery Limited (HRRL) has released a recruitment notification for 131 vacancies across various departments including Engineering (Chemical, Mechanical, Electrical, Civil, Instrumentation), HR, Finance, Legal, Fire &amp;amp; Safety, and Medical.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan Police Constable 2025 New Examdate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan-police/constable-bharti-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 09:40:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan-police/constable-bharti-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;table-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल भर्ती पात्रता मानदंड&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;th&gt;पद का नाम&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;        &lt;th&gt;कुल पद&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;        &lt;th&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल पात्रता&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल जीडी / ड्राइवर / बैंड नॉन टीएसपी&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;6939&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;राजस्थान सीईटी 10+2 स्तर परीक्षा उत्तीर्ण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;भारत में किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10+2 इंटरमीडिएट परीक्षा&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;ड्राइवर पद के लिए:&lt;/span&gt; एलएमवी / एचएमवी ड्राइविंग लाइसेंस 01/01/2026 तक 1 वर्ष पुराना होना चाहिए&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;अधिक पात्रता विवरण के लिए आधिकारिक अधिसूचना अवश्य पढ़ें&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल जीडी / ड्राइवर / बैंड टीएसपी&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;1209&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;राजस्थान सीईटी 10+2 स्तर परीक्षा उत्तीर्ण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;भारत में किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10+2 इंटरमीडिएट परीक्षा&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;ड्राइवर पद के लिए:&lt;/span&gt; एलएमवी / एचएमवी ड्राइविंग लाइसेंस 01/01/2026 तक 1 वर्ष पुराना होना चाहिए&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;अधिक पात्रता विवरण के लिए आधिकारिक अधिसूचना अवश्य पढ़ें&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt; राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल: &lt;/b&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt; PET Details/पीईटी विवरण 2025 (सामान्य क्षेत्र)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;    &lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;            &lt;td colspan=&#34;3&#34;&gt;&#xA;                &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;ऊंचाई&lt;/b&gt; पुरुष: 168 सेंटीमीटर और महिला: 152 सेंटीमीटर&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;छाती&lt;/b&gt; पुरुष: 81-86 सेंटीमीटर&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;दौड़: पुरुष:&lt;/b&gt; 25 मिनट में 5 किलोमीटर &lt;b&gt;| महिला:&lt;/b&gt; 35 मिनट में 5 किलोमीटर&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt; ​राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल भर्ती 2025 से संबंधित महत्तपूर्ण लिंक  (Important Links) &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th&gt;Important Links&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th&gt;Action&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Dwonload New Exam Date Notice&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://police.rajasthan.gov.in/uploads/C_Tpressnote_2686_9da7aafe1f.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Check New Notice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Dwonload Exam Date Notice&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yojnaportal.com/open/?pdf=LzIwMjUvMDYvcnBzYy1yYWphc3Rhbi1wb2xpY2UtZXhhbWRhdGUtbm90aWNlLmh0bWw=&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Check Notice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Apply Online&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sso.rajasthan.gov.in/signin?ru=RECRUITMENT2&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;📄 Date Extended Notice&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yojnaportal.com/open/?pdf=LzIwMjUvMDUvcmotcG9saWNlLWRhdGUtZXh0ZW5kZWQtbm90aWNlLmh0bWw=&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;📄 Download Notificiation&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yojnaportal.com/open/?pdf=L3AvcnBjLmh0bWw=&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Join Whatsapp&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/whatsapp/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Join Telegram&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/telegram/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Official Source&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.police.rajasthan.gov.in/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;RJ Police Official Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Lab Attendant Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-lab-attendant-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 20:14:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-lab-attendant-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB) has released the notification for Lab Attendant (Prayogshala Sahayak) Recruitment 2025. Eligible candidates can apply online through the official website. This recruitment is a great opportunity for 10th pass candidates seeking government jobs in Rajasthan. Applicants must have a valid domicile of Rajasthan to claim reservation benefits; candidates from other states can apply under the unreserved category (UR). The selection process will include a written examination followed by document verification. Interested candidates are advised to read the official notification carefully and apply before the last date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan High Court Class IV (Peon) Vacancy 2025 - Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-group-d-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:07:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-group-d-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan High Court Class IV (Peon) Recruitment 2025 के अंतर्गत राजस्थान उच्च न्यायालय द्वारा चपरासी (Class IV) पदों पर भर्ती के लिए अधिसूचना जारी की गई है (विज्ञापन संख्या: रा.उ.न्या.जो./परीक्षा प्रकोष्ठ/अधीनस्थ न्यायालय/च.श्रे.क./2025/2349)। इस भर्ती के लिए अभ्यर्थी को किसी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10वीं (माध्यमिक) उत्तीर्ण होना आवश्यक है। साथ ही देवनागरी लिपि में हिंदी का व्यावहारिक ज्ञान और राजस्थान की संस्कृति की जानकारी भी अनिवार्य है। इस भर्ती में राजस्थान राज्य के अभ्यर्थी आवेदन कर सकते हैं, साथ ही अन्य राज्यों के उम्मीदवार भी आवेदन कर सकते हैं, लेकिन उन्हें अनारक्षित श्रेणी (Unreserved Category) में माना जाएगा और किसी प्रकार का आरक्षण प्राप्त नहीं होगा। आवेदन प्रक्रिया पूरी तरह ऑनलाइन होगी और विस्तृत जानकारी व आवेदन के लिए आधिकारिक वेबसाइट hcraj.nic.in पर विज़िट करें।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan HC Driver Recruitment 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-driver-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:20:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-driver-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan High Court has officially released the notification for Driver Recruitment 2025, inviting applications for a total of 58 vacancies. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online through the official website hcraj.nic.in from 18 June to 7 July 2025. This recruitment drive offers a great opportunity for candidates seeking government jobs in the driving sector under the Rajasthan judiciary. Applicants are advised to carefully read the eligibility criteria, application process, and important dates mentioned in the official notification before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSSC Field Assistant 2025 Apply Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/field-assistant-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:33:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/field-assistant-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>फील्ड असिस्टेंट (कृषि विभाग) भर्ती 2025</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
