<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sarkari Result: Gajab Jobs 2025 – Latest Jobs sarkariresult.com, sarkari result .com on Gajab Jobs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sarkari Result: Gajab Jobs 2025 – Latest Jobs sarkariresult.com, sarkari result .com on Gajab Jobs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:41:05 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army JAG Entry Scheme 124th Course Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-jag-124th-course-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:41:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-jag-124th-course-2026/</guid>
      <description>Indian Army JAG Recruitment 2026 is announced for the 124th Course commencing in October 2026 under the Judge Advocate General Branch. Unmarried male and female LLB graduates are eligible for Short Service Commission. The recruitment offers 08 vacancies and applications will be accepted online from 27 January 2026 to 27 February 2026. Selection will be through CLAT PG 2025 score, SSB interview, medical examination and merit list. Selected candidates will receive 49 weeks of pre-commission training at OTA Chennai.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Lab Assistant Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan/rssb-lab-assistant-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:29:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan/rssb-lab-assistant-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>RSSB has announced Lab Assistant and Junior Lab Assistant Recruitment 2026 for a total of 804 vacancies. The online application process starts on 27/01/2026 and ends on 25/02/2026. Vacancies are available for Non-TSP and TSP areas in various departments. Candidates who have passed 12th or Senior Secondary are eligible. The written exam will be conducted on 09/05/2026 and 10/05/2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB MP Police Constable Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mpesb-police-constable-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 18:02:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mpesb-police-constable-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Madhya Pradesh Professional Examination Board (MPESB) has announced the MP Police Constable Recruitment 2025 for a total of 7500 Constable (General Duty – SAF &amp;amp; DEF) posts. The online application process will start from 15/09/2025 and remain open till 29/09/2025, while the correction window will be available up to 04/10/2025. The written examination is scheduled to begin from 30/10/2025. Candidates applying for this recruitment must have passed 10th/12th (for UR/SC/OBC/EWS) or at least 8th standard (for ST candidates) from a recognized board. The minimum age limit is 18 years and the maximum is 33 years for general category male candidates, with age relaxations applicable for reserved categories and women as per rules. The application fee is ₹500 for UR, ₹250 for SC/ST/OBC/EWS (MP domicile), while departmental candidates need to pay ₹200 (UR) or ₹100 (reserved categories) along with applicable portal charges. This recruitment offers a great opportunity for candidates seeking a stable government job in the Madhya Pradesh Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aadhaar Supervisor Operator Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aadhaar-operator-supervisor-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:03:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aadhaar-operator-supervisor-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Aadhaar Supervisor / Operator District Recruitment 2025–26 is open across various states in India. Candidates aged 18 years or above with 12th, ITI or Polytechnic qualification and a UIDAI authorized Aadhaar Operator/Supervisor certificate can apply online. Selection is based on certification and state authorization, and salary will be paid as per state minimum wages. The last date to apply is 31 January 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Central Bank Specialist Officer Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bank/cbi-specialist-officer-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:05:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bank/cbi-specialist-officer-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Central Bank of India has announced Specialist Officer Recruitment 2026 for 350 vacancies in Foreign Exchange Officer and Marketing Officer posts. The online application process will be open from 20/01/2026 to 03/02/2026. Candidates will be selected through an online examination and interview process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Ministerial &amp; Isolated Category Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrb-ministerial-isolated-category-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:05:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrb-ministerial-isolated-category-dec25/</guid>
      <description>RRB Ministerial &amp;amp; Isolated Category Recruitment 2025 notification has been released under CEN No. 08/2025 for a total of 311 vacancies across various posts including Junior Translator, Staff &amp;amp; Welfare Inspector, Publicity Inspector, Law Assistant and others. The recruitment is conducted by the Railway Recruitment Boards (RRBs) under the Ministry of Railways, Government of India. Eligible male and female candidates can apply online from 30/12/2025 to 29/01/2026. Selection will be based on Computer Based Test (CBT), Document Verification and Medical Examination as per RRB rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haryana Police Constable Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hr/haryana-police-constable-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:04:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hr/haryana-police-constable-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Haryana Police Constable Recruitment 2026 is being conducted by HSSC for 5500 Constable posts under CET Phase-II. The recruitment is open to CET Group-C qualified Haryana domicile candidates only. Selection will be based on PMT, PST, and a Written Knowledge Test. The application process is online with no application fee, and the pay scale is ₹21,700 (Level-3</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Group-2 Sub Group-3 Various Posts 2025 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppeb-group-2-sub-group-3-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:47:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppeb-group-2-sub-group-3-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The MPESB has announced Group-2 Sub Group-3 Recruitment 2025 for a total of 339 posts in multiple departments including Food, Dairy, Medical, Municipal Corporations, and Pollution Control Board. The online application process is open for eligible candidates, with different qualifications required depending on the post. Interested applicants can check the detailed notification for eligibility, age limit, fees, and post-wise vacancy before applying online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Police Subedar &amp; Sub Inspector Answer Key  2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mp-police-si-subedar-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:42:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mp-police-si-subedar-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>मध्य प्रदेश पुलिस विभाग द्वारा MP Police Subedar &amp;amp; Sub Inspector Recruitment 2025 के अंतर्गत पुरुष एवं महिला अभ्यर्थियों के लिए 500+ पदों पर भर्ती की जा रही है। ऑनलाइन आवेदन प्रक्रिया 27 अक्टूबर 2025 से शुरू होकर 10 नवंबर 2025 तक चलेगी। उम्मीदवार का स्नातक होना आवश्यक है तथा निर्धारित आयु सीमा और शारीरिक मापदंडों को पूरा करना होगा। आवेदन शुल्क सामान्य वर्ग के लिए ₹500 और आरक्षित वर्ग के लिए ₹250 निर्धारित है। लिखित परीक्षा 9 जनवरी 2026 से आयोजित की जाएगी, जिसके बाद PET और दस्तावेज़ सत्यापन होगा।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IAF Agniveervayu Intake 01/2027 Batch Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/iaf-agniveervayu-intake-01-2027-batch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:36:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/iaf-agniveervayu-intake-01-2027-batch/</guid>
      <description>Indian Air Force Agniveervayu Intake 01/2027 recruitment notification. Know eligibility, qualification, age limit, exam schedule, salary and apply online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court Law Clerk Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sci-law-clerk-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:10:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sci-law-clerk-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Supreme Court of India invites online applications for Law Clerk-cum-Research Associate Recruitment 2026. Around 90 posts are available for law graduates and final-year students. Online applications are open from 20/01/2026 to 07/02/2026. Selection will be through written examination and interview, and selected candidates will receive a consolidated salary of ₹1,00,000 per month on a contractual basis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBI Office Attendant Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bank/rbi-bank-office-attendant-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:45:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bank/rbi-bank-office-attendant-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Reserve Bank of India has announced RBI Office Attendant Recruitment 2025 for 572 vacancies. Candidates who have passed 10th and are undergraduates can apply online between 15/01/2026 and 04/02/2026. Selection will be based on an online test followed by a Language Proficiency Test. The post offers an attractive monthly salary of around ₹46,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCO Bank Generalist &amp; Specialist Officer Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bank/uco-bank-generalist-specialist-officers-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:45:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bank/uco-bank-generalist-specialist-officers-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>UCO Bank has published the official notification for the recruitment of Generalist and Specialist Officers for 173 posts. The online application window will be open from 13 January 2026 to 02 February 2026. Eligible candidates must apply online through the official website. The selection process may involve written examination, screening and interview as per bank norms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB NTPC Graduate Level Vacancy 2025 - Application Status</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-graduate-level-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-graduate-level-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has announced the RRB NTPC Graduate Level Recruitment 2025 (CEN 06/2025) with around 5800 vacancies under the graduate category. Eligible candidates with a Bachelor’s degree can apply online for posts such as Station Master, Goods Guard, Senior Clerk cum Typist, Junior Accounts Assistant, Commercial Apprentice, and Traffic Assistant. The online application window will remain open from 21 October 2025 to 20 November 2025. The selection process includes CBT-1, CBT-2, Computer Based Aptitude Test (for Station Master &amp;amp; Traffic Assistant), Typing Skill Test (for Clerk/Typist posts), Document Verification, and Medical Examination. The salary ranges from ₹25,500 to ₹35,400 (Level-4 to Level-6 as per 7th CPC) along with allowances. Candidates must check the official notification for detailed eligibility, post-wise vacancies, exam pattern, and other important updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shramodaya Admission Test Online Form 2026–27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/shramodaya-admission-test-2026%E2%80%9327/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:20:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/shramodaya-admission-test-2026%E2%80%9327/</guid>
      <description>Shramodaya Admission Test 2026–27 is an entrance examination conducted in Madhya Pradesh for admission to Shramodaya Awasiya Vidyalaya for Class 6, 7, 8 and 9. The admission is exclusively for children of registered construction workers under the MP Building and Other Construction Workers Welfare Board. The online application window will remain open from 24/12/2025 to 20/01/2026. Candidates will be selected through a written entrance test and final admission will be done on the basis of merit and seat availability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Group D Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrb-group-d-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:08:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrb-group-d-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>RRB Level-1 / Group D Recruitment 2025 has been announced through CEN No. 09/2025 by the Railway Recruitment Boards for approximately 22000 vacancies across all RRB zones. The recruitment is for Level-1 posts under the 7th CPC Pay Matrix with an initial salary of ₹18000 per month. The online application process will be conducted in 2026 from 21 January to 20 February 2026 through the official RRB website. Candidates aged between 18 and 33 years as on 01 January 2026 will be eligible to apply, subject to relaxation as per rules. Detailed post-wise eligibility qualification selection process and syllabus will be released in the full notification on official RRB websites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP State Forest Service Exam Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/mppsc-forest-service-exam-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/mppsc-forest-service-exam-2026/</guid>
      <description>MPPSC has announced the State Forest Service Examination 2026 for Assistant Conservator of Forest and Forest Ranger Officer posts. A total of 36 vacancies are notified. Eligible candidates with a Bachelor’s degree in Science, Engineering or Technology can apply online. Selection will be done through Preliminary Exam, Main Exam, Interview and Physical Test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC State Service Exam SSE Pre Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/mppsc-state-service-exam-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/mppsc-state-service-exam-2026/</guid>
      <description>The State Service Exam 2026 is conducted by Madhya Pradesh Public Service Commission (MPPSC) for recruitment to various administrative and allied services in Madhya Pradesh. A total of 155 posts are available across multiple departments. Candidates with a graduation degree are eligible to apply online from 10/01/2026 to 09/02/2026. The selection process includes Preliminary Exam, Main Exam, and Interview. The preliminary examination is scheduled on 26/04/2026. Application fees vary by category, and late submission is allowed with additional charges. Interested candidates should apply online through the official portal before the last date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Agriculture Supervisor Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rj/rssb-agriculture-supervisor-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rj/rssb-agriculture-supervisor-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Agriculture Supervisor Vacancy 2026 notification has been issued by RSSB for 1100 Agriculture Supervisor posts in the Rajasthan Agriculture Department. Candidates possessing B.Sc. Agriculture or equivalent qualification are eligible to apply online via the SSO portal between 13/01/2026 and 11/02/2026. The recruitment process consists of an offline OMR-based written examination to be held on 18/04/2026, followed by document verification according to government norms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police Constable Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-constable-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-constable-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>UP Police Constable Recruitment 2025 has been announced for a total of 32,679 posts including Constable Civil Police, PAC, Special Security Force, Female Battalion, Mounted Police and Jail Warder posts. Candidates who have passed 12th (Intermediate) are eligible to apply. The age limit is 18–22 years for male and 18–25 years for female candidates, with relaxation for reserved categories as per rules. The selection process includes a written examination, document verification, Physical Standard Test (PST), Physical Efficiency Test (PET) and medical examination. The online application process will start from 31/12/2025 and the last date to apply is 30/01/2026. This recruitment offers a significant opportunity for candidates seeking a government job in Uttar Pradesh Police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/ssc-exam-calendar-2026-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:25:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/ssc-exam-calendar-2026-27/</guid>
      <description>Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the SSC Exam Calendar 2026. The calendar includes notification dates, last dates to apply, and exam months for CGL, CHSL, MTS, GD, JE, Stenographer, Hindi Translator and other SSC exams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTET February 2026 Registration - Reopen Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/ctet-february-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:58:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/ctet-february-2026/</guid>
      <description>The CTET February 2026 notification has been released, and the online application process is open from 27/11/2025 to 18/12/2025. Candidates can apply for Paper I (Class 1–5) and Paper II (Class 6–8) based on NCTE eligibility norms. The exam will be conducted on 08 February 2026 in offline OMR mode across multiple exam centers. The application fee is ₹1000 for General/OBC (single paper) and ₹500 for SC/ST/PwD candidates. The CTET certificate is valid for a lifetime, and all important details regarding syllabus, exam pattern, eligibility, and fee structure are provided in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NABARD Development Assistant Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nabard-development-assistant-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:09:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nabard-development-assistant-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>The National Bank for Agriculture and Rural Development (NABARD) has announced 162 vacancies for Development Assistant and Development Assistant (Hindi) posts under Recruitment 2026. Eligible graduate candidates can apply online as per the official schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC Multi Tasking Staff MTS Vacancy 2025- Self-Slot Booking </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-mts-exam-date-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:21:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-mts-exam-date-2025/</guid>
      <description>SSC ने MTS और Havaldar भर्ती 2025 के लिए अधिसूचना जारी की है। इन पदों के लिए न्यूनतम शैक्षणिक योग्यता 10वीं पास रखी गई है। चयन प्रक्रिया में कंप्यूटर आधारित परीक्षा (CBT) शामिल है, जबकि Havaldar पद हेतु शारीरिक दक्षता परीक्षा भी होगी।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Board Exam 2026 Admit Card Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/education/mp-board-10th-12th-admit-card-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:19:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/education/mp-board-10th-12th-admit-card-2026/</guid>
      <description>MPBSE द्वारा आयोजित 10वीं एवं 12वीं परीक्षाओं के Admit Card, टाइम टेबल और परिणाम से जुड़ी आधिकारिक जानकारी यहाँ दी गई है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSE Group A B &amp; C Posts 2026 - Tier-I Exam City </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cbse/cbse-group-a-b-c-posts-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:16:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cbse/cbse-group-a-b-c-posts-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>CBSE has released the Direct Recruitment 2026 notification for 124 vacancies across Group A, B and C posts including Assistant Secretary, Assistant Professor, Accounts Officer, Superintendent, Junior Translation Officer, Junior Accountant and Junior Assistant. Eligible candidates can apply online from 02 December to 22 December 2025. Selection will be based on Tier-1 and Tier-2 examinations, followed by an interview or skill test as per the post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB ITI Training Officer Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/mp-iti-training-officer-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:15:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/mp-iti-training-officer-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>The ITI Training Officer Recruitment 2026 has been announced for a total of 1120 vacancies across various trades. Eligible candidates holding ITI, Diploma, or Engineering Degree in the relevant discipline can apply online. The online application process will begin on 17/01/2026 and the last date to apply is 31/01/2026. The selection will be based on a computer-based examination, and eligibility will be verified during document verification. This recruitment offers a valuable opportunity for candidates seeking a government job in technical education and skill development in Madhya Pradesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Excellence School (SOE) &amp; Model School (SOM) Class 9 Admission 2026–27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/soe-som-class-9-admission-2026%E2%80%9327/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:11:12 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/soe-som-class-9-admission-2026%E2%80%9327/</guid>
      <description>MP Excellence School Entrance Exam 2027 is a joint selection test for admission to Class 9 in Excellence Schools (SOE) and Model Schools (SOM) across Madhya Pradesh. MP resident students who have passed or are appearing in Class 8 can submit the online application between 30/12/2025 and 16/01/2026. Admission will be based on the entrance examination, with reservation benefits applicable as per state government norms. The application fee for all categories is ₹200 including portal charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Boiler Inspector Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-boiler-inspector-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:35:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-boiler-inspector-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has announced the Boiler Inspector Recruitment 2026 for 05 vacancies. Eligible engineering graduates with relevant experience can apply online. Selection will be based on academic performance and work experience as per BPSC guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Deputy Director (Fire Service) Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-deputy-director-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:59:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-deputy-director-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has announced the Deputy Director (Fire Service) Recruitment 2026 for 14 posts. The online application window will remain open from 13 January 2026 to 03 February 2026. Applicants must possess a Bachelor’s degree in Science or Engineering along with approved fire service training and at least 12 years of relevant professional experience. Selection will be carried out based on academic qualifications, work experience and interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC State Fire Officer Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-additional-director-cum-assistant-state-fire-officer-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:29:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-additional-director-cum-assistant-state-fire-officer-jan26/</guid>
      <description>BPSC has announced the Additional Director-cum-Assistant State Fire Officer Recruitment 2026 for 04 vacancies. Applicants must hold a Science or Engineering degree or a recognized Fire Officer qualification with at least 15 years of fire service experience. Selection will be based on a written examination and interview. Online applications are accepted from 13 January to 03 February 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Factory Inspector Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-factory-inspector-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:37:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-factory-inspector-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>BPSC has announced Factory Inspector Recruitment 2026 for 17 vacancies in the Labour Resources Department, Bihar. Eligible candidates with Engineering, Technology or Medical (MBBS) degrees can apply online from 12 January to 02 February 2026. Selection will be made on the basis of academic merit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Assistant Conservator of Forests ACF Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-acf-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:55:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-acf-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>BPSC ACF Recruitment 2026 is released for 12 Assistant Conservator of Forests posts in Bihar. Online applications are open from 12/01/2026 to 02/02/2026 for eligible candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCERT Non-Academic Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/ncert-non-academic-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:51:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/ncert-non-academic-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>NCERT Non-Academic Recruitment 2025 has been announced by the National Council of Educational Research and Training (NCERT) for a total of 173 Non-Academic vacancies. The recruitment will be conducted through Direct Recruitment. The application process will be online, and the last date to apply will be 21 days from the date of publication in Employment News. The selection process will include a Written Examination / Skill Test / Interview, as applicable to the post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar BPSC Stenographer Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-stenographer-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:23:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-stenographer-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Public Service Commission has invited online applications for 15 Stenographer posts under BPSC Recruitment 2026. Eligible candidates with Intermediate qualification and typing and shorthand skills can apply online between 12/01/2026 and 02/02/2026. Selection will be through written and skill tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Maharashtra Apprentice Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:34:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Maharashtra has announced Apprentice Recruitment 2025–26 for 600 posts under the Apprentices Act, 1961. Graduate candidates can apply online for one-year apprenticeship with a monthly stipend of ₹12,300. Selection will be merit-based on 12th/Diploma marks. The online application process is open from 15 January 2026 to 25 January 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPCT Exam Jan-2026 -  Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/cpct-exam-jan-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:44:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/cpct-exam-jan-2026/</guid>
      <description>The CPCT Exam 2026 is scheduled on 16, 17 and 18 January 2026. The online application window will remain open from 15 to 29 December 2025. Applicants need to upload scanned photograph, signature and relevant marksheets. Mock test facility is available, candidates with 12th or 10th plus Polytechnic Diploma are eligible and the CPCT T Scorecard will remain valid for 7 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSSSC Lekhpal Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/up/upsssc-lekhpal-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:34:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/up/upsssc-lekhpal-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>UPSSSC Lekhpal Recruitment 2025 has been announced for a total of 7994 vacancies under the Revenue Department, Government of Uttar Pradesh. Candidates who have passed Intermediate (10+2) and qualified in UPSSSC PET 2025 are eligible to apply online from 29 December 2025 to 28 January 2026, with the selection conducted through the main examination as per the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTA UGC NET December 2025 - Answer Key</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/nta-ugc-net-december-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:32:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/nta-ugc-net-december-2025/</guid>
      <description>The UGC NET December 2025 Notification has been released by the National Testing Agency (NTA) for determining the eligibility of candidates for Assistant Professor and Junior Research Fellowship (JRF) in Indian universities and colleges. Candidates with a Master’s degree (55% marks for General and 50% for reserved categories) can apply online from 07 October to 07 November 2025 at ugcnet.nta.nic.in. The exam will be conducted in Computer Based Test (CBT) mode across multiple subjects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC CGL 2025 Tier - II Admit Card Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-combined-graduate-level-exam-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:27:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-combined-graduate-level-exam-2025/</guid>
      <description>SSC CGL 2025 में आवेदन करने के लिए उम्मीदवार के पास किसी मान्यता प्राप्त विश्वविद्यालय से स्नातक डिग्री होना आवश्यक है। जूनियर स्टैटिस्टिकल ऑफिसर पद के लिए 10+2 स्तर पर गणित में न्यूनतम 60% अंक या स्नातक डिग्री में सांख्यिकी एक विषय होना चाहिए। स्टैटिस्टिकल इन्वेस्टिगेटर ग्रेड-II के लिए भी स्नातक में सांख्यिकी अनिवार्य विषय होना चाहिए। रिसर्च असिस्टेंट (NHRC) और अन्य सभी पदों के लिए किसी भी स्ट्रीम में स्नातक डिग्री मान्य है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Junior Engineer Vacancy 2025 - Application Status</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-je-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:25:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-je-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Railway Recruitment Boards (RRBs) have released the indicative notice for RRB JE Recruitment 2025 under CEN No. 05/2025. A total of 2570 vacancies are announced for Junior Engineer (JE), Depot Material Superintendent (DMS), and Chemical &amp;amp; Metallurgical Assistant (CMA) posts. Eligible candidates can apply online from 31 October 2025 to 30 November 2025. Detailed information on application fees, qualifications, and selection process will be available in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eklavya Model School Class 6 Admission 2026-27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/eklavya-model-school-class-6-admission-2026-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:03:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/eklavya-model-school-class-6-admission-2026-27/</guid>
      <description>Eklavya Model Residential School (EMRS) has released the notification for Class 6 admission for the 2026–27 academic session. Scheduled Tribe (ST) students studying in or passed Class 5 can apply online. Admission will be through an entrance examination followed by document verification. Selected students will receive free residential education with hostel, food, books, uniforms and other facilities under the CBSE curriculum. The application window is open from 10 January 2026 to 10 February 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Female Supervisor Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rj/rssb-female-supervisor-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:52:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rj/rssb-female-supervisor-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Supervisor Female Direct Recruitment 2026 is being conducted by the Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB) for the Women &amp;amp; Child Development Department, Rajasthan. A total of 72 vacancies are available, and only female candidates are eligible to apply. The selection will be based on a written examination of graduation level with negative marking. The salary will be as per Pay Matrix Level-7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Forester / Vanpal Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rj/rajasthan-vanpal-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:52:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rj/rajasthan-vanpal-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Forest Guard (Vanpal) Recruitment 2026 has been released for 259 posts under the Rajasthan Forest Department. Eligible candidates with Senior Secondary (10+2) qualification can apply online through SSO Login. The selection process includes a written examination, physical efficiency test and document verification. Online applications are open from 06/01/2026 to 04/02/2026, and One Time Registration (OTR) fee is applicable as per category.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Clerk Grade II &amp; Junior Assistant Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rj/rssb-clerk-grade-ii-jr-assistant-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:38:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rj/rssb-clerk-grade-ii-jr-assistant-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB) has released the notification for Clerk Grade-II and Junior Assistant Recruitment 2026. A total of 10,644 posts are available for 12th pass candidates with a valid computer qualification. Online applications will be accepted from 15/01/2026 to 13/02/2026, and the written examination is scheduled on 05/07/2026 and 06/07/2026. The recruitment includes posts in both Non-Scheduled and Scheduled Areas. Eligible candidates can apply online through the SSO Recruitment Portal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Assistant Town Planner Supervisor ATPS Online form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-atps-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:27:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-atps-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>BPSC has announced 36 vacancies for the posts of Assistant Town Planner and Town Planning Supervisor under Advertisement No. 07/2026. The recruitment is conducted by the Urban Development &amp;amp; Housing Department, Government of Bihar. Selection will be based on a written examination only. Eligible candidates with qualifications in Town/Urban/Regional Planning or GIS can apply online from 14 January 2026 to 05 February 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSSC Inter Level Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-inter-level-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:52:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-inter-level-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Staff Selection Commission (BSSC) has released the notification for the Inter Level Combined Competitive Exam 2025 with 23,175 vacancies across various departments. Eligible candidates can register online from 15th October 2025 to 25th November 2025, while the final submission deadline is 27th November 2025. The minimum qualification required is Intermediate (10+2) or equivalent along with computer knowledge and typing skills. This is one of the biggest recruitment drives in Bihar offering opportunities for thousands of aspirants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Constable 2025 - Answer key</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-answerkey-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:47:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-answerkey-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the Delhi Police Constable (Executive) Recruitment 2025 notification for 7565 vacancies. Both male and female candidates can apply online from 22 September to 21 October 2025. The recruitment process includes a Computer-Based Examination, followed by Physical Endurance &amp;amp; Measurement Tests (PE&amp;amp;MT). Eligible candidates must have passed 10+2, and male applicants must hold a valid LMV driving license. The pay scale is Level-3 (₹21,700 – ₹69,100). Reserved categories and women candidates are exempted from the application fee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB REET Mains Primary Teacher Level-1 Vacancy 2025- Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSMSSB) has released the Rajasthan Primary Teacher Recruitment 2025 notification for a total of 5636 Level-1 posts under the Primary Education Department and Sanskrit Education Department. Eligible candidates who have passed REET Level-1 can apply online from 07/11/2025 to 06/12/2025 through the official website rsmssb.rajasthan.gov.in. The recruitment includes General and Sanskrit teachers for both Non-TSP and TSP areas. Selection will be based on merit and eligibility as per REET qualification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB REET Mains Upper Primary Teacher Level-II Vacancy 2025 - Admit Card </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-upper-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-upper-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSMSSB) has released the REET Mains Level-II Upper Primary School Teacher Recruitment 2025 for a total of 2123 posts under the Sanskrit Education Department. Eligible candidates can apply online from 07/11/2025 to 06/12/2025 through the official website rsmssb.rajasthan.gov.in. This recruitment includes vacancies for subjects like Sanskrit, Hindi, English, Social Science, and Maths-Science. Applicants must have a Graduation degree with B.Ed/D.El.Ed or 4-Year Integrated B.A./B.Sc. B.Ed as per NCTE norms. The application fee ranges from ₹400 to ₹600, and the exam is expected between 17/01/2026 to 21/01/2026. Interested candidates should check the official notification for eligibility, syllabus, and document requirements before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KVS NVS Teaching &amp; Non-Teaching Vacancy 2025 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/kvs-nvs-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:38:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/kvs-nvs-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>KVS NVS Recruitment 2025 offers more than 14967 Teaching and Non-Teaching vacancies under Kendriya Vidyalaya Sangathan and Navodaya Vidyalaya Samiti. Eligible candidates can apply online from 14/11/2025 to 04/12/2025 for posts such as PRT, TGT, PGT, Principal, Clerk, Stenographer, Librarian and others. The application fee is ₹1500 for General, OBC and EWS categories, while SC, ST, PwD and all female candidates are exempted from fees. Qualifications vary by post and include 10th, 12th, Graduation, Post Graduation, B.Ed, D.El.Ed and CTET. The selection process includes a computer-based test followed by document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nainital Bank PO, SO &amp; CSA Vacancy 2025 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bank/nainital-bank-po-so-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:36:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bank/nainital-bank-po-so-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Nainital Bank Recruitment 2025 has been announced for 185 vacancies including CSA, PO, and Specialist Officer posts. The online application window is open from 12 December 2025 to 01 January 2026, and the written exam will be conducted on 18 January 2026. Eligible graduates, postgraduates, MBA, and CA candidates can apply as per the post requirements. The selection process includes an online examination followed by an interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC NDA 1 2026 - Exam Date</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/upsc/upsc-nda-1-admit-card-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:26:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/upsc/upsc-nda-1-admit-card-2026/</guid>
      <description>UPSC NDA &amp;amp; NA (I) 2026 offers a total of 394 vacancies across Army, Navy and Air Force wings. Eligible unmarried male and female candidates born between 02 July 2007 and 01 July 2010 with 10+2 qualification can apply online until 30 December 2025. Selection includes a written exam, SSB interview and medical test, with the final merit determining admission to NDA and Naval Academy courses starting January 2027.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC GD Constable 2026 - Correction Start</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ssc/ssc-gd-constable-admit-card-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ssc/ssc-gd-constable-admit-card-2026/</guid>
      <description>The SSC GD Constable Recruitment 2026 has been announced for a total of 25,487 vacancies across various forces. The online application process will be conducted from 01/12/2025 to 31/12/2025. Candidates must have passed Class 10th (Matriculation) to be eligible. The selection process includes a Computer-Based Examination (CBT), Physical Efficiency Test (PET), Physical Standard Test (PST), and Medical Examination. The application fee is ₹100 for General/OBC/EWS, while SC/ST, Female, and Ex-Servicemen candidates are exempted from the fee. Detailed force-wise vacancies, age limit, physical standards, and exam pattern are provided in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Project Manager Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-project-manager-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:03:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpsc-project-manager-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>BPSC has invited online applications for the recruitment of 09 Project Manager posts in the Bihar Industries Service. The application process will start from 10th September 2025 and continue till 6th October 2025. Candidates with Engineering, MBA, Economics, CA, CMA, Pharmacy or related qualifications are eligible. The selection will be based on Prelims, Mains and Interview. The post carries a Level-9 pay scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army SSC Tech 67th Women Online Form 2026 </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-army-ssc-tech-67th-women-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:22:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-army-ssc-tech-67th-women-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Indian Army has released the SSC (Tech) 67 Women Recruitment 2026 for unmarried female engineering graduates. A total of 29 posts are available across Civil, Computer Science, Electrical, Electronics, and Mechanical branches. Online applications are open from 2026-01-06 to 2026-02-04 on the official website joinindianarmy.nic.in. Selection will be based on shortlisting, SSB interview, medical examination, and merit list. Training duration is 49 weeks and candidates will receive a stipend of ₹56,100 per month during training</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army SSC Technical 67 Men Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-army-ssc-tech-67th-men-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:29:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-army-ssc-tech-67th-men-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Indian Army has released the SSC (Technical) 67 Men Recruitment 2026 for 350 Technical Officer posts. Unmarried male engineering graduates aged 20 to 27 years can apply online from 07/01/2026 to 05/02/2026 through the official website. Selection will be done through shortlisting, SSB interview, medical examination and merit list. Selected candidates will undergo 49 weeks of training at OTA Gaya and will be commissioned as Lieutenant with an attractive salary and allowances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Group 1 Subgroup 2 Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/mpesb-group-1-sub-group-2-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 10:55:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/mpesb-group-1-sub-group-2-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>MPESB Group 1 Subgroup 2 Recruitment 2025 has been announced for a total of 474 various posts under different departments of the Government of Madhya Pradesh. Candidates having a postgraduate degree in the relevant subject as per departmental recruitment rules are eligible to apply. The online application process will start from 24 December 2025 and will remain open till 07 January 2026 through the official website esb.mp.gov.in. The selection will be conducted through a written examination followed by further procedures as mentioned in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway RRB Technician Exam Date  2025 </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-technician-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:49:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-technician-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has released the RRB Technician Recruitment 2025 notification for Technician Grade-1 (Signal) and Technician Grade-3 (Open Line) posts. Around 6238 vacancies will be filled. Grade-1 requires a B.Sc, BE/B.Tech or 3-year diploma in Physics, Electronics, Computer Science, IT, or Instrumentation. Grade-3 requires 10th pass with ITI in relevant trade from NCVT/SCVT. Eligible candidates can apply online. Please read the official notification for full details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Paramedical Staff 2025 -  Exam Date</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-paramedical-various-posts-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:26:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-paramedical-various-posts-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB), Ministry of Railways, Government of India, has released the Centralized Employment Notice (CEN No. 03/2025) for Paramedical Categories Recruitment 2025 with a total of 434 vacancies across various posts including Nursing Superintendent, Pharmacist, Dialysis Technician, ECG Technician, Radiographer, and Lab Assistant. The online application process will begin on 09 August 2025 and will remain open until 08 September 2025 (11:59 PM). The educational qualifications vary by post, ranging from 10+2 with Diploma/Certificate to B.Sc. in relevant fields, and the age limit is 18 to 40 years as on 01 January 2026. The selected candidates will receive a salary ranging between ₹21,700 and ₹44,900 as per the 7th CPC Pay Matrix (Level 2 to Level 7). The selection process will consist of a Computer Based Test (CBT), Document Verification, and a Medical Examination. Candidates can apply through the official RRB regional websites such as rrbahmedabad.gov.in and others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC CDS 1 Vacancy 2026 - Exam Date</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/upsc/upsc-cds-1-admit-card-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:21:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/upsc/upsc-cds-1-admit-card-2026/</guid>
      <description>UPSC CDS (I) 2026 offers a total of 451 vacancies across IMA, INA, AFA and OTA. Eligible graduate candidates can apply online from 10 to 30 December 2025. The selection process includes a written exam, SSB interview and medical examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSSC Home Guard Havildar Clerk Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpssc-home-guard-havildar-clerk-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:41:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpssc-home-guard-havildar-clerk-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Home Guard Adhinayak Havildar Recruitment 2026 has been released by BPSSC under Advertisement No. 02/2026 for a total of 64 posts reserved for Home Guard quota. Eligible candidates must be Intermediate (10+2) pass, have at least 5 years of Home Guard service, and fall within the age limit of 24 to 50 years as on 01/08/2025. The selection process includes a qualifying written examination followed by a Physical Efficiency Test (PET), on which the final merit list will be prepared. Online applications are accepted from 05/01/2026 to 05/02/2026 through the official BPSSC website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSSC Havildar Clerk Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpssc-havildar-clerk-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:34:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpssc-havildar-clerk-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Havildar Clerk (Adhinayak Lipik) Recruitment 2026 is conducted by the Bihar Police Subordinate Services Commission (BPSSC) for appointment in Bihar Home Guard under the Home Department (Special), Government of Bihar. A total of 64 posts are available for direct recruitment. Eligible candidates who have passed Intermediate (10+2) can apply online from 02 January 2026 to 02 February 2026. The selection process includes a qualifying written examination followed by a Physical Efficiency Test (PET) and document verification. The application fee is ₹100 for all categories, and the recruitment is open to both male and female candidates as per the official notification (Advt. No. 01/2026).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMRS Teaching &amp; Non-Teaching Answer Keyd 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/emrs-teaching-non-teaching-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:22:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/emrs-teaching-non-teaching-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The National Education Society for Tribal Students (NESTS) has announced the EMRS Recruitment 2025 (ESSE-2025) notification for a total of 7267 vacancies across teaching and non-teaching posts. The vacancies include Principal, PGT, TGT, Female Staff Nurse, Hostel Warden, Accountant, Junior Secretariat Assistant (JSA), and Lab Attendant. Candidates can apply online until 23rd October 2025, with application fees ranging from ₹500 to ₹2500 depending on the post and category. The eligibility criteria vary by position, requiring qualifications from 10th/12th to Graduate, Postgraduate, B.Ed., CTET, or professional degrees. The age limit is set between 30 to 50 years, with applicable relaxations for reserved categories. This recruitment provides a major opportunity for aspirants seeking teaching and non-teaching jobs in Eklavya Model Residential Schools (EMRS) across India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Protection Officer Online Form 2025 </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rj/rpsc-protection-officer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 11:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rj/rpsc-protection-officer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>RPSC Protection Officer Recruitment 2025–26 has been announced by the Rajasthan Public Service Commission for 12 posts under the Women and Child Development Department, Government of Rajasthan. The online application process will start on 24 December 2025 and continue till 22 January 2026. Candidates having the required qualification in Law or Social Work are eligible to apply. Selection will be done through a written examination followed by document verification as per RPSC rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Bank Specialist Officer SO Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bank/sbi-bank-so-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 11:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bank/sbi-bank-so-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>State Bank of India has released the Wealth Management Specialist Cadre Officer recruitment for VP Wealth (SRM), AVP Wealth (RM) and Customer Relationship Executive (CRE) posts. Online applications are open from 02 to 23 December 2025. Selection will be based on shortlisting and interview. Eligible candidates with the required qualification, experience and age criteria can apply online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Head Constable Ministerial 2025 - Exam City / Admit Card Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-hc-ministerial-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 10:59:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-hc-ministerial-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for Delhi Police Head Constable (Ministerial) Recruitment 2025. A total of 509 vacancies (341 male &amp;amp; 168 female) are available. Candidates with 10+2 qualification can apply online from 29/09/2025 to 20/10/2025. The selection process includes Computer Based Examination, Physical Endurance &amp;amp; Measurement Test (PE&amp;amp;MT), Typing Test, and Computer Formatting Test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Navy 10&#43;2 B.Tech Cadet Entry July 2026 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-navy-10-2-btech-cadet-entry-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:25:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-navy-10-2-btech-cadet-entry-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Indian Navy 10+2 (B.Tech) Cadet Entry Recruitment 2026 is conducted for admission to a four-year B.Tech course at the Indian Naval Academy, Ezhimala, for grant of Permanent Commission in Executive and Technical Branches. Unmarried male and female candidates who have appeared in JEE (Main) 2025 are eligible to apply. Selection is based on JEE Main CRL shortlisting, SSB Interview, and medical fitness. The recruitment is for 44 posts, including a maximum of 07 posts for women. The online application window is open from 03 January 2026 to 19 January 2026, and no application fee is required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUET (UG) 2026 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/cuet-ug-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:59:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/cuet-ug-2026/</guid>
      <description>CUET (UG) 2026 is an all-India entrance examination conducted by the National Testing Agency for admission to undergraduate programs in Central and other participating universities for the 2026–27 session. Students who have passed or are appearing in Class 12 are eligible to apply. The test is conducted in computer-based mode, permits selection of up to five subjects, and follows a uniform marking scheme. Final admission is offered by universities based on CUET scores, cut-off lists, and course-specific eligibility requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Anganwadi Worker &amp; Helper Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/mp-anganwadi-worker-helper-phase2-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:45:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/mp-anganwadi-worker-helper-phase2-dec25/</guid>
      <description>MP Anganwadi Recruitment 2025 Phase-2 notification has been issued by the Women and Child Development Department, Madhya Pradesh, inviting applications for 4767 posts of Anganwadi Worker and Helper. The recruitment includes 1573 AWW and 3194 AWH vacancies and will be carried out through the MP Online selection portal on a district-wise basis. Only female candidates belonging to the same village or urban ward as the Anganwadi centre are eligible to apply. Applicants must have passed 12th standard, and the prescribed age limit is 18 to 35 years as on 01 January 2025. The online application window will remain open from 31 December 2025 to 10 January 2026, while corrections can be made up to 12 January 2026. Final selection will be based on merit, and no written examination will be held.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Constable Driver 2025 - Answer Key </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-driver-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:24:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-driver-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for Delhi Police Constable (Driver) – Male Recruitment 2025 with 737 vacancies. Applications can be submitted online from 24/09/2025 to 15/10/2025. Candidates must have 10+2 qualification, a valid Heavy Motor Vehicle (HMV) driving license, and knowledge of vehicle maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRDO CEPTAM-11 Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drdo/drdo-ceptam-11-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:20:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drdo/drdo-ceptam-11-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>DRDO CEPTAM-11 Recruitment 2025 has been announced for a total of 764 vacancies, including 561 posts for Senior Technical Assistant-B and 203 posts for Technician-A. The online application process will begin on 09 December 2025 and is expected to remain open until 08 January 2026. Eligible candidates can apply online after checking the required qualification, age limit, and fee details. The exam date will be notified later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC SET Exam 2025 - Exam Date Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/mp-set-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/mp-set-2025/</guid>
      <description>The MP State Eligibility Test (MP SET 2025) is a state-level examination conducted by the Madhya Pradesh Public Service Commission for determining eligibility for Assistant Professor recruitment in colleges and universities of Madhya Pradesh. The online application process will begin on 25 October 2025 and close on 20 November 2025. The written examination is scheduled to be held on 11 January 2026. Candidates are advised to review eligibility conditions, syllabus and subject list as per the official notification before submitting the application form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSBC Bihar Constable Driver Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csbc-bihar-constable-driver-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:11:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csbc-bihar-constable-driver-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>This recruitment has been announced by RailTel Corporation of India Limited for various posts, where candidates will be selected based on interview and document verification. Interested candidates who fulfill all the required qualifications and experience can apply online. The last date to apply is August 5, 2025. This is a great opportunity for candidates aspiring to build a career in the fields of Electronics, Telecom, IT, and Networking. Before applying, all candidates are advised to carefully read the official notification to avoid any mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOI Credit Officer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bank/boi-credit-officer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:39:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bank/boi-credit-officer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Bank of India has released the Credit Officer Recruitment 2025 notification for a total of 514 vacancies under GBO Stream. The recruitment includes posts in MMGS-II, MMGS-III and SMGS-IV scales. Eligible candidates with required qualification and banking experience can apply online through the official website. Selection will be based on an online examination followed by an interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Junior Engineer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/btsc-junior-engineer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:39:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/btsc-junior-engineer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Junior Engineer Recruitment 2025–26 has been announced for 2809 regular vacancies, including 2653 Civil, 86 Electrical and 70 Mechanical posts. Eligible Diploma holders can apply online through BTSC from 12 December 2025 to 11 January 2026. The selection will be done through a Computer Based Test (CBT) followed by a merit list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Work Inspector Mechanical Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/btsc-work-inspector-mechanical-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:39:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/btsc-work-inspector-mechanical-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>BTSC Bihar has announced the Work Inspector (Mechanical) Recruitment 2025 for 493 vacancies. Candidates with 10th pass and ITI qualification in Machinist, Fitter, Wireman or Electrician trades can apply online from 12 December 2025 to 12 January 2026 through the official website btsc.bihar.gov.in. Selection will be based on a Computer Based Test (CBT) followed by document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police Computer Operator Grade-A Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-computer-operator-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:39:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-computer-operator-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Police Computer Operator Grade-A Recruitment 2025 has been announced by the Uttar Pradesh Police Recruitment and Promotion Board (UPPRPB) for a total of 1352 vacancies. The recruitment is for the post of Police Computer Operator Grade-A. Eligible candidates who have passed Intermediate (10+2) and possess a valid computer qualification certificate can apply online from 16/12/2025 to 15/01/2026 through the official UPPRPB website. Selection will be done through a written examination followed by document verification, as per the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Medical Officer, Veterinary &amp; Various Posts Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/up/uppsc-medical-officer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:39:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/up/uppsc-medical-officer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>UPPSC Direct Recruitment 2025 has been announced through Advertisement No. D-6/E-1/2025 for a total of 2158 Group B Gazetted posts. The recruitment includes various medical, veterinary, drug inspector, ayurved, unani and homoeopathy posts across multiple departments of Uttar Pradesh. Eligible candidates can apply online through the OTR based application system from 22/12/2025 to 22/01/2026. Selection will be done through a screening examination followed by interview as per UPPSC rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar Police Sub Inspector Vacancy 2025 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-police-si-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:39:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-police-si-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Police Subordinate Services Commission (BPSSC) has released the Bihar Police SI Recruitment 2025 (Advt. No. 05/2025) for 1799 Sub-Inspector (SI) vacancies in the Home Department (Police Section), Government of Bihar. The pay scale for the post is Level-6 (₹35,400 – ₹1,12,400/-). Eligible candidates must hold a graduation degree from a recognized university by 01 August 2025. The age limit is 20–37 years for UR male candidates, 20–40 years for UR female/BC/EBC, and 20–42 years for SC/ST. The selection process includes a preliminary exam, main written exam, physical efficiency test, followed by document verification and medical test. The online application process will be open from 26 September 2025 to 26 October 2025, and the application fee is ₹100/- (payable online). Interested candidates can apply through the official website bpssc.bihar.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rpsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:00:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rpsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>RPSC Exam Calendar 2026 has been officially released by the Rajasthan Public Service Commission, Ajmer. The calendar provides the tentative schedule of various recruitment examinations to be conducted in 2026, including Deputy Commandant, Lecturer, Sub Inspector, Veterinary Officer, Assistant Engineer, Senior Teacher, Junior Legal Officer, Statistical Officer and other posts. The exams will be held between January 2026 and December 2026, with some examinations conducted in CBRT (Computer Based Recruitment Test) mode. Detailed exam programmes, admit cards and shift information will be issued separately by RPSC as per schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOCL Northern Region Apprentice Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iocl-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:12:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iocl-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>IOCL Northern Region Apprentice Recruitment 2025–26 has been announced for 501 state-wise vacancies for Trade, Technician, and Graduate Apprentice posts. Candidates with 12th, ITI, Diploma, or Graduation qualifications can apply online from 27/12/2025 to 12/01/2026 through the NAPS/NATS portals. The selection process is merit-based with no written examination, and the apprenticeship training duration is 12 months, as per the notification issued by Indian Oil Corporation Limited – Marketing Division, Northern Region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTA NCHM JEE 2026 Admission Test</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/nta-nchm-jee-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:07:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/nta-nchm-jee-2026/</guid>
      <description>NCHM JEE 2026 is a national level entrance examination conducted by the National Testing Agency (NTA) for admission to the B.Sc. Hospitality &amp;amp; Hotel Administration (B.Sc. HHA) course. Candidates who have passed or are appearing in 10+2 with English as a subject are eligible to apply. The examination is conducted in Computer Based Test (CBT) mode, and admission to Central, State, and Private Institutes of Hotel Management is offered based on rank, counselling, and seat availability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB Multi Tasking Staff (MTS) Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/delhi/dsssb-mts-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:31:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/delhi/dsssb-mts-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>DSSSB MTS Recruitment 2025 has been announced for 714 Multi-Tasking Staff (Group-C) posts in various Delhi Government departments. Eligible 10th pass candidates can apply online from 17 December 2025 to 15 January 2026. Selection will be through a CBT exam with negative marking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSF Constable (GD) Sports Quota Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-constable-sports-quota-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:45:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-constable-sports-quota-dec25/</guid>
      <description>BSF Constable (GD) Sports Quota Recruitment 2025 has been announced for 549 posts for eligible male and female sportspersons across India. Candidates who are 10th pass and have valid sports achievements in recognized national or international competitions can apply online from 27/12/2025 to 15/01/2026 at rectt.bsf.gov.in. Selection will be done on the basis of sports merit, Physical Standard Test (PST), document verification and medical examination as per BSF recruitment rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PNB Local Bank Officer LBO 2025 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/pnb-lbo-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/pnb-lbo-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Punjab National Bank (PNB) has released the official notification for LBO Recruitment 2025, offering 750 Local Bank Officer (LBO) vacancies across India. Eligible graduates with at least one year of banking experience can apply online from 03/11/2025 to 23/11/2025 through the official website pnbindia.in. The selection process includes an online written test and interview, and the appointment will be made in the Junior Management Grade Scale-I. Candidates are advised to check their eligibility, fees, age limit, and local language proficiency before applying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHS Bihar ANM Vacancy 2025 Answer Key Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/shs-bihar-anm-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:37:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/shs-bihar-anm-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar SHS is inviting online applications for 5,006 ANM vacancies under HSC, RBSK, and NUHM programs. Only female candidates with a 2-year ANM diploma and BNRC registration are eligible. Applications are open from 14 to 28 August 2025, with selection based on a CBT and document verification. The monthly salary is ₹15,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTET Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/htet-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 17:29:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/htet-2025/</guid>
      <description>HTET 2025 is conducted by the Board of School Education Haryana to determine the eligibility of candidates for Primary Teacher (PRT), Trained Graduate Teacher (TGT), and Post Graduate Teacher (PGT) posts in Haryana. Candidates can apply for Level-1, Level-2, or Level-3 based on their educational qualification. The HTET certificate is valid for a lifetime, there is no limit on attempts, and the examination is conducted in offline (pen and paper) mode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rrb-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:00:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rrb-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has released the official RRB Exam Calendar 2026 outlining the recruitment planning schedule for various railway posts. The calendar includes major categories such as Assistant Loco Pilot (ALP), Technicians, NTPC (Graduate and Under Graduate), Junior Engineer (JE), Paramedical, Ministerial &amp;amp; Isolated posts, Section Controller, and Level-1 (Group D). It provides a clear timeline for vacancy assessment, OIRMS assessment, indenting process, and draft CEN preparation across different quarters of 2026. This calendar helps candidates understand the expected recruitment cycle; however, actual notifications and exam dates will be released separately through individual CENs by the respective RRBs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC CPO SI 2025 - Answer Key</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-cpo-si-capf-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 10:26:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-cpo-si-capf-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for CPO SI Recruitment 2025, offering 3073 vacancies for Sub-Inspector posts in Delhi Police and CAPFs. Eligible candidates with a bachelor’s degree can apply online from 26 September to 16 October 2025. The selection process includes a Computer-Based Test (Paper-I &amp;amp; II), Physical Tests (PST/PET), Medical Examination, and Document Verification. This recruitment provides an excellent opportunity for graduates to join Delhi Police and CAPFs with a pay scale of Level-6 (₹35,400 – ₹1,12,400).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of India Apprentice Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 10:24:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Bank of India Apprentice Recruitment 2025 has been announced for a total of 400 apprenticeship positions across various states of India. The recruitment is open to graduate candidates who meet the prescribed age and eligibility criteria. The online application process will be conducted from 25 December 2025 to 10 January 2026. Selection will be based on an online written test followed by a local language proficiency test. The apprenticeship training duration is one year, during which selected candidates will receive a monthly stipend of ₹13,000. This program is designed to provide hands-on banking experience but does not guarantee permanent employment in the bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:40:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Union Public Service Commission (UPSC) has released the official Programme of Examinations / Recruitment Tests (RTs) Calendar 2026. The calendar includes the complete schedule of major UPSC examinations such as Civil Services (Preliminary &amp;amp; Main), NDA &amp;amp; NA (I &amp;amp; II), CDS (I &amp;amp; II), CAPF (ACs), IES/ISS, Combined Medical Services (CMS), Indian Forest Service, Engineering Services, Geo-Scientist Exams, and several Reserved Recruitment Tests. It provides important details including notification dates, last dates to apply, exam commencement dates, and duration of each examination. Candidates preparing for UPSC exams in 2026 are advised to regularly check official updates, as dates are subject to change based on administrative requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Sports Trainer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/btsc-sports-trainer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:58:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/btsc-sports-trainer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Sports Trainer (क्रीड़ा प्रशिक्षक) Recruitment 2025 notification has been released by the Bihar Technical Service Commission (BTSC) for a total of 48 vacancies. The recruitment is for Sports Trainer posts under the state sports services. Eligible candidates having Graduation along with required sports qualification or state/national level sports participation can apply online. The online application process will start from 22/12/2025 and will continue till 22/01/2026. Selection of candidates will be done through a Computer Based Test (CBT) as per the official rules. This recruitment offers a good opportunity for candidates seeking government jobs in the sports sector in Bihar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Section Controller Recruitment 2025- Exam Date</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrb-section-controller-admitcard-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:30:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrb-section-controller-admitcard-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has announced 368 vacancies for Section Controller posts through CEN 04/2025. The online application process will be open from 15 September to 14 October 2025. Candidates with a graduation degree and age between 20 to 33 years can apply. Selection will be based on a Computer-Based Test, skill test (if required), document verification, and medical examination. The post offers a Level 6 pay scale with attractive allowances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar BPSC AEDO Online Form 2025 - Exam Date</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-bpsc-aedo-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:29:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-bpsc-aedo-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has released the official notification for 935 Assistant Education Development Officer (AEDO) vacancies under the Education Department. The online application process will begin on 27 August 2025 and continue till 26 September 2025. Candidates with a graduate degree from a recognized university are eligible to apply. The salary will be as per Level-5 pay scale (₹29,200 + allowances). Applicants must pay an examination fee of ₹100/- plus bank charges through online mode. Interested candidates should visit the official website bpsc.bihar.gov.in to apply online and check detailed guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uttar Pradesh Home Guard Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-home-guard-recruitment-exam-date-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:21:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-home-guard-recruitment-exam-date-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Home Guard Recruitment 2025 has announced 41,424 vacancies for Home Guard (Male/Female) posts across all districts of the state. The online application process will run from 18 November 2025 to 17 December 2025. Candidates must have passed Class 10 (High School) from a recognized board and must be between 18 to 30 years of age as on 01 July 2025. The selection process includes Physical Standards Test (PST) and Physical Efficiency Test (PET), where male candidates must complete 4.8 km in 28 minutes and female candidates must complete 2.4 km in 16 minutes. The application fee is ₹400 for General/OBC/EWS and ₹300 for SC/ST candidates. The complete district-wise vacancy list and PET/PST rules are provided in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Jamadar Grade-II Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-jamadar-grade-ii-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:08:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-jamadar-grade-ii-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSMSSB) has released the official notification for Jamadar Grade-II Recruitment 2025 under the Public Works Department (PWD). A total of 72 posts are available — 64 for Non-Scheduled Area and 8 for Scheduled Area. Eligible candidates who have passed Senior Secondary (12th) and possess a valid computer qualification (like RSCIT, DOEACC “O” Level, COPA, or Diploma in Computer Science) can apply online. The online application process will be active from 17/10/2025 to 15/11/2025, and the OMR-based exam will be conducted on 27/12/2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Ayush Officer Admit Card  2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-ayush-officer-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:07:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-ayush-officer-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB), Jaipur has issued Advertisement No. 06/2025 for the recruitment of 1535 Contractual Ayush Officers (Ayurved, Homoeopathy, Unani) under the National Health Mission (NHM), Rajasthan. Eligible candidates can apply online through the SSO Rajasthan Portal from 10 October 2025 to 08 November 2025. The recruitment will be on a one-year contract basis, extendable as per the project duration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBPS RRBs CRP XIV Office Assistant Scale I, II, III Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-rrbs-crp-xiv-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:03:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-rrbs-crp-xiv-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>IBPS has announced the CRP RRBs XIV Recruitment 2025-26 with 13217 vacancies for Office Assistants and Officers (Scale I, II &amp;amp; III) in Regional Rural Banks. Online applications are open from 1st to 21st September 2025 at ibps.in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAN Card - New PAN, Correction, e-PAN Download &amp; Status Check</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/apply-pan-card-and-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:09:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/apply-pan-card-and-details/</guid>
      <description>PAN Card is a permanent identification number issued by the Income Tax Department of India for tax and financial transactions. This page provides complete information about PAN Card including online application, correction, verification, Aadhaar linking, e-PAN, required documents, uses for job and business, and important rules in a simple and clear format.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police SI Confidential, ASI Clerk and Accounts Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-si-confidential-asi-clerk-accounts-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:08:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-si-confidential-asi-clerk-accounts-dec25/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Police Recruitment and Promotion Board (UPPRPB) has released the notification for Police Sub Inspector (Confidential) and Police Assistant Sub Inspector (Clerk &amp;amp; Accounts) Recruitment 2025 under Advertisement No. PRPB-B (Cl.)/2025. A total of 537 vacancies are available. The online application process will start on 20/12/2025 and end on 19/01/2026. Candidates are required to meet the prescribed educational qualifications and age criteria as per the official notification. Selection will be conducted through a written examination followed by skill test (where applicable), document verification and medical examination. Only Physical Standard Test (PST) will be conducted; no PET is applicable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Polytechnic Lecturer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/up/uppsc-polytechnic-lecturer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:23:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/up/uppsc-polytechnic-lecturer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>UPPSC has released the Technical Education (Teaching) Service Recruitment 2025 for 513 posts of Polytechnic Lecturers, Workshop Superintendent, and Architecture faculty. Eligible candidates can apply online from 02 December 2025 to 02 January 2026. Selection will be based on a written exam and interview. Engineering posts require First Class B.Tech/M.Tech, while non-engineering posts require First Class Master’s degree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Police ASI &amp; Subedar Stenographer Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mp-police-asi-subedar-answerkey-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 17:30:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mp-police-asi-subedar-answerkey-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Madhya Pradesh Police Headquarters has announced 500 vacancies for Subedar (Stenographer) and Assistant Sub Inspector (Clerk) posts under direct and departmental recruitment. Eligible candidates with 12th pass and computer proficiency (CPCT/Hindi Typing) can apply online via MPESB from 03 October to 17 October 2025. The written exam will start on 10 December 2025. Reservation benefits and age relaxation are applicable only for MP domicile candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOCL Non-Executive Personnel Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/iocl-non-executive-personnel-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:08:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/iocl-non-executive-personnel-dec25/</guid>
      <description>IOCL Non-Executive Recruitment 2025 has been announced by Indian Oil Corporation Limited for various non-executive posts in its Refineries Division. The recruitment is open for Diploma and B.Sc qualified candidates to fill Junior Engineering Assistant, Junior Technical Assistant and Quality Control Analyst positions across multiple refinery locations in India. The selection will be based on a Computer Based Test followed by a qualifying Skill/Proficiency/Physical Test. Online applications are invited from 20 December 2025 to 09 January 2026 with a pay scale ranging from ₹25,000 to ₹1,05,000 along with standard PSU allowances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCRH Research Officer &amp; Other Posts Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-research-officer-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-research-officer-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Central Council for Research in Homoeopathy (CCRH), under the Ministry of AYUSH, Government of India, has released the CCRH Recruitment 2025 Notification (Advt. No. 179/2025-26) for 48 vacancies across Group A, B and C posts. Eligible candidates can apply online from 05 November 2025 to 26 November 2025 through the official websites - ccrhindia.ayush.gov.in, ccrhonline.in or eapplynow.com. The recruitment includes posts like Research Officer, Junior Librarian, Pharmacist, X-Ray Technician, LDC, and Driver. Selection will be based on a Computer-Based Test (CBT) and an interview (for Group-A). Interested applicants should read the full notification for eligibility, qualification, age limit, and application fee details before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCRH Staff Nurse, MLT, Stenographer &amp; ARO Answer Key  2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-mlt-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:58:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-mlt-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Central Council for Research in Homoeopathy (CCRH) has released the official notification Advt. No. 180/2025-26 for 42 Group B &amp;amp; C vacancies including Staff Nurse, Medical Laboratory Technologist, Junior Stenographer, Junior MLT, and Assistant Research Officer (Pharmacognosy). The online application process will be open from 05/11/2025 to 26/11/2025. Candidates must apply through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ccrhindia.nic.in&#34;&gt;www.ccrhindia.nic.in&lt;/a&gt;. The application fee is ₹500 for UR/OBC/EWS, while SC/ST/PwD/Female candidates are exempted. Selection will be based on a Computer Based Test (CBT) followed by document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Village Development Officer VDO Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-village-development-officer-vdo-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:35:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-village-development-officer-vdo-2025/</guid>
      <description>राजस्थान कर्मचारी चयन बोर्ड (RSSB) द्वारा ग्राम विकास अधिकारी (VDO) पदों पर भर्ती के लिए अधिसूचना जारी कर दी गई है। इच्छुक और पात्र उम्मीदवार जो भारत के किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त विश्वविद्यालय से स्नातक हैं और जिनके पास O लेवल, COPA, DPCS, कंप्यूटर डिप्लोमा या RS-CIT प्रमाण पत्र है, वे इस भर्ती के लिए ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। भर्ती से जुड़ी पात्रता, आयु सीमा, आवेदन तिथि, चयन प्रक्रिया और अन्य जानकारी के लिए आधिकारिक नोटिफिकेशन जरूर पढ़ें।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC Jr Engineer Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-junior-engineer-je-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:31:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-junior-engineer-je-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for the Junior Engineer (JE) Recruitment 2025. The vacancies are available in various departments such as BRO, CPWD, CWC, MES, NTRO, and others for trades including Civil, Electrical, and Mechanical. Candidates must have a Diploma or Degree in the relevant engineering discipline. Some departments also require two years of work experience. The application process is completely online, and the selection will be based on a Computer-Based Test (Paper 1), Paper 2, and Document Verification. This recruitment is open to both male and female candidates across India. Interested applicants can visit the official SSC website &lt;a href=&#34;https://ssc.gov.in&#34;&gt;https://ssc.gov.in&lt;/a&gt; for more details and to apply online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPKVVCL Line Attendant Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/mppkvvcl-line-attendant-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:30:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/mppkvvcl-line-attendant-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Madhya Pradesh Paschim Kshetra Vidyut Vitaran Company Limited (MPWZ / MPPKVVCL) has released a notification for 4009 vacancies including AE, JE, Line Attendant, Test Assistant, Stenographer and various other posts. The online application will start from 20 December 2025 and the last date to apply is 21 January 2026. Candidates from all states can apply. Selection will be based on a written exam and document verification. Salary ranges from ₹18,000 to ₹42,700 per month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Probationary Officers PO Final Result 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-probationary-officers-po-bharti-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:33:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-probationary-officers-po-bharti-2025/</guid>
      <description>The State Bank of India (SBI) has released the notification for the recruitment of 541 Probationary Officer (PO) posts, including 500 regular posts and 41 backlog posts. Candidates must have a Bachelor’s degree in any stream from a recognized university in India to be eligible. The category-wise distribution of vacancies is as follows: UR – 203, OBC – 135, EWS – 50, SC – 80, and ST – 73. The application process will be conducted online through the official SBI website at sbi.co.in. This is a golden opportunity for graduates seeking a prestigious career in banking with SBI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB OTR One-Time Registration 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/otr/dsssb-otr-one-time-registration-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:09:29 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/otr/dsssb-otr-one-time-registration-online/</guid>
      <description>DSSSB One-Time Registration (OARS) allows candidates to create a unique login to apply for multiple posts under the Delhi Subordinate Services Selection Board. The registration process requires personal, academic, and ID details, along with uploading photograph and signature. Once registered, candidates can easily apply for DSSSB vacancies online, check application status, and retrieve login credentials if needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC OTR 2025 – One Time Registration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/otr/ssc-otr-online-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:55:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/otr/ssc-otr-online-form/</guid>
      <description>SSC OTR 2025 allows candidates to create a single profile for multiple SSC exams. Register online once, fill personal and educational details, upload documents, and easily apply for upcoming SSC exams. Check eligibility, important dates, fees, and registration steps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Candidate Profiling / Profile Panjiyan Form Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/profile/mpesb-candidate-profile-panjiyan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:13:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/profile/mpesb-candidate-profile-panjiyan/</guid>
      <description>To apply for any government recruitment under the Madhya Pradesh Employees Selection Board (MPESB), all candidates must complete the Candidate Profile Registration process. This is a one-time mandatory step where applicants register using Aadhaar eKYC, upload personal and academic details, and receive a unique Profile ID. This ID is required for all future MPESB applications. The process is simple, online, and essential for anyone seeking government jobs in Madhya Pradesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar Vidhan Parishad Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-vidhan-parishad-office-attendant-driver-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 10:25:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-vidhan-parishad-office-attendant-driver-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Vidhan Parishad Secretariat has released the official notification for 24 vacancies including 09 Driver and 15 Office Attendant posts. Eligible candidates with a minimum qualification of Matric (10th Pass) can apply online from 29/09/2025 to 20/10/2025. Selection will be based on a written exam, while Driver posts also require a driving skill test. Interested applicants are advised to read the official notification for detailed eligibility, age limit, and application process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRLPS JEEViKA Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-brlps-jeevika-form-aug25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 10:19:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-brlps-jeevika-form-aug25/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Rural Livelihoods Promotion Society (BRLPS), under the Rural Development Department of the Government of Bihar, has released the official notification for JEEViKA Recruitment 2025. A total of 2747 vacancies have been announced across various posts including Block Project Manager, Livelihood Specialist, Area Coordinator, Accountant, Office Assistant, Community Coordinator, and Block IT Executive. The required educational qualifications vary by post, ranging from Intermediate (for female Community Coordinators) to Graduation, Post-Graduation, Diploma, or B.Tech. The minimum age for applicants is 18 years, while the upper age limit goes up to 42 years depending on the category. The selection process involves a Computer-Based Test (CBT) and a typing test for relevant positions. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://brlps.in&#34;&gt;https://brlps.in&lt;/a&gt; from 30th July to 18th August 2025. This is a great opportunity to contribute to Bihar’s largest rural development mission and support the empowerment of rural communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSF Head Constable (RO/RM) PET / PST Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-head-constable-ro-rm-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 10:15:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-head-constable-ro-rm-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>BSF Head Constable Recruitment 2025 has been released to fill 1121 technical posts of Radio Operator and Radio Mechanic. The application window will remain open from 24 August to 23 September 2025. Eligible candidates must have 12th pass with PCM or 10th pass along with ITI qualification as prescribed. The selection procedure consists of a written exam, physical test and medical examination. This recruitment provides a valuable opportunity for candidates seeking a technical government job in the Border Security Force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC Food Safety Officer Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppsc-food-safety-officer-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:04:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppsc-food-safety-officer-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>Madhya Pradesh Public Service Commission (MPPSC) has released a notification for the recruitment of Food Safety Officer (FSO) with a total of 67 vacancies. The application process will be conducted online, and the job location is Madhya Pradesh. Candidates from all over India are eligible to apply, but those from other states will be treated as General (UR) category and will not receive any reservation or fee relaxation. Applicants must hold a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s, Master&amp;rsquo;s, or Ph.D. degree in Food Technology, Agriculture, Biotechnology, Chemistry, Veterinary Science, Medicine, or a related field, or possess an equivalent qualification recognized by the Central Government. The age limit is 21 to 40 years, with age relaxation applicable as per rules for reserved categories. For complete details and to apply, visit the official website mppsc.mp.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IB Security Assistant/Executive Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-security-assistant-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:17:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-security-assistant-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau (IB), under the Ministry of Home Affairs (MHA), has released a notification for the recruitment of Security Assistant/Executive posts for the year 2025. A total of 4987 vacancies are available across various states and Union Territories. Candidates must have passed 10th standard, possess knowledge of the local language/dialect, and hold a domicile certificate of the region applied for. The post offers a Level-3 pay scale (₹21,700 – ₹69,100) along with special allowances. This is a central government Group &amp;lsquo;C&amp;rsquo; non-gazetted, non-ministerial post, offering job security and growth in the intelligence sector. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online through the official portal before the last date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:01:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Madhya Pradesh Public Service Commission has published the MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 to inform candidates about the tentative schedule of upcoming examinations. According to the calendar, important exams such as State Service Main Examination 2025, Assistant Professor Examinations 2025 and 2026, State Engineering Service Examination 2025, and State Service and Forest Service Preliminary and Main Examinations 2026 will be held from January 2026 to September 2026. This exam calendar helps aspirants plan their preparation in advance, though exam dates may be revised due to administrative reasons or court orders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:21:02 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The MPESB Exam Calendar 2026 lists the expected timeline of examinations conducted by MPESB for government recruitment and professional entrance courses. According to the calendar, exams for various groups, police, nursing, technical and teaching posts are proposed between February and October 2026. Aspirants can refer to this calendar to organize their study plan, while official notifications will confirm exact dates and further details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOB Apprentice 2025 - Exam Date Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:39:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Baroda has released the official notification for 2700 Apprentice posts under the Apprentices Act, 1961. The online application process started on 11 November 2025 and will continue till 01 December 2025. Candidates having a Graduation Degree in any discipline can apply through the official website bankofbaroda.in or via the BFSI SSC portal. Selection will be done through an Online Exam, Document Verification, and Local Language Test. Selected candidates will receive a monthly stipend of ₹15,000 during the 1-year apprenticeship training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assam Police Constable Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/assam/assam-police-constable-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 10:37:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/assam/assam-police-constable-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Assam Police ने Constable (UB) के 1052 और Constable (AB) के 663 पदों के लिए भर्ती प्रक्रिया शुरू की है। आवेदन 16/12/2025 से 16/01/2026 तक बिना किसी शुल्क के किए जा सकेंगे। केवल Assam के Permanent Residents जिनका Employment Exchange Registration Assam में है, वही आवेदन कर सकते हैं। UB के लिए 12th pass और AB के लिए 10th pass आवश्यक है। चयन प्रक्रिया में PST, PET, Written Exam और Viva शामिल हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bombay High Court Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mh/bombay-high-court-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 10:37:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mh/bombay-high-court-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Bombay High Court Recruitment 2025 में कुल 2381 पदों पर भर्ती निकली है, जिसमें Clerk, Peon, Driver और Stenographer शामिल हैं। आवेदन 15 दिसंबर 2025 से 5 जनवरी 2026 तक ऑनलाइन स्वीकार किए जाएंगे। पात्र उम्मीदवार Graduation, 10th Pass या 7th Pass योग्यता अनुसार आवेदन कर सकते हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi DDA Recruitment 2025- Admit Card Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/delhi-dda-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:35:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/delhi-dda-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Delhi Development Authority (DDA) has released its Recruitment Notification 2025 for a total of 1732 vacancies across various posts including Deputy Director, Assistant Director, Junior Engineer, Stenographer, Patwari, Mali, and Multi Tasking Staff (MTS). The online application process is scheduled from 06 October 2025 to 05 November 2025, and the Computer Based Test (CBT) is expected in December 2025 – January 2026. Candidates can apply online through the official DDA website. The recruitment includes category-wise vacancies (UR, EWS, SC, ST, OBC) and posts for ESM / PwBD candidates. Qualifications vary by post, ranging from 10th/12th pass to Graduate/Degree holders in relevant fields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPGCL Plant Assistant Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppgcl-assistant-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:14:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppgcl-assistant-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>MPPGCL has released the notification for Plant Assistant Recruitment 2025 with a total of 90 vacancies for Mechanical (53) and Electrical (37) posts. Only male candidates with ITI qualification can apply. The online application process will run from 01/12/2025 to 30/12/2025. Selection will be based on a Computer Based Test followed by document verification. Salary will be provided as per Level-6 after successful training and probation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAI Junior Assistant &amp; Senior Assistant Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/aai-ner-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 10:09:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/aai-ner-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>AAI North Eastern Region has released the recruitment notification for 14 Non-Executive posts, including Senior Assistant (Electronics), Junior Assistant (HR), and Junior Assistant (Fire Services). Only candidates who are domicile of the North Eastern states—Assam, Arunachal Pradesh, Manipur, Meghalaya, Mizoram, Nagaland, and Tripura—are eligible to apply. The online application process will remain open from 12 December 2025 to 11 January 2026. The selection process includes a Computer-Based Test (CBT), document verification, and physical/medical tests for Fire Services. Eligible candidates are advised to apply online through the AAI official website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police Assistant Operator Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-assistant-operator-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 10:09:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-assistant-operator-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>UP Police has released the Assistant Operator Recruitment 2025 for 44 posts under the Police Radio Cadre. Eligible 12th PCM passed candidates aged 18–22 years can apply online from 03/12/2025 to 02/01/2026. The selection includes a written exam, PST, PET and document verification. Application fee is ₹500 for General/OBC/EWS and ₹400 for SC/ST.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IIMC Non-Teaching Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/delhi/iimc-non-teaching-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:34:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/delhi/iimc-non-teaching-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Indian Institute of Mass Communication (IIMC) has invited online applications for 51 non-teaching vacancies across Delhi and regional centres. Selection will be through written test and skill test (and interview for Group A posts). Online applications close on 12/01/2026 and hard copy must reach by 19/01/2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Pump Operator Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/btsc-pump-operator-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:30:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/btsc-pump-operator-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>BTSC Bihar has announced the Pump Operator Recruitment 2025 for a total of 191 vacancies. Candidates who have passed 10th (Matric) along with ITI in Machinist or Fitter trade are eligible to apply online from 12 December 2025 to 12 January 2026 through the official website btsc.bih.nic.in. The selection process will be conducted through a Computer Based Test (CBT) followed by document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Dental Hygienist Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-dental-hygienist-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 15:04:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-dental-hygienist-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Technical Service Commission (BTSC) has released the Dental Hygienist Recruitment 2025 notification for 702 posts under the Health Department. Eligible candidates with a Diploma in Dental Hygienist can apply online from 10 October to 10 November 2025. Selection will be based on a merit list prepared from academic qualifications. Check eligibility, salary, and application process below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Hostel Manager Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-hostel-manager-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 15:04:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-hostel-manager-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Technical Service Commission (BTSC) has released the Hostel Manager Recruitment 2025 notification for 91 posts under the Backward and Extremely Backward Class Welfare Department. Eligible candidates with a Bachelor’s Degree or Diploma in Hotel Management can apply online through the official website btsc.bihar.gov.in. The selection will be based on a written examination and document verification. Candidates are advised to check the eligibility criteria, age limit, and reservation details before submitting the online form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Works Supervisor Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-works-supervisor-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 15:04:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-works-supervisor-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>BTSC Works Supervisor Recruitment 2025 (Advt. 25/2025) is out for 1114 posts under PHED Bihar. Apply online from 10 Oct to 10 Nov 2025. Eligibility: Matric (10th) + ITI in Draughtsman (Civil) / Surveyor / Plumber. Selection via CBT (100 MCQs, 2 hrs, 0.25 negative); Level-2 pay; category-wise and 35% female (horizontal) reservation applicable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IAF AFCAT 01/2026 Batch Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iaf-afcat-01-2026-batch-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 10:41:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iaf-afcat-01-2026-batch-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Air Force (IAF) has announced the AFCAT 01/2026 Batch Recruitment 2025 for Flying and Ground Duty (Technical &amp;amp; Non-Technical) branches. The online application process will begin on 10 November 2025 and continue till 9 December 2025 through the official website afcat.cdac.in. Candidates holding a graduate or engineering degree with Physics and Mathematics at 10+2 level can apply. The selection process includes an online written test, AFSB interview, and medical examination. Successful candidates will join the AFCAT 01/2026 course commencing in January 2026 as Group-A Gazetted Officers in the Indian Air Force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIR NCL Technician (1) &amp; Technical Assistant Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/csir-ncl-technical-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 10:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/csir-ncl-technical-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>CSIR–NCL Recruitment 2025 has announced 34 vacancies including 15 Technician (1) and 19 Technical Assistant posts. Eligible 10th+ITI, Diploma and B.Sc candidates can apply online from 12 December 2025 to 12 January 2026. Selection will be based on Trade Test and a three-paper written examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KVS LDE/LDCE Teaching and Non-Teaching Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/kvs-ldce-teaching-and-non-teaching-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:57:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/kvs-ldce-teaching-and-non-teaching-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>KVS LDE/DE Recruitment 2026 has announced 2499 vacancies for Principal, Vice-Principal, PGT, TGT, Head Master, Finance Officer, Section Officer and Secretariat Assistant posts. Eligible KVS employees can apply online from 11 December 2025 to 26 December 2025, and the controlling officer verification will close on 02 January 2026. The LDE/DE examination is scheduled for 15 February 2026. No application fee is required for any category.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHS Bihar Ophthalmic Assistant Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bihar-shs-ophthalmic-assistant-admitcard-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bihar-shs-ophthalmic-assistant-admitcard-2025/</guid>
      <description>State Health Society Bihar is inviting applications for 220 Ophthalmic Assistant posts under Advt. No. 07/2025. Candidates with 10+2 in Biology/Mathematics and a 2-year Diploma in Optometry or Ophthalmic Assistant are eligible. The application window is open from 14 to 28 August 2025, with a monthly salary of ₹15,000. Selection will be through CBT, document verification, and medical examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Assistant Teacher Bharti 2025 Answer Key Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-assistant-teacher-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:46:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-assistant-teacher-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Directorate of Medical Education and Research (DMER) has announced a recruitment drive for 7466 Assistant Teacher posts. Candidates must hold a Bachelor’s Degree in the relevant subject from any recognized university in India. Detailed eligibility criteria and subject-wise qualifications will be released soon. Interested applicants are advised to stay updated with the official notification and prepare to apply online as per the given schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBPS SO XV 15th Mains Result 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-specialist-officer-so-15th-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:05:12 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-specialist-officer-so-15th-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Institute of Banking Personnel Selection (IBPS) has released the notification for the Specialist Officer (SO) CRP SPL-XV Recruitment 2025. A total of 1007 vacancies have been announced for various Scale I posts including IT Officer, Agriculture Field Officer (AFO), Rajbhasha Adhikari, Law Officer, HR/Personnel Officer, and Marketing Officer. The online application process will be open from 1st July 2025 to 21st July 2025. The Preliminary Examination is scheduled for August 2025, followed by the Main Examination in November 2025. Interviews are likely to be conducted in January/February 2026. Applications will be accepted in online mode only. For more details and to apply, visit the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibps.in&#34;&gt;www.ibps.in&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCF Kapurthala Apprentice Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rcf-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:28:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rcf-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Rail Coach Factory Kapurthala has announced 550 Act Apprentice vacancies for various ITI trades. Eligible candidates from all states can apply online until 07 January 2026. Selection will be based on merit prepared from 10th and ITI marks, followed by document verification and a medical exam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC 10&#43;2 CHSL 2025 Answer Key Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-chsl-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 10:34:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-chsl-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>कर्मचारी चयन आयोग (SSC) द्वारा CHSL (10+2) भर्ती 2025 का नोटिफिकेशन जारी किया गया है। इस भर्ती के अंतर्गत लोअर डिवीजन क्लर्क (LDC), डाटा एंट्री ऑपरेटर (DEO), डाक सहायक (PA) व छंटाई सहायक (SA) जैसे पदों पर नियुक्तियाँ की जाएंगी। भारत के किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 12वीं (इंटरमीडिएट) उत्तीर्ण उम्मीदवार इसके लिए आवेदन कर सकते हैं। आवेदन प्रक्रिया पूरी तरह ऑनलाइन है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WBBPE Assistant Teacher Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/wbbpe-assistant-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 10:29:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/wbbpe-assistant-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The West Bengal Board of Primary Education (WBBPE) has released the official notification for 13,421 Assistant Teacher (Primary) posts in Government and Government-aided schools. The online application process will run from 19 November 2025 (3:00 PM) to 9 December 2025 (11:59 PM). Candidates with 12th + D.El.Ed or B.El.Ed are eligible. The application fee is ₹600 for General, ₹500 for OBC, and ₹300 for SC/ST/PH applicants. Selection will be based on merit, interview, and document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haryana Medical Officer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hr/haryana-health-department-mo-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:26:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hr/haryana-health-department-mo-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Health Department Haryana has announced 450 vacancies for Medical Officer (HCMS-I) posts. MBBS-qualified candidates with valid medical registration can apply online from 08 December 2025 to 07 January 2026. The age limit is 22–35 years with category-wise relaxations. Application fee ranges from NIL to ₹1000 depending on category.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Air Force Apprentice Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iaf-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:52:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iaf-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Indian Air Force Apprentice 2026 भर्ती में कुल 144 ITI ट्रेड पदों पर आवेदन आमंत्रित किए गए हैं। यह प्रशिक्षण Base Repair Depot, Chandigarh में आयोजित होगा। आवेदन की अंतिम तिथि 30 दिसंबर 2025 है। पात्र उम्मीदवार 17 से 35 वर्ष आयु सीमा के भीतर ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। चयन प्रक्रिया में लिखित परीक्षा, इंटरव्यू, मेडिकल वेरिफिकेशन और मेरिट लिस्ट शामिल है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGPSC Assistant Professor Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cg/cgpsc-assistant-professor-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cg/cgpsc-assistant-professor-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>CGPSC Assistant Professor (Medical Education) Recruitment 2025 के तहत कुल 125 पदों के लिए ऑनलाइन आवेदन आमंत्रित किए गए हैं। आवेदन 25 नवंबर से 24 दिसंबर 2025 तक स्वीकार किए जाएंगे। इस भर्ती में संबंधित मेडिकल स्पेशलिटी में MD/MS/DNB योग्यता और न्यूनतम 1 वर्ष का Senior Resident अनुभव आवश्यक है। Chhattisgarh domicile उम्मीदवारों के लिए फीस में छूट और परीक्षा में उपस्थित होने पर फीस रिफंड का प्रावधान है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGPSC SSE Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cg/cgpsc-sse-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cg/cgpsc-sse-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>CGPSC SSE 2025 भर्ती में कुल 238 पद जारी किए गए हैं। आवेदन 01 से 30 दिसंबर 2025 तक ऑनलाइन होंगे। योग्यता स्नातक, आयु सीमा 21–30 वर्ष (CG Domicile: 35 वर्ष) है। चयन प्रक्रिया में Pre, Mains और Interview शामिल हैं। SC/ST/OBC के लिए आवेदन शुल्क ₹300 और अन्य सभी के लिए ₹400 है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IB Multi Tasking Staff Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-mts-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 10:31:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-mts-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau has released the IB MTS Recruitment 2025 notification for 362 Multi-Tasking Staff (General) posts across various SIBs in India. Candidates who have passed Class 10 and possess a valid state domicile certificate can apply online from 22/11/2025 to 14/12/2025. The selection process includes a Tier-I objective exam and a Tier-II descriptive exam. Application fees are ₹650 for General/OBC/EWS male applicants and ₹550 for all other categories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Head Constable  2025 - Self Slot Booking</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-head-constable-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 12:13:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-head-constable-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for Delhi Police Head Constable (Assistant Wireless Operator/Tele-Printer Operator) Recruitment 2025. A total of 552 vacancies are available, including 370 posts for male candidates and 182 posts for female candidates. The online application process will remain open from 24 September to 15 October 2025. Candidates must have passed 10+2 with Science and Mathematics or hold an NTC in Mechanic-cum-Operator Electronic Communication System. The age limit is 18 to 27 years, with applicable relaxations for reserved categories. The selection process includes a Computer Based Examination, Physical Endurance &amp;amp; Measurement Test (PE&amp;amp;MT), Trade Test, and Computer Proficiency Test. The pay scale is Level-4 (₹25,500 – ₹81,100) as per the 7th CPC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Sports Officer Exam Date Out 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-sports-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 12:02:29 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-sports-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has announced 33 vacancies for the posts of District Sports Officer, Assistant Director (Sports/Youth), and Lecturer (SH &amp;amp; Colleges) under the Bihar Sports Service Cadre through Advt. No. 90/2025. Candidates with a Graduate Degree and a Diploma/PG Diploma in Sports Coaching from a recognized institute are eligible to apply. The online application window will remain open from 02 September 2025 to 30 September 2025, and applicants need to pay a fee of ₹100/- plus bank charges. This is a good opportunity for candidates with sports coaching qualifications to build their career in the Bihar Sports Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya Selection Test - 2026 Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/jnv-navodaya-admission-6th-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 11:04:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/jnv-navodaya-admission-6th-2026/</guid>
      <description>Apply for Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya Selection Test (JNVST) 2026 for Class 6 admission. Last date is 29 July 2025. Check eligibility, exam date, prospectus PDF &amp;amp; online application link.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar PCS 71st Mains Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-71th-exam-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:57:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-71th-exam-2025/</guid>
      <description>बिहार लोक सेवा आयोग (BPSC) ने 71वीं संयुक्त प्रतियोगिता परीक्षा (CCE) 2025 का नोटिफिकेशन जारी कर दिया है। यह परीक्षा विभिन्न प्रशासनिक पदों जैसे DSP, SDM, बीडीओ, राजस्व अधिकारी आदि के लिए आयोजित की जाती है। आवेदन प्रक्रिया ऑनलाइन मोड में होगी और सभी भारत के योग्य उम्मीदवार आवेदन कर सकते हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OICL Administrative Officer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/oicl-ao-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 12:15:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/oicl-ao-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Oriental Insurance Company Limited (OICL) has released the OICL AO Recruitment 2025 notification for 300 vacancies, including 285 Generalist and 15 Hindi Officer posts. Eligible candidates can apply online from 01/12/2025 to 15/12/2025. The selection process includes Prelims, Mains, and Interview. Candidates must check eligibility, age limit, and qualification before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police Sub Inspector SI Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-si-admitcard-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 12:13:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-si-admitcard-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Police Recruitment and Promotion Board (UPPRPB) has announced the UP Police Sub Inspector (SI) Recruitment 2025. The online application process will be open from 12 August 2025 to 11 September 2025, and fee adjustments for submitted payments can be made until 13 September 2025. The application fee is ₹500/- for General, EWS, and OBC candidates, while SC and ST candidates will have to pay ₹400/-. The recruitment is for posts in Uttar Pradesh, and applications must be submitted online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Patwari Bharti 2025 Result Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-patwari-bharti-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 12:06:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-patwari-bharti-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSMSSB) has released the notification for Patwari Bharti 2025. A total of 3705 vacancies are available, including 522 posts for TSP areas and 3183 posts for Non-TSP areas. Candidates must have a Bachelor’s Degree and a recognized Computer qualification such as NIELIT O Level, COPA, RS-CIT, or a Diploma/Degree in Computer Science/Application.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPPB Executive Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ippb-gds-executive-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 12:02:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ippb-gds-executive-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>India Post Payments Bank (IPPB) has released the Executive Recruitment 2025 notification for 348 vacancies on engagement from existing Gramin Dak Sevaks (GDS) of the Department of Posts. Eligible GDS employees having a Graduate degree in any discipline can apply online from 09/10/2025 to 29/10/2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ippbonline.com&#34;&gt;www.ippbonline.com&lt;/a&gt;. Selected candidates will receive a monthly salary of ₹30,000, and selection will be based on merit of graduation marks. The recruitment aims to strengthen IPPB’s doorstep banking network across India by engaging trained GDS executives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC ATP Assistant Town Planner Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-atp-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:29:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-atp-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has announced 35 vacancies for Assistant Town Planner (ATP) under Advertisement No. 89/2025 in the Urban Development &amp;amp; Housing Department. The online application process will be open from 28th August 2025 to 22nd September 2025 on the official BPSC website. Candidates with a Post Graduate degree in Town Planning, Regional/Urban Planning, City Planning, Country/Transport Planning, Housing, or Environmental Planning are eligible to apply. The selection will be based on a written examination and interview, and appointed candidates will receive a salary under Pay Level 09 (₹53,100 – ₹1,67,800) along with allowances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBPS Probationary Officer Mains Result 2025 Out – Download Now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-probationary-officer-po-15th-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:25:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-probationary-officer-po-15th-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Institute of Banking Personnel Selection (IBPS) has released the notification for CRP PO/MT-XV Recruitment 2025 for the post of Probationary Officer (PO)/Management Trainee (MT). A total of 5208 vacancies have been announced across 8 participating public sector banks. Candidates who hold a Bachelor’s Degree in any discipline from a recognized university in India are eligible to apply. The recruitment process includes a preliminary exam, main exam, and interview. Applications must be submitted online through the official IBPS website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibps.in&#34;&gt;www.ibps.in&lt;/a&gt;. Selected candidates will be appointed across various locations in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC Deputy Director &amp; Principal Grade-II Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/mppsc-principal-grade-2-recruitment-nov25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 12:41:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/mppsc-principal-grade-2-recruitment-nov25/</guid>
      <description>The MPPSC Technical Recruitment 2025 invites applications for the posts of Deputy Director, Principal Grade-II, and Assistant Director (Technical). Candidates with an engineering degree and the required professional experience can apply online from 01 December to 31 December 2025. The recruitment includes a correction window from 09 December 2025 to 02 January 2026. Applicants will be selected through a written examination followed by document verification. Interested candidates should carefully read the official notification before submitting the online form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Gram Panchayat Sachiv Online Form 2025-26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/mp-panchayat-sachiv-recruitment-nov25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:49:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/mp-panchayat-sachiv-recruitment-nov25/</guid>
      <description>MP Gram Panchayat Sachiv Bharti 2026 के तहत मध्यप्रदेश में कुल 23,011 ग्राम पंचायत सचिव पदों पर भर्ती प्रस्तावित है। योग्यता के लिए Graduation + Computer Diploma (DCA/PGDCA) और आयु 21 से 35 वर्ष निर्धारित की जा सकती है। चयन प्रक्रिया MPESB की लिखित परीक्षा, मेरिट सूची और दस्तावेज सत्यापन के आधार पर होगी। नियुक्ति जिला पंचायत द्वारा की जाएगी और वेतनमान प्रशिक्षण अवधि में ₹10,000 से शुरू होकर नियमित सेवा में ₹19,500–₹52,000 प्रति माह तक रहेगा। आवेदन और परीक्षा की तिथि आधिकारिक नोटिफिकेशन जारी होने के बाद अपडेट की जाएगी।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Panchayati Raj Block Project Manager Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-panchayati-raj-bpm-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 15:51:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-panchayati-raj-bpm-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Panchayati Raj Department has released the notification for 826 Block Project Manager (BPM) posts under the RGSA scheme. Eligible graduates with 60% marks and valid computer certificates can apply online from 01/12/2025 to 15/12/2025. No written exam will be conducted; selection will be based on merit, qualifications, and verification. Candidates are advised to read the official notification for detailed eligibility and instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBI Officer Grade B Phase II Admit Card  2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officer-grade-b-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 14:03:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officer-grade-b-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has announced 120 vacancies for Grade B Officers in General, DEPR, and DSIM streams. The application window will remain open from 10 September to 30 September 2025. Phase I examination is scheduled on 18–19 October 2025, while Phase II will be held on 6–7 December 2025. Candidates must carefully read the official notification for detailed eligibility criteria, qualifications, age limit, and application fees before applying online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Computer Assistant Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-computer-assistant-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 18:07:48 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-computer-assistant-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Public Service Commission (UPPSC) has released a notification for the recruitment of Computer Assistant posts in 2025. A total of 13 vacancies have been announced for eligible male and female candidates across India. To apply, candidates must have passed 10+2 (Intermediate) along with either a valid “O” Level certificate from NIELIT or a Diploma in Computer Science. The minimum age required is 18 years, and selected candidates will receive an initial salary in the ₹25,500 – ₹81,100 pay scale (Level-4). The application process is online only and will be available soon on the official website uppsc.up.nic.in. Interested candidates are advised to regularly check the website for the release of the online form and notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB NTPC Inter Level Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-inter-level-recruitment-sep-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:13:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-inter-level-recruitment-sep-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has released the notification for RRB NTPC Inter Level Recruitment 2025 (CEN 07/2025) with 3050 vacancies under the 10+2 (Undergraduate) category. Eligible candidates who have passed Intermediate (Class 12th) can apply online for posts like Junior Clerk cum Typist, Accounts Clerk cum Typist, Train Clerk, and Commercial cum Ticket Clerk. The application process will start from 28 October 2025 and continue till 27 November 2025. The selection process includes CBT-1, CBT-2, Typing Skill Test (for Clerk/Typist posts), Document Verification, and Medical Examination. The pay scale ranges from ₹19,900 to ₹21,700 (Level-2 &amp;amp; Level-3 as per 7th CPC) with additional allowances. Candidates are advised to check the official notification for complete eligibility, age limit, application fees, and exam details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MHA Intelligence Bureau ACIO Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mha-intelligence-bureau-acio-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:56:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mha-intelligence-bureau-acio-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau (IB), under the Ministry of Home Affairs (MHA), has announced the recruitment of 3717 posts for Assistant Central Intelligence Officer (ACIO) Grade-II / Executive. This is a Group &amp;lsquo;C&amp;rsquo;, Non-Gazetted, and Non-Ministerial post offering candidates a prestigious opportunity to work with India’s internal intelligence agency. Applicants must possess a Bachelor’s Degree in any stream from a recognized university in India. The selection process involves a written examination followed by an interview. Eligible candidates can apply online through the official MHA website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMD Project Scientist Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/imd-project-scientist-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:17:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/imd-project-scientist-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>India Meteorological Department (IMD) has released Advertisement No. 02/2025 for the recruitment of 134 Project Staff posts on a contractual basis under the Mission Mausam Scheme. The vacancies include Project Scientist (E, III, II, I), Scientific Assistant, and Admin Assistant. Eligible M.Sc. and B.Tech candidates from relevant fields can apply online from 24/11/2025 to 14/12/2025. No application fee is mentioned in the notification. The engagement will initially be for one year and may be extended based on performance up to 31 March 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC NR Apprentice Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-nr-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:32:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-nr-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Northern Railway has released the Act Apprentice Recruitment 2025 for 4116 posts across multiple clusters. Eligible candidates with 10th pass and ITI (NCVT/SCVT) can apply online. The selection will be based on a merit list prepared from 10th and ITI marks. The application process begins from 25 November 2025 and continues till 24 December 2025. No written exam or interview will be conducted. Interested candidates must check the eligibility, age limit, application fees, and required documents before submitting the online form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSPCB JSO &amp; JEE Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan/rspcb-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:16:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan/rspcb-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>RSPCB has announced 100 vacancies for Junior Scientific Officer and Junior Environmental Engineer. Candidates can apply online from 26 November to 16 December 2025. The notification includes eligibility criteria, age limits, application fees and detailed instructions for uploading documents and completing the online form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOI Specialist Officer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/boi-so-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:09:02 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/boi-so-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bank of India has released the Specialist Officer Recruitment 2025 for a total of 115 vacancies in Scale II III and IV. Eligible candidates can apply online from 17/11/2025 to 30/11/2025. The recruitment includes various posts in IT Risk Finance Law Engineering Fintech Data Science and Security fields. Selection will be based on an online test and/or interview. Interested applicants must check the required qualification age limit and fees before submitting the form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIR CDRI Technical Assistant &amp; Technician Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csir-cdri-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:12:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csir-cdri-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>CSIR CDRI has released Advt. No. 10/2025 for the recruitment of 44 posts including Technical Assistant and Technician (1). Online applications will be accepted from 25/11/2025 to 26/12/2025. Candidates across India are eligible to apply. Required qualifications include B.Sc./Diploma for Technical Assistant and 10th + ITI for Technician. The selection process consists of a written examination followed by a skill test as per the post requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adhar Card Dwonload- and Address Update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/aadhaar-card-download-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 10:27:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/aadhaar-card-download-online/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;yp-table-wrapper&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;table border=&#34;1&#34; cellpadding=&#34;8&#34; cellspacing=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;caption&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aadhaar Card – Important Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/caption&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;th&gt;Details&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;th&gt;Description&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Document Name&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Aadhaar Card&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Issuing Authority&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;UIDAI (Unique Identification Authority of India)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Aadhaar Number&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;12-digit unique identity number&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Type of ID&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Proof of Identity and Proof of Address&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Used For&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Bank account, SIM card, government schemes, pension, scholarship, subsidy, KYC, etc.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Eligibility&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Any resident of India, including children&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Required Documents&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Proof of Identity, Proof of Address, Date of Birth document (as per UIDAI list)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;How to Enrol&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Visit nearest Aadhaar Enrolment/Update Centre with required documents and biometrics&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Download Aadhaar&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;From UIDAI website or mAadhaar app using Aadhaar Number / Enrolment ID and OTP&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;PDF Password Format&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;First 4 letters of name in CAPITAL + Year of Birth (e.g., VIKR2001)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Update Options&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Name, Address, Date of Birth, Mobile Number, Email, Photo, Biometrics (as per UIDAI rules)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Update Charges&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;₹50 for demographic update, ₹100 for biometric update (may change as per UIDAI)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Official Website&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;https://uidai.gov.in and https://myaadhaar.uidai.gov.in&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Important Note&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Aadhaar is an identity proof, not proof of citizenship.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;yp-table-wrapper&#34;&gt; &lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police CO Recruitment 2024 - Syllabus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-computer-operator-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:13:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/up/up-police-computer-operator-2024/</guid>
      <description>UP Police invited online applications for the recruitment of Programmer Grade-2 and Computer Operator Grade-A from 07/01/2024 to 28/01/2024. The last date for fee payment was 31/01/2024, and the correction window was open from 01/02/2024 to 02/02/2024. The written examination is scheduled for 01/11/2025, and the admit card will be available three days before the exam. Eligible candidates—12th PCM passed with O Level or a related Diploma—can apply through the official UPPBPB website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar STET Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/bihar-stet-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:44:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/bihar-stet-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar School Examination Board (BSEB) will release the BSTET / STET 2025 Answer Key soon on the official website. The exam was held on 14 October 2025, and the application process closed on 05 October 2025. Candidates can check their Answer Key by logging in with their Enrollment Number, Registration Number, or Date of Birth. A direct link to download the Answer Key is available below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer - GajabJobs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:30:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;style&gt;&#xA;    :root {&#xA;      --primary: #2563eb;&#xA;      --primary-soft: #dbeafe;&#xA;      --bg: #f3f4f6;&#xA;      --card-bg: #ffffff;&#xA;      --text: #111827;&#xA;      --muted: #6b7280;&#xA;      --border: #e5e7eb;&#xA;      --radius-xl: 16px;&#xA;      --shadow-soft: 0 14px 30px rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.10);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    * { box-sizing: border-box; }&#xA;&#xA;    body {&#xA;      margin: 0;&#xA;      font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &#34;Segoe UI&#34;, sans-serif;&#xA;      background: radial-gradient(circle at top, #e0f2fe 0, #f9fafb 45%, #eef2ff 100%);&#xA;      color: var(--text);&#xA;      padding: 24px 12px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .page { max-width: 960px; margin: 0 auto; }&#xA;    .header { text-align: center; margin-bottom: 24px; }&#xA;&#xA;    .badge {&#xA;      display: inline-flex;&#xA;      align-items: center;&#xA;      gap: 6px;&#xA;      padding: 4px 10px;&#xA;      border-radius: 999px;&#xA;      background: rgba(37, 99, 235, 0.08);&#xA;      color: #1d4ed8;&#xA;      font-size: 12px;&#xA;      font-weight: 600;&#xA;      text-transform: uppercase;&#xA;      letter-spacing: 0.06em;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .title {&#xA;      font-size: clamp(26px, 4vw, 32px);&#xA;      margin: 10px 0 6px;&#xA;      font-weight: 700;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .subtitle {&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;      max-width: 640px;&#xA;      margin: 0 auto;&#xA;      line-height: 1.6;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .tag { font-size: 12px; color: var(--muted); margin-top: 4px; }&#xA;&#xA;    .card {&#xA;      background: var(--card-bg);&#xA;      border-radius: var(--radius-xl);&#xA;      padding: 22px 20px;&#xA;      margin-top: 26px;&#xA;      border: 1px solid rgba(148,163,184,0.20);&#xA;      box-shadow: var(--shadow-soft);&#xA;      position: relative;&#xA;      overflow: hidden;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .card::before {&#xA;      content: &#34;&#34;;&#xA;      position: absolute;&#xA;      inset: 0;&#xA;      background:&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 0 0, rgba(59,130,246,0.12), transparent 55%),&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 100% 100%, rgba(129,140,248,0.15), transparent 60%);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .card-inner { position: relative; z-index: 1; }&#xA;&#xA;    h2 { margin-top: 18px; margin-bottom: 6px; font-size: 18px; }&#xA;    p, ul { font-size: 14px; line-height: 1.7; color: var(--muted); margin-bottom: 10px; }&#xA;    ul { padding-left: 18px; }&#xA;&#xA;    .highlight {&#xA;      background: #fef3c7;&#xA;      border: 1px solid #fbbf24;&#xA;      padding: 12px;&#xA;      border-radius: 12px;&#xA;      margin-top: 18px;&#xA;      color: #92400e;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    a { color: var(--primary); text-decoration: none; }&#xA;    a:hover { text-decoration: underline; }&#xA;&#xA;    .small-footer {&#xA;      text-align: center;&#xA;      margin-top: 20px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      font-size: 12px;&#xA;    }&#xA;  &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;page&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;header class=&#34;header&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;badge&#34;&gt;⚠️ Disclaimer&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h1 class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p class=&#34;subtitle&#34;&gt;&#xA;      This Disclaimer explains the limitations of responsibility regarding the information published on GajabJobs.com.&#xA;    &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMCA &amp; Copyright - GajabJobs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dmca-copyright/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:30:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dmca-copyright/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;style&gt;&#xA;    :root {&#xA;      --primary: #2563eb;&#xA;      --primary-soft: #dbeafe;&#xA;      --bg: #f3f4f6;&#xA;      --card-bg: #ffffff;&#xA;      --text: #111827;&#xA;      --muted: #6b7280;&#xA;      --border: #e5e7eb;&#xA;      --radius-xl: 16px;&#xA;      --shadow-soft: 0 14px 30px rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.10);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    * { box-sizing: border-box; }&#xA;&#xA;    body {&#xA;      margin: 0;&#xA;      font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &#34;Segoe UI&#34;, sans-serif;&#xA;      background: radial-gradient(circle at top, #e0f2fe 0, #f9fafb 45%, #eef2ff 100%);&#xA;      color: var(--text);&#xA;      padding: 24px 12px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .page { max-width: 960px; margin: 0 auto; }&#xA;    .header { text-align: center; margin-bottom: 24px; }&#xA;&#xA;    .badge {&#xA;      display: inline-flex;&#xA;      align-items: center;&#xA;      gap: 6px;&#xA;      padding: 4px 10px;&#xA;      border-radius: 999px;&#xA;      background: rgba(37, 99, 235, 0.08);&#xA;      color: #1d4ed8;&#xA;      font-size: 12px;&#xA;      font-weight: 600;&#xA;      text-transform: uppercase;&#xA;      letter-spacing: 0.06em;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .title {&#xA;      font-size: clamp(26px, 4vw, 32px);&#xA;      margin: 10px 0 6px;&#xA;      font-weight: 700;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .subtitle {&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;      max-width: 640px;&#xA;      margin: 0 auto;&#xA;      line-height: 1.6;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .tag { font-size: 12px; color: var(--muted); margin-top: 4px; }&#xA;&#xA;    .card {&#xA;      background: var(--card-bg);&#xA;      border-radius: var(--radius-xl);&#xA;      padding: 22px 20px;&#xA;      margin-top: 26px;&#xA;      border: 1px solid rgba(148,163,184,0.20);&#xA;      box-shadow: var(--shadow-soft);&#xA;      position: relative;&#xA;      overflow: hidden;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .card::before {&#xA;      content: &#34;&#34;;&#xA;      position: absolute;&#xA;      inset: 0;&#xA;      background:&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 0 0, rgba(59,130,246,0.12), transparent 55%),&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 100% 100%, rgba(129,140,248,0.15), transparent 60%);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .card-inner { position: relative; z-index: 1; }&#xA;&#xA;    h2 { margin-top: 18px; margin-bottom: 6px; font-size: 18px; }&#xA;    p, ul { font-size: 14px; line-height: 1.7; color: var(--muted); margin-bottom: 10px; }&#xA;    ul { padding-left: 18px; }&#xA;&#xA;    .highlight {&#xA;      background: #eff6ff;&#xA;      border: 1px solid #bfdbfe;&#xA;      padding: 12px;&#xA;      border-radius: 12px;&#xA;      margin-top: 18px;&#xA;      color: #1e40af;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    a { color: var(--primary); text-decoration: none; }&#xA;    a:hover { text-decoration: underline; }&#xA;&#xA;    .small-footer {&#xA;      text-align: center;&#xA;      margin-top: 20px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      font-size: 12px;&#xA;    }&#xA;  &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;page&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;header class=&#34;header&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;badge&#34;&gt;📄 DMCA &amp; Copyright&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h1 class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;DMCA &amp; Copyright Policy&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p class=&#34;subtitle&#34;&gt;&#xA;      This page explains how we handle copyright issues and DMCA takedown requests on GajabJobs.com.&#xA;    &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy – GajabJobs.com</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:30:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;style&gt;&#xA;    :root {&#xA;      --primary: #2563eb;&#xA;      --primary-soft: #dbeafe;&#xA;      --bg: #f3f4f6;&#xA;      --card-bg: #ffffff;&#xA;      --text: #111827;&#xA;      --muted: #6b7280;&#xA;      --border: #e5e7eb;&#xA;      --radius-xl: 16px;&#xA;      --shadow-soft: 0 14px 30px rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.10);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    * {&#xA;      box-sizing: border-box;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    body {&#xA;      margin: 0;&#xA;      font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &#34;Segoe UI&#34;, sans-serif;&#xA;      background: radial-gradient(circle at top, #e0f2fe 0, #f9fafb 45%, #eef2ff 100%);&#xA;      color: var(--text);&#xA;      padding: 24px 12px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .page {&#xA;      max-width: 960px;&#xA;      margin: 0 auto;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .header {&#xA;      text-align: center;&#xA;      margin-bottom: 24px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .badge {&#xA;      display: inline-flex;&#xA;      align-items: center;&#xA;      gap: 6px;&#xA;      padding: 4px 10px;&#xA;      border-radius: 999px;&#xA;      background: rgba(37, 99, 235, 0.08);&#xA;      color: #1d4ed8;&#xA;      font-size: 12px;&#xA;      font-weight: 600;&#xA;      text-transform: uppercase;&#xA;      letter-spacing: 0.06em;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .title {&#xA;      font-size: clamp(26px, 4vw, 32px);&#xA;      margin: 10px 0 6px;&#xA;      font-weight: 700;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .subtitle {&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;      max-width: 640px;&#xA;      margin: 0 auto;&#xA;      line-height: 1.6;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .card {&#xA;      background: var(--card-bg);&#xA;      border-radius: var(--radius-xl);&#xA;      padding: 20px 18px;&#xA;      box-shadow: var(--shadow-soft);&#xA;      border: 1px solid rgba(148, 163, 184, 0.20);&#xA;      margin-top: 26px;&#xA;      position: relative;&#xA;      overflow: hidden;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .card::before {&#xA;      content: &#34;&#34;;&#xA;      position: absolute;&#xA;      inset: 0;&#xA;      background:&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 0 0, rgba(59, 130, 246, 0.12), transparent 55%),&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 100% 100%, rgba(129, 140, 248, 0.15), transparent 60%);&#xA;      pointer-events: none;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .card-inner {&#xA;      position: relative;&#xA;      z-index: 1;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    h2 {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 10px;&#xA;      font-size: 18px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    h3 {&#xA;      margin: 18px 0 6px;&#xA;      font-size: 16px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    p {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 10px;&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      line-height: 1.7;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    ul {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 10px;&#xA;      padding-left: 18px;&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      line-height: 1.6;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    ul li + li {&#xA;      margin-top: 4px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .tag {&#xA;      font-size: 12px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      margin-top: 4px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .highlight-box {&#xA;      margin-top: 14px;&#xA;      padding: 10px 12px;&#xA;      border-radius: 12px;&#xA;      background: #eff6ff;&#xA;      border: 1px solid #bfdbfe;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;      color: #1e40af;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .small-footer {&#xA;      margin-top: 18px;&#xA;      text-align: center;&#xA;      font-size: 11px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    a {&#xA;      color: var(--primary);&#xA;      text-decoration: none;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    a:hover {&#xA;      text-decoration: underline;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .section-spacer {&#xA;      margin-top: 18px;&#xA;    }&#xA;  &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;page&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;!-- Header --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;header class=&#34;header&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;badge&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;span&gt;🔒 Privacy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;      &lt;span&gt;GajabJobs.com&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h1 class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p class=&#34;subtitle&#34;&gt;&#xA;      This Privacy Policy explains how GajabJobs.com collects, uses, and protects your information when you visit our website.&#xA;    &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terms &amp; Conditions - GajabJobs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:30:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/terms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;title&gt;Terms &amp; Conditions - GajabJobs&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;style&gt;&#xA;    :root {&#xA;      --primary: #2563eb;&#xA;      --primary-soft: #dbeafe;&#xA;      --bg: #f3f4f6;&#xA;      --card-bg: #ffffff;&#xA;      --text: #111827;&#xA;      --muted: #6b7280;&#xA;      --border: #e5e7eb;&#xA;      --radius-xl: 16px;&#xA;      --shadow-soft: 0 14px 30px rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.10);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    * { box-sizing: border-box; }&#xA;&#xA;    body {&#xA;      margin: 0;&#xA;      font-family: system-ui, sans-serif;&#xA;      background: radial-gradient(circle at top, #e0f2fe 0, #f9fafb 45%, #eef2ff 100%);&#xA;      color: var(--text);&#xA;      padding: 24px 12px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .page { max-width: 960px; margin: 0 auto; }&#xA;    .header { text-align: center; margin-bottom: 24px; }&#xA;&#xA;    .badge {&#xA;      display: inline-flex;&#xA;      align-items: center;&#xA;      gap: 6px;&#xA;      padding: 4px 10px;&#xA;      border-radius: 999px;&#xA;      background: rgba(37, 99, 235, 0.08);&#xA;      color: #1d4ed8;&#xA;      font-size: 12px;&#xA;      font-weight: 600;&#xA;      text-transform: uppercase;&#xA;      letter-spacing: 0.06em;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .title {&#xA;      font-size: clamp(26px, 4vw, 32px);&#xA;      margin: 10px 0 6px;&#xA;      font-weight: 700;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .subtitle {&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;      max-width: 640px;&#xA;      margin: 0 auto;&#xA;      line-height: 1.6;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .card {&#xA;      background: var(--card-bg);&#xA;      border-radius: var(--radius-xl);&#xA;      padding: 22px 20px;&#xA;      margin-top: 26px;&#xA;      border: 1px solid rgba(148,163,184,0.20);&#xA;      box-shadow: var(--shadow-soft);&#xA;      position: relative;&#xA;      overflow: hidden;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .card::before {&#xA;      content: &#34;&#34;;&#xA;      position: absolute;&#xA;      inset: 0;&#xA;      background:&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 0 0, rgba(59,130,246,0.12), transparent 55%),&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 100% 100%, rgba(129,140,248,0.15), transparent 60%);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .card-inner { position: relative; z-index: 1; }&#xA;&#xA;    h2 { margin-top: 18px; margin-bottom: 6px; font-size: 18px; }&#xA;    p, ul { font-size: 14px; line-height: 1.7; color: var(--muted); margin-bottom: 10px; }&#xA;    ul { padding-left: 18px; }&#xA;&#xA;    .highlight {&#xA;      background: #eff6ff;&#xA;      border: 1px solid #bfdbfe;&#xA;      padding: 12px;&#xA;      border-radius: 12px;&#xA;      margin-top: 16px;&#xA;      color: #1e3a8a;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .tag { font-size: 12px; color: var(--muted); }&#xA;    .small-footer { text-align: center; margin-top: 20px; color: var(--muted); font-size: 12px; }&#xA;  &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;page&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;header class=&#34;header&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;badge&#34;&gt;📘 Terms &amp; Conditions&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h1 class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;Terms &amp; Conditions&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p class=&#34;subtitle&#34;&gt;Read these terms carefully before using GajabJobs.com&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us - GajabJobs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:24:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;title&gt;About Us - GajabJobs&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;style&gt;&#xA;    :root {&#xA;      --primary: #2563eb;&#xA;      --primary-soft: #dbeafe;&#xA;      --bg: #f3f4f6;&#xA;      --card-bg: #ffffff;&#xA;      --text: #111827;&#xA;      --muted: #6b7280;&#xA;      --border: #e5e7eb;&#xA;      --radius-xl: 16px;&#xA;      --shadow-soft: 0 14px 30px rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.10);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    * {&#xA;      box-sizing: border-box;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    body {&#xA;      margin: 0;&#xA;      font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &#34;Segoe UI&#34;, sans-serif;&#xA;      background: radial-gradient(circle at top, #e0f2fe 0, #f9fafb 45%, #eef2ff 100%);&#xA;      color: var(--text);&#xA;      padding: 24px 12px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-page {&#xA;      max-width: 960px;&#xA;      margin: 0 auto;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-header {&#xA;      text-align: center;&#xA;      margin-bottom: 24px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-badge {&#xA;      display: inline-flex;&#xA;      align-items: center;&#xA;      gap: 6px;&#xA;      padding: 4px 10px;&#xA;      border-radius: 999px;&#xA;      background: rgba(37, 99, 235, 0.08);&#xA;      color: #1d4ed8;&#xA;      font-size: 12px;&#xA;      font-weight: 600;&#xA;      text-transform: uppercase;&#xA;      letter-spacing: 0.06em;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-title {&#xA;      font-size: clamp(26px, 4vw, 32px);&#xA;      margin: 10px 0 6px;&#xA;      font-weight: 700;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-subtitle {&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;      max-width: 640px;&#xA;      margin: 0 auto;&#xA;      line-height: 1.6;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-main-card {&#xA;      background: var(--card-bg);&#xA;      border-radius: var(--radius-xl);&#xA;      padding: 20px 18px;&#xA;      box-shadow: var(--shadow-soft);&#xA;      border: 1px solid rgba(148, 163, 184, 0.20);&#xA;      margin-top: 26px;&#xA;      position: relative;&#xA;      overflow: hidden;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-main-card::before {&#xA;      content: &#34;&#34;;&#xA;      position: absolute;&#xA;      inset: 0;&#xA;      background:&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 0 0, rgba(59, 130, 246, 0.12), transparent 55%),&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 100% 100%, rgba(129, 140, 248, 0.15), transparent 60%);&#xA;      pointer-events: none;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-main-inner {&#xA;      position: relative;&#xA;      z-index: 1;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-main-inner h2 {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 10px;&#xA;      font-size: 20px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-main-inner p {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 10px;&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      line-height: 1.7;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-highlight {&#xA;      display: inline-flex;&#xA;      flex-wrap: wrap;&#xA;      gap: 8px;&#xA;      margin-top: 10px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-pill {&#xA;      padding: 5px 10px;&#xA;      border-radius: 999px;&#xA;      background: #eff6ff;&#xA;      border: 1px solid #bfdbfe;&#xA;      font-size: 12px;&#xA;      color: #1d4ed8;&#xA;      display: inline-flex;&#xA;      align-items: center;&#xA;      gap: 6px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-pill span {&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-grid {&#xA;      display: grid;&#xA;      grid-template-columns: repeat(3, minmax(0, 1fr));&#xA;      gap: 16px;&#xA;      margin-top: 24px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    @media (max-width: 880px) {&#xA;      .about-grid {&#xA;        grid-template-columns: repeat(2, minmax(0, 1fr));&#xA;      }&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    @media (max-width: 640px) {&#xA;      .about-grid {&#xA;        grid-template-columns: 1fr;&#xA;      }&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-card {&#xA;      background: #f9fafb;&#xA;      border-radius: 14px;&#xA;      padding: 14px 12px;&#xA;      border: 1px solid var(--border);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-card h3 {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 6px;&#xA;      font-size: 15px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-card p {&#xA;      margin: 0;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      line-height: 1.6;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-list {&#xA;      margin: 8px 0 0;&#xA;      padding-left: 18px;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      line-height: 1.5;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-list li + li {&#xA;      margin-top: 4px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .two-column {&#xA;      display: grid;&#xA;      grid-template-columns: minmax(0, 1.4fr) minmax(0, 1.1fr);&#xA;      gap: 18px;&#xA;      margin-top: 24px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    @media (max-width: 768px) {&#xA;      .two-column {&#xA;        grid-template-columns: 1fr;&#xA;      }&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-block {&#xA;      background: #ffffff;&#xA;      border-radius: 14px;&#xA;      border: 1px solid var(--border);&#xA;      padding: 14px 12px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-block h3 {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 6px;&#xA;      font-size: 15px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-block p {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 8px;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      line-height: 1.6;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-bullets {&#xA;      margin: 0;&#xA;      padding-left: 16px;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .about-bullets li + li {&#xA;      margin-top: 4px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .disclaimer-box {&#xA;      margin-top: 20px;&#xA;      padding: 12px 12px;&#xA;      border-radius: 12px;&#xA;      background: #fef3c7;&#xA;      border: 1px solid #fbbf24;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;      color: #92400e;&#xA;      line-height: 1.6;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .small-footer {&#xA;      margin-top: 18px;&#xA;      text-align: center;&#xA;      font-size: 11px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;    }&#xA;  &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;about-page&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;!-- Header --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;header class=&#34;about-header&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;about-badge&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;span&gt;ℹ️ About&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;      &lt;span&gt;GajabJobs.com&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h1 class=&#34;about-title&#34;&gt;About Us&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p class=&#34;about-subtitle&#34;&gt;&#xA;      GajabJobs.com is a government job and educational information portal where we provide&#xA;      reliable, fast, and well-structured updates on government job notifications, admit cards,&#xA;      results, scholarships, schemes, and exam-related details.&#xA;    &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us – GajabJobs.com</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:02:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;style&gt;&#xA;    :root {&#xA;      --primary: #2563eb;&#xA;      --primary-soft: #dbeafe;&#xA;      --bg: #f3f4f6;&#xA;      --card-bg: #ffffff;&#xA;      --text: #111827;&#xA;      --muted: #6b7280;&#xA;      --border: #e5e7eb;&#xA;      --radius-xl: 16px;&#xA;      --shadow-soft: 0 10px 25px rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.08);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    * {&#xA;      box-sizing: border-box;&#xA;    }&#xA;    .contact-page {&#xA;      max-width: 960px;&#xA;      margin: 0 auto;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-header {&#xA;      text-align: center;&#xA;      margin-bottom: 24px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-badge {&#xA;      display: inline-flex;&#xA;      align-items: center;&#xA;      gap: 6px;&#xA;      padding: 4px 10px;&#xA;      border-radius: 999px;&#xA;      background: rgba(37, 99, 235, 0.08);&#xA;      color: #1d4ed8;&#xA;      font-size: 12px;&#xA;      font-weight: 600;&#xA;      text-transform: uppercase;&#xA;      letter-spacing: 0.06em;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-title {&#xA;      font-size: clamp(26px, 4vw, 32px);&#xA;      margin: 10px 0 6px;&#xA;      font-weight: 700;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-subtitle {&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;      max-width: 520px;&#xA;      margin: 0 auto;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-grid {&#xA;      display: grid;&#xA;      grid-template-columns: minmax(0, 2fr) minmax(0, 1.4fr);&#xA;      gap: 20px;&#xA;      margin-top: 26px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    @media (max-width: 768px) {&#xA;      .contact-grid {&#xA;        grid-template-columns: 1fr;&#xA;      }&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-card {&#xA;      background: var(--card-bg);&#xA;      border-radius: var(--radius-xl);&#xA;      padding: 20px 18px;&#xA;      box-shadow: var(--shadow-soft);&#xA;      border: 1px solid rgba(148, 163, 184, 0.18);&#xA;      position: relative;&#xA;      overflow: hidden;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-card::before {&#xA;      content: &#34;&#34;;&#xA;      position: absolute;&#xA;      inset: 0;&#xA;      background: radial-gradient(circle at top right, rgba(37, 99, 235, 0.08), transparent 55%);&#xA;      pointer-events: none;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-card h2 {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 10px;&#xA;      font-size: 18px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-card p {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 10px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;      line-height: 1.5;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-list {&#xA;      margin: 14px 0 0;&#xA;      padding: 0;&#xA;      list-style: none;&#xA;      display: grid;&#xA;      gap: 10px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-item {&#xA;      display: flex;&#xA;      align-items: center;&#xA;      gap: 10px;&#xA;      padding: 10px 10px;&#xA;      border-radius: 12px;&#xA;      background: #f9fafb;&#xA;      border: 1px solid var(--border);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-icon {&#xA;      width: 30px;&#xA;      height: 30px;&#xA;      border-radius: 999px;&#xA;      display: inline-flex;&#xA;      align-items: center;&#xA;      justify-content: center;&#xA;      background: var(--primary-soft);&#xA;      font-size: 16px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-label {&#xA;      font-size: 12px;&#xA;      text-transform: uppercase;&#xA;      letter-spacing: 0.08em;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-value a,&#xA;    .contact-value span {&#xA;      font-size: 14px;&#xA;      font-weight: 500;&#xA;      color: var(--text);&#xA;      word-break: break-all;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-value a {&#xA;      text-decoration: none;&#xA;      color: var(--primary);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .contact-value a:hover {&#xA;      text-decoration: underline;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .note-box {&#xA;      margin-top: 14px;&#xA;      padding: 10px 12px;&#xA;      border-radius: 12px;&#xA;      background: #eff6ff;&#xA;      border: 1px dashed #bfdbfe;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;      color: #1e40af;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .info-card {&#xA;      background: rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.98);&#xA;      color: #e5e7eb;&#xA;      border-radius: var(--radius-xl);&#xA;      padding: 18px 16px;&#xA;      border: 1px solid rgba(148, 163, 184, 0.35);&#xA;      position: relative;&#xA;      overflow: hidden;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .info-card::before {&#xA;      content: &#34;&#34;;&#xA;      position: absolute;&#xA;      inset: -40%;&#xA;      background:&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 20% 0%, rgba(59, 130, 246, 0.32), transparent 65%),&#xA;        radial-gradient(circle at 80% 100%, rgba(129, 140, 248, 0.28), transparent 60%);&#xA;      opacity: 0.9;&#xA;      pointer-events: none;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .info-inner {&#xA;      position: relative;&#xA;      z-index: 1;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .info-chip {&#xA;      display: inline-flex;&#xA;      align-items: center;&#xA;      gap: 6px;&#xA;      border-radius: 999px;&#xA;      padding: 3px 10px;&#xA;      font-size: 11px;&#xA;      text-transform: uppercase;&#xA;      letter-spacing: 0.08em;&#xA;      background: rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.7);&#xA;      border: 1px solid rgba(148, 163, 184, 0.5);&#xA;      margin-bottom: 10px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .info-card h3 {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 8px;&#xA;      font-size: 16px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .info-card p {&#xA;      margin: 0 0 10px;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;      line-height: 1.6;&#xA;      color: #e5e7eb;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .info-list {&#xA;      margin: 0;&#xA;      padding-left: 16px;&#xA;      font-size: 13px;&#xA;      color: #cbd5f5;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .info-list li + li {&#xA;      margin-top: 4px;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .highlight-tag {&#xA;      display: inline-flex;&#xA;      align-items: center;&#xA;      gap: 6px;&#xA;      margin-top: 8px;&#xA;      padding: 4px 8px;&#xA;      border-radius: 999px;&#xA;      font-size: 11px;&#xA;      background: rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.9);&#xA;      border: 1px solid rgba(129, 140, 248, 0.7);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    .small-footer {&#xA;      margin-top: 18px;&#xA;      text-align: center;&#xA;      font-size: 11px;&#xA;      color: var(--muted);&#xA;    }&#xA;  &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;contact-page&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;!-- Header --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;header class=&#34;contact-header&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;contact-badge&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;span&gt;📞 Contact&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;      &lt;span&gt;GajabJobs.com&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h1 class=&#34;contact-title&#34;&gt;Contact Us&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p class=&#34;contact-subtitle&#34;&gt;&#xA;      If you have any query related to government jobs, recruitment notifications, results, admit cards, syllabus or other updates,&#xA;      you can easily get in touch with us using the details below.&#xA;    &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONGC Apprentice Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/ongc-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:56:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/ongc-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Limited (ONGC) has released the official notification for Apprentice Recruitment 2025 under the Apprentices Act, 1961. A total of 2743 vacancies have been announced across India in various sectors such as Northern, Western, Eastern, Southern, Mumbai, and Central.Eligible candidates with ITI, Diploma, or Graduate qualifications can apply for trades like Fitter, Electrician, Computer Operator, Lab Chemist, Mechanical Executive, Accounts Executive, and others. The online application process began on 16/10/2025 and will continue till 06/11/2025 through the official ONGC Apprentice portal – ongcapprentices.ongc.co.in. Selection will be based on merit of qualifying exam marks, and no examination fee is required. Selected apprentices will receive a monthly stipend up to ₹12,300 during the 12-month training period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAI Graduate &amp; Diploma Apprenticeship Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/aai-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:39:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/aai-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Airports Authority of India (AAI) has announced the AAI Apprentice Recruitment 2025-26 for 20 posts of Graduate and Diploma Apprentices under the Apprentices Act, 1961 at RCDU/FIU/CRSD &amp;amp; E&amp;amp;M Workshop, Safdarjung Airport, New Delhi. Candidates who have completed their BE/B.Tech, BCA, B.Sc, B.Com, BA, BBA, or Diploma (Mechanical, Automobile, EEE, ECE, Instrumentation, Material Management) after 2021 are eligible to apply. The apprenticeship duration will be 1 year, with a monthly stipend of ₹15,000 for graduates and ₹12,000 for diploma holders. Selection will be based on merit and document verification, and applications can be submitted through the NATS portal (nats.education.gov.in) till 24 November 2025. Preference will be given to candidates from the Delhi/NCR region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NABARD Assistant Manager Grade A Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nabard-assistant-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 12:02:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nabard-assistant-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The National Bank for Agriculture and Rural Development (NABARD) has released the Grade A Assistant Manager Recruitment 2025 notification for 91 vacancies across various streams including Generalist, Agriculture, IT, Finance, Legal, and Protocol &amp;amp; Security Service. Eligible candidates can apply online from 08 November 2025 to 30 November 2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nabard.org&#34;&gt;www.nabard.org&lt;/a&gt;. Applicants must hold a relevant Bachelor’s or Master’s degree depending on the discipline. The selection process includes Preliminary, Main, and Interview rounds. NABARD offers an attractive salary of around ₹ 1 lakh/month (including allowances) and a prestigious career in rural development and agricultural banking. Candidates are advised to read the official notification carefully before applying online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPCIL Deputy Manager &amp; Jr. Hindi Translator Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/npcil-deputy-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 11:30:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/npcil-deputy-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Nuclear Power Corporation of India Limited (NPCIL) has released the NPCIL Recruitment 2025 notification for 122 vacancies including Deputy Manager (HR, F&amp;amp;A, C&amp;amp;MM, Legal) and Junior Hindi Translator (JHT). The online application process will be open from 07 November to 27 November 2025 at npcilcareers.co.in. Candidates with MBA, CA, CMA, CFA, LLB, or Postgraduate qualifications can apply online. The selection process includes an Online Test and Interview for Deputy Manager posts and a Preliminary plus Advanced Test for JHT. Selected candidates will receive a salary of up to ₹86,955 per month along with various allowances and benefits. Posting can be anywhere in India under the Department of Atomic Energy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPRPB One Time Registration 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/otr/upprpb-otr-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 10:08:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/otr/upprpb-otr-online/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Police Recruitment and Promotion Board (UPPRPB) has launched the One Time Registration (OTR) 2025 process for all aspiring candidates. This OTR is mandatory for those who wish to apply for any upcoming UP Police recruitment exams. By completing the OTR once, candidates will not need to repeatedly enter their details for each application. This system ensures a faster, more transparent, and convenient application process. Interested candidates can register online at uppbpb.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIDBI AM Grade A and B Phase II Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sidbi-assistant-manager-grade-a-b-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 12:18:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sidbi-assistant-manager-grade-a-b-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Small Industries Development Bank of India (SIDBI) has released the official notification for the recruitment of Assistant Manager Grade A (General) and Manager Grade B (General, Legal, IT) posts, with a total of 76 vacancies. This is a great opportunity for candidates holding a Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in fields like Commerce, Economics, Law, Engineering, Management, or related disciplines. A minimum of 5 years of relevant experience is required for all Grade B positions. The application process will be conducted online, and the postings will be pan-India. Interested candidates are advised to visit the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sidbi.in&#34;&gt;www.sidbi.in&lt;/a&gt; to check complete details and apply. For eligibility criteria, experience requirements, and selection procedure, please refer to the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPGCL Assistant &amp; Junior Engineer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppgcl-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 12:06:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mppgcl-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>Madhya Pradesh Power Generating Company Limited (MPPGCL) has released the Phase-II Recruitment 2025-26 notification for 131 posts of Assistant Engineer, Junior Engineer, Chemist, and Office Assistant. Eligible candidates can apply online from 17 October 2025 to 15 November 2025 through the MPOnline portal at &lt;a href=&#34;https://chayan.mponline.gov.in&#34;&gt;https://chayan.mponline.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;. Selection will be based on a Computer-Based Test (CBT) followed by document verification. Candidates must hold the prescribed qualifications (BE/B.Tech/Diploma/M.Sc/12th + Computer Diploma) as per post. This recruitment offers a great opportunity for technical and administrative aspirants in the MP Power sector under a government enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Clerk (Junior Associate) Pre Result 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-clerk-junior-associate-vacancy-aug-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 09:56:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-clerk-junior-associate-vacancy-aug-2025/</guid>
      <description>State Bank of India (SBI) has released the official notification for Junior Associate (Customer Support &amp;amp; Sales) recruitment under Advertisement No. CRPD/CR/2025-26/06. A total of 5583 vacancies have been announced, including 5180 regular and 403 backlog posts, to be filled across various states. The online application process will be open from 06 August to 26 August 2025. Candidates must hold a graduation degree in any discipline, with final year students also eligible to apply provisionally. The age limit is 20 to 28 years as on 01 April 2025, with age relaxation applicable as per government rules. The selection process includes an online Preliminary Exam, Main Exam, and a Local Language Proficiency Test (if applicable). The Preliminary exam is expected in September 2025, and the Main exam in November 2025. The starting basic salary is ₹26,730/-, with gross monthly emoluments of around ₹46,000/- in metro cities. The application fee is ₹750/- for General/OBC/EWS, while it is exempted for SC/ST/PwBD/Ex-servicemen. Selected candidates will be posted in the state/circle they apply for, and no inter-state transfer will be allowed. Interested candidates can apply online through the SBI official website: &lt;a href=&#34;https://sbi.co.in/web/careers&#34;&gt;https://sbi.co.in/web/careers&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBI Officers Grade A &amp; B Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officers-grade-a-and-b-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:28:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officers-grade-a-and-b-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has announced 28 vacancies for various Grade A and B Officer posts under the 2025 recruitment drive. The available posts include Law Officer, Manager (Technical – Civil and Electrical), Assistant Manager (Rajbhasha), and Assistant Manager (Protocol &amp;amp; Security). Candidates applying for these positions must meet the minimum educational qualifications such as LLB, BE/B.Tech, Master’s Degree, or have military experience, along with relevant work experience where required. This is a great opportunity for eligible candidates to join the RBI as an officer and contribute to the nation’s central banking system. Interested applicants can submit their applications through the official RBI website within the given deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IB ACIO-II/Tech Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-acio-technical-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:58:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-acio-technical-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau (IB), under the Ministry of Home Affairs, has released the official notification for IB ACIO-II/Technical Recruitment 2025. A total of 258 vacancies are available for disciplines in Computer Science &amp;amp; Information Technology and Electronics &amp;amp; Communication. Eligible candidates with valid GATE 2023, 2024, or 2025 scores can apply online from 25/10/2025 to 16/11/2025 through &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mha.gov.in&#34;&gt;www.mha.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;. The recruitment includes Level-7 pay scale (₹44,900–₹1,42,400), with additional security allowances and other benefits. Selection will be based on GATE score, Skill Test, and Interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRO SAC Group C Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobsisro-sac-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:52:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobsisro-sac-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>Space Applications Centre (SAC), Ahmedabad – Indian Space Research Organisation (ISRO) has released a recruitment notification for 55 vacancies of Technician ‘B’ and Pharmacist ‘A’ under Group ‘C’ posts. Eligible candidates can apply online through sac.gov.in from 24 October 2025 to 13 November 2025. The recruitment includes various trades such as Fitter, Machinist, Electrician, Electronics Mechanic, IT/ICTSM, Lab Assistant (Chemical Plant) and Refrigeration &amp;amp; Air Conditioning. The selection process consists of a Written Test followed by a Skill Test (qualifying nature). Salary: Level 3 (₹21,700–₹69,100) for Technician B and Level 5 (₹29,200–₹92,300) for Pharmacist A Age Limit: 18–35 years (as on 13/11/2025) Qualification: 10th Pass + ITI/NTC/NAC in relevant trade or Diploma in Pharmacy (First Class)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI SCO Wealth Management Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-sco-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:10:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-sco-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>State Bank of India (SBI) has released the official notification for Wealth Management Recruitment 2025 under the Specialist Cadre Officer (SCO) category. A total of 103 vacancies are available for posts like Head, Zonal Head, Regional Head, Relationship Manager, Investment Specialist, Investment Officer, and others. Eligible candidates can apply online from 27/10/2025 to 17/11/2025 through the official website sbi.bank.in/web/careers. The selection will be based on a personal interview only.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEBI Assistant Manager Grade A Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sebi-assistant-manager-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sebi-assistant-manager-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has released the SEBI Officer Grade A (Assistant Manager) Recruitment 2025 notification for 110 vacancies across various streams including General, Legal, IT, Research, Official Language, Civil, and Electrical Engineering. The online application process will be open from 30/10/2025 to 28/11/2025. The Phase-I exam is scheduled for 10/01/2026 and Phase-II for 21/02/2026. Candidates must possess a Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in relevant disciplines and be below 30 years of age as on 30/09/2025. The selection process consists of Phase-I, Phase-II, and Interview. The pay scale ranges from ₹62,500 to ₹1,26,100 with an approximate gross salary of ₹1.84 lakh per month (without accommodation). Eligible candidates can apply online through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sebi.gov.in&#34;&gt;www.sebi.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPHC Data Processing Assistant Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mphc-dpa-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:53:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mphc-dpa-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Madhya Pradesh High Court (MPHC) has announced the Data Processing Assistant (DPA) Recruitment 2025 under advertisement S2A/Exam/DPA/2025 for 41 vacancies. Eligible candidates with a BCA or B.Sc. (Computer Science/IT) degree and at least 60% marks, along with 3 years of data entry experience, can apply online from 29/10/2025 to 19/11/2025 through mphc.gov.in. The selection process includes a Preliminary Exam, Practical Test, and Interview, and the final merit will be based on Practical and Interview marks. The pay scale is ₹5200–20200 + Grade Pay ₹2400, and the application fees are ₹943.40 for UR and ₹743.40 for Reserved categories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHAI Various Posts Recruitment 2025 – Apply Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nhai-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:28:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nhai-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) has released a notification for direct recruitment 2025 under the Ministry of Road Transport &amp;amp; Highways. Eligible candidates can apply online for various posts including Deputy Manager (Finance &amp;amp; Accounts), Accountant, Stenographer, Library Assistant, and Junior Translation Officer. The application process starts from 30/10/2025 and continues till 15/12/2025. Candidates are advised to read the official notification carefully before applying at nhai.gov.in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC APO Recruitment 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-apo-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 11:32:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-apo-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Public Service Commission (UPPSC) has released the official notification for Assistant Prosecution Officer (APO) Recruitment 2025 with 182 vacancies. Eligible candidates with a Law degree (LLB) can apply online from 16 September 2025 to 16 October 2025 through the UPPSC portal. The selection process includes Prelims, Mains, and Interview, followed by document verification and medical examination. Applicants must be between 21 to 40 years of age as on 1 July 2025. The pay scale ranges from Rs. 47,600 to Rs. 1,51,100, offering a great career opportunity for law graduates in Uttar Pradesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan Police Constable Sports Quota Bharti 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan-police-constable-sports-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan-police-constable-sports-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Police has announced 167 Sports Quota Constable vacancies for 2025. Applications will be accepted online between 12th September and 1st October 2025. Selection will consider CET 2024 score, sports performance, and physical criteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us - Gajab Jobs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:49:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;title&gt;About Us - Gajab Jobs&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;About Gajab Jobs - Your trusted source for government jobs, yojana updates, and career opportunities.&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;style&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;    .container { max-width: 900px; margin: 40px auto; padding: 20px; background: #fff; border-radius: 10px; box-shadow: 0 2px 8px rgba(0,0,0,0.1);}&#xA;    h1 { color: #004aad; }&#xA;    h2 { margin-top: 30px; color: #222; }&#xA;    p { margin-bottom: 15px; }&#xA;    ul { margin: 15px 0; padding-left: 20px; }&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;header&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h1&gt;About Us&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/header&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h2&gt;Welcome to Gajab Jobs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;&#xA;      &lt;strong&gt;Gajab Jobs&lt;/strong&gt; is your trusted source for the latest government jobs, yojana updates, career opportunities, and educational resources.  &#xA;      We aim to provide accurate, timely, and easy-to-understand information to help students, job seekers, and individuals stay updated with important news and opportunities.&#xA;    &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us - Gajab Jobs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:49:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;style&gt;&#xA;&#xA;        .container {&#xA;            max-width: 800px;&#xA;            margin:  auto;&#xA;&#xA;            padding: 20px;&#xA;            background: #fff;&#xA;            border-radius: 8px;&#xA;            box-shadow: 0 2px 5px rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);&#xA;        }&#xA;        h1 {&#xA;            text-align: center;&#xA;            color: #0056b3;&#xA;        }&#xA;        p {&#xA;            font-size: 16px;&#xA;            line-height: 1.5;&#xA;        }&#xA;      &#xA;      #Message-container {&#xA;              margin:auto;&#xA;              max-width:500px; }&#xA;    &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;h1&gt;Contact Us&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;        &lt;p&gt;&#xA;            If you have any questions, feedback, or need support regarding Yojna Portal, feel free to contact us using the form below or reach us via email or phone.&#xA;        &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer - Gajab Jobs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:49:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;title&gt;Disclaimer - Gajab Jobs&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;Disclaimer of Gajab Jobs - Read our terms of responsibility regarding job notifications, yojana updates, and other information provided on this website.&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;style&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    .container { max-width: 900px; margin: 40px auto; padding: 20px; background: #fff; border-radius: 10px; box-shadow: 0 2px 8px rgba(0,0,0,0.1);}&#xA;  &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;header&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h1&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/header&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;&#xA;      The information provided on &lt;strong&gt;Gajab Jobs&lt;/strong&gt; (https://www.gajabjobs.com) is for general informational purposes only.  &#xA;      While we strive to provide accurate and up-to-date details regarding government jobs, yojanas, and career opportunities, we make no warranties of any kind about the completeness, reliability, or accuracy of the information.&#xA;    &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy - Gajab Jobs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:49:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;title&gt;Privacy Policy - Gajab Jobs&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;Privacy Policy of Gajab Jobs - Learn how we collect, use, and protect your personal information when you visit our website.&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;style&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    .container { max-width: 900px; margin: 40px auto; padding: 20px; background: #fff; border-radius: 10px; box-shadow: 0 2px 8px rgba(0,0,0,0.1);}&#xA;  &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;header&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h1&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/header&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;&#xA;      At &lt;strong&gt;Gajab Jobs&lt;/strong&gt; (https://www.gajabjobs.com), we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information.  &#xA;      This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and safeguard the data you share with us.&#xA;    &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Paramedical Post-wise Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobtable/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:13:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobtable/</guid>
      <description>&lt;style&gt;&#xA;.yp-table-wrapper {&#xA;  width: 100%;&#xA;  margin: 10px auto;&#xA;  overflow-x: auto;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.yp-table {&#xA;  width: 100%;&#xA;  border-collapse: collapse;&#xA;  font-family: Arial, sans-serif;&#xA;  background: #fff;&#xA;  box-shadow: 0 2px 8px rgba(0,0,0,0.1);&#xA;}&#xA;.yp-table td {&#xA;  border: 1px solid #ddd;&#xA;  padding: 15px;&#xA;  vertical-align: top;&#xA;}&#xA;.yp-table td {&#xA;  border: 1px solid #ddd;&#xA;  padding: 15px;&#xA;  vertical-align: top;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.yp-heading {&#xA;  text-align: center;&#xA;  font-size: 1rem;&#xA;  font-weight: bold;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.yp-table h3 {&#xA;  margin: 0 0 10px;&#xA;  font-size: 1rem;&#xA;  color: #007c11;&#xA;  display: inline-block;&#xA;  padding-bottom: 3px;&#xA;   font-size: 1rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.yp-table ul {&#xA;  margin: 0;&#xA;  padding-left: 20px;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.yp-table li {&#xA;  margin-bottom: 6px;&#xA;  line-height: 1.5;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;yp-table-wrapper&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td colspan=&#34;2&#34; class=&#34;yp-heading&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;span style=&#34;color: #ff00ff&#34;&gt;Chandigarh High Court (Punjab and Haryana High Court)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;       &lt;span style=&#34;color: #007c11&#34;&gt;  Punjab and Haryana at Chandigarh High Court Group D Recruitment 2025 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;        &lt;span style=&#34;color: #fc0606&#34;&gt; Detail of Short Notification&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;         &lt;span style=&#34;color: #000000&#34;&gt; www.gajabjobs.com&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;h3&gt;Important Date&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;        &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;Application Start Date : 28/07/2025&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;Application Last Date : 30/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;Correction Last Date : 02/09/2025&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;Exam Date Start : 27/09/2025&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;Admit Card Available : Before Exam&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;Exam Date : Notify soon&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;h3&gt;Application Fee&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;        &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;General / Unreserved Candidates: ₹500/-&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;SC/ST/OBC/EWS/PWD (MP Domicile): ₹250/-&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;MP Online Portal Fee (All Candidates): ₹60/-&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;₹20/- if using registered Citizen User.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;Pay fee through MP Online Kiosk or online mode.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td colspan=&#34;2&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #ff00ff&#34;&gt;Bihar BPSC AES Notification 2025 &lt;/span&gt;: &lt;span style=&#34;color: #007c11&#34;&gt; Age Limits As On 01 August 2025&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td colspan=&#34;2&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;        &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;As on 01/01/2025&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;Minimum Age: 18 years&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;Maximum Age: 40 years&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;For relaxation, read official notification &#34;MPESB Paramedical Vacancy 2025&#34;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;yp-table-wrapper&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;table border=&#34;1&#34; cellspacing=&#34;0&#34; cellpadding=&#34;8&#34; class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;     &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td colspan=&#34;3&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #ff00ff&#34; &gt;  BPSC AEDO Recruitment 2025 &lt;/span&gt; : &lt;span style=&#34;color: #007c11&#34;&gt; Total Post 2225 Vacancy Details  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;th&gt;Post Name&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;th&gt;Total Posts&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;th&gt;Qualification&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Physiotherapist&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;41&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        Bachelor&#39;s Degree in Physiotherapy (BPT)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;        Registration in MP Council of Medical Science&#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Counselor&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        Master&#39;s Degree in Social Work (MSW)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;        OR PG Diploma in Counseling and Family Therapy (PGDCFT)&#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Pharmacist Grade-II&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;313&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        10+2 with PCB stream (Physics, Chemistry, Biology)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;        Diploma or Degree in Pharmacy&lt;br&gt;&#xA;        Registration in MP Pharmacy Council&#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Ophthalmic Assistant&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;100&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        10+2 with PCB stream (Physics, Chemistry, Biology)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;        Diploma in Ophthalmic Assistant&lt;br&gt;&#xA;        Registration in Council&#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;O.T. Technician&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;288&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        10+2 with PCB stream (Physics, Chemistry, Biology)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;        1-year Diploma in O.T. Technician&lt;br&gt;&#xA;        Registration in MP Paramedical Council&#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td colspan=&#34;2&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #ff00ff&#34;&gt;Bihar BPSC AES Notification 2025 &lt;/span&gt;: &lt;span style=&#34;color: #007c11&#34;&gt; How To Apply&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;li&gt;Visit the Official Website: Go to the official BTSC website btsc.bihar.gov.in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Read the Official Notification: Carefully read the complete advertisement/notification for eligibility and instructions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Register as a New User: If you are a new user, click on &#34;New Registration&#34; and fill in the basic details to create your account.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Login to Your Account: Use your registered email/mobile number and password to log in.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fill the Application Form: Enter personal details, qualifications, and other required information.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Upload Documents: Upload scanned copies of your photograph, signature, and relevant documents.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pay the Application Fee: Pay the fee online via Debit Card / Credit Card / Net Banking / UPI.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Preview and Submit: Check all details carefully and submit the form.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Print the Final Application Form: After successful submission, download or print the final application form for your records.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td colspan=&#34;2&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #ff00ff&#34;&gt;Bihar BPSC AES Notification 2025 &lt;/span&gt;: &lt;span style=&#34;color: #007c11&#34;&gt; Some Useful Link&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th&gt;Important Links&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th&gt;Action&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Apply Online&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://esb.mponline.gov.in/Portal/Examinations/Vyapam/examsList.aspx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;  title=&#34;Go to Online Form&#39;s external page&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Online Form&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Dwonload Notification&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;          &#xA;         &lt;a href=&#34;https://esb.mp.gov.in/Rulebooks/RB_2025/Paramedical_Pharmasist_2025_RuleBook.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;  title=&#34;Go to Read Notice&#39;s external page&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Read Notice&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Profile Panjiyan&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;          &#xA;         &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yojnaportal.com/esb-profile&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;  title=&#34;Go to MPESB Profile&#39;s external page&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MPESB Profile&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Rojgar Panjiyan&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;          &#xA;         &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yojnaportal.com/mprojgar&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;  title=&#34;Go to MP Rojgar Panjiyan&#39;s external page&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MP Rojgar Panjiyan&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Follow Yojna Portal&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;          &#xA;         &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/telegram/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;  title=&#34;Go to Telegram&#39;s external page&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Telegram&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;           | &#xA;         &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/whatsapp/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;  title=&#34;Go to WhatsApp&#39;s external page&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;WhatsApp&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;           | &#xA;         &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/instagram/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;  title=&#34;Go to Instagram&#39;s external page&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Official Website&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;          &#xA;         &lt;a href=&#34;https://esb.mp.gov.in/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;  title=&#34;Go to MPESB Official Website&#39;s external page&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MPESB Official Website&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;      &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Village Development Officer VDO 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-village-development-officer-vdo-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:31:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-village-development-officer-vdo-2025/</guid>
      <description>राजस्थान कर्मचारी चयन बोर्ड (RSSB) द्वारा ग्राम विकास अधिकारी (VDO) पदों पर भर्ती के लिए अधिसूचना जारी कर दी गई है। इच्छुक और पात्र उम्मीदवार जो भारत के किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त विश्वविद्यालय से स्नातक हैं और जिनके पास O लेवल, COPA, DPCS, कंप्यूटर डिप्लोमा या RS-CIT प्रमाण पत्र है, वे इस भर्ती के लिए ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। भर्ती से जुड़ी पात्रता, आयु सीमा, आवेदन तिथि, चयन प्रक्रिया और अन्य जानकारी के लिए आधिकारिक नोटिफिकेशन जरूर पढ़ें।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRRL Various Posts Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hrrl-various-posts-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:39:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hrrl-various-posts-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Hindustan Petroleum Rajasthan Refinery Limited (HRRL) has released a recruitment notification for 131 vacancies across various departments including Engineering (Chemical, Mechanical, Electrical, Civil, Instrumentation), HR, Finance, Legal, Fire &amp;amp; Safety, and Medical.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan Police Constable 2025 New Examdate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan-police/constable-bharti-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 09:40:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan-police/constable-bharti-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;table-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल भर्ती पात्रता मानदंड&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;th&gt;पद का नाम&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;        &lt;th&gt;कुल पद&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;        &lt;th&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल पात्रता&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल जीडी / ड्राइवर / बैंड नॉन टीएसपी&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;6939&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;राजस्थान सीईटी 10+2 स्तर परीक्षा उत्तीर्ण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;भारत में किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10+2 इंटरमीडिएट परीक्षा&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;ड्राइवर पद के लिए:&lt;/span&gt; एलएमवी / एचएमवी ड्राइविंग लाइसेंस 01/01/2026 तक 1 वर्ष पुराना होना चाहिए&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;अधिक पात्रता विवरण के लिए आधिकारिक अधिसूचना अवश्य पढ़ें&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल जीडी / ड्राइवर / बैंड टीएसपी&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;1209&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;राजस्थान सीईटी 10+2 स्तर परीक्षा उत्तीर्ण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;भारत में किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10+2 इंटरमीडिएट परीक्षा&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;ड्राइवर पद के लिए:&lt;/span&gt; एलएमवी / एचएमवी ड्राइविंग लाइसेंस 01/01/2026 तक 1 वर्ष पुराना होना चाहिए&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;अधिक पात्रता विवरण के लिए आधिकारिक अधिसूचना अवश्य पढ़ें&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt; राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल: &lt;/b&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt; PET Details/पीईटी विवरण 2025 (सामान्य क्षेत्र)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;    &lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;            &lt;td colspan=&#34;3&#34;&gt;&#xA;                &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;ऊंचाई&lt;/b&gt; पुरुष: 168 सेंटीमीटर और महिला: 152 सेंटीमीटर&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;छाती&lt;/b&gt; पुरुष: 81-86 सेंटीमीटर&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;दौड़: पुरुष:&lt;/b&gt; 25 मिनट में 5 किलोमीटर &lt;b&gt;| महिला:&lt;/b&gt; 35 मिनट में 5 किलोमीटर&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt; ​राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल भर्ती 2025 से संबंधित महत्तपूर्ण लिंक  (Important Links) &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th&gt;Important Links&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th&gt;Action&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Dwonload New Exam Date Notice&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://police.rajasthan.gov.in/uploads/C_Tpressnote_2686_9da7aafe1f.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Check New Notice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Dwonload Exam Date Notice&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yojnaportal.com/open/?pdf=LzIwMjUvMDYvcnBzYy1yYWphc3Rhbi1wb2xpY2UtZXhhbWRhdGUtbm90aWNlLmh0bWw=&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Check Notice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Apply Online&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sso.rajasthan.gov.in/signin?ru=RECRUITMENT2&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;📄 Date Extended Notice&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yojnaportal.com/open/?pdf=LzIwMjUvMDUvcmotcG9saWNlLWRhdGUtZXh0ZW5kZWQtbm90aWNlLmh0bWw=&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;📄 Download Notificiation&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yojnaportal.com/open/?pdf=L3AvcnBjLmh0bWw=&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Join Whatsapp&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/whatsapp/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Join Telegram&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/telegram/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Official Source&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.police.rajasthan.gov.in/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;RJ Police Official Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Lab Attendant Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-lab-attendant-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 20:14:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-lab-attendant-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB) has released the notification for Lab Attendant (Prayogshala Sahayak) Recruitment 2025. Eligible candidates can apply online through the official website. This recruitment is a great opportunity for 10th pass candidates seeking government jobs in Rajasthan. Applicants must have a valid domicile of Rajasthan to claim reservation benefits; candidates from other states can apply under the unreserved category (UR). The selection process will include a written examination followed by document verification. Interested candidates are advised to read the official notification carefully and apply before the last date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan High Court Class IV (Peon) Vacancy 2025 - Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-group-d-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:07:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-group-d-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan High Court Class IV (Peon) Recruitment 2025 के अंतर्गत राजस्थान उच्च न्यायालय द्वारा चपरासी (Class IV) पदों पर भर्ती के लिए अधिसूचना जारी की गई है (विज्ञापन संख्या: रा.उ.न्या.जो./परीक्षा प्रकोष्ठ/अधीनस्थ न्यायालय/च.श्रे.क./2025/2349)। इस भर्ती के लिए अभ्यर्थी को किसी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10वीं (माध्यमिक) उत्तीर्ण होना आवश्यक है। साथ ही देवनागरी लिपि में हिंदी का व्यावहारिक ज्ञान और राजस्थान की संस्कृति की जानकारी भी अनिवार्य है। इस भर्ती में राजस्थान राज्य के अभ्यर्थी आवेदन कर सकते हैं, साथ ही अन्य राज्यों के उम्मीदवार भी आवेदन कर सकते हैं, लेकिन उन्हें अनारक्षित श्रेणी (Unreserved Category) में माना जाएगा और किसी प्रकार का आरक्षण प्राप्त नहीं होगा। आवेदन प्रक्रिया पूरी तरह ऑनलाइन होगी और विस्तृत जानकारी व आवेदन के लिए आधिकारिक वेबसाइट hcraj.nic.in पर विज़िट करें।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan HC Driver Recruitment 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-driver-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:20:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-driver-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan High Court has officially released the notification for Driver Recruitment 2025, inviting applications for a total of 58 vacancies. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online through the official website hcraj.nic.in from 18 June to 7 July 2025. This recruitment drive offers a great opportunity for candidates seeking government jobs in the driving sector under the Rajasthan judiciary. Applicants are advised to carefully read the eligibility criteria, application process, and important dates mentioned in the official notification before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSSC Field Assistant 2025 Apply Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/field-assistant-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:33:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/field-assistant-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>फील्ड असिस्टेंट (कृषि विभाग) भर्ती 2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exam Date Reminder</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/exam-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/exam-date/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/download/generate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/download/generate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &lt;title&gt;Generate Permanent Link&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h2&gt;Generate Permanent Link&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;    &lt;input type=&#34;text&#34; id=&#34;inputUrl&#34; placeholder=&#34;Enter URL to encode&#34; style=&#34;width: 80%;&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &lt;button onclick=&#34;generateLink()&#34;&gt;Generate Link&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p id=&#34;generatedLink&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;script&gt;&#xA;        // Predefined tokens (custom static tokens)&#xA;        const tokens = [&#xA;            &#34;abc123&#34;, &#34;xyz456&#34;, &#34;pqr789&#34;, &#xA;            &#34;rst111&#34;, &#34;mno222&#34;, &#34;uvw333&#34;&#xA;        ];&#xA;&#xA;        function generateLink() {&#xA;            const url = document.getElementById(&#39;inputUrl&#39;).value;&#xA;            if (url) {&#xA;                const encodedUrl = btoa(url); &#xA;                const token = tokens[Math.floor(Math.random() * tokens.length)];&#xA;&#xA;                permanentLinks[token] = encodedUrl;&#xA;&#xA;                const permanentLink = `https://yojnaportal.com/download/pdf?token=${token}&amp;url=${encodedUrl}`;&#xA;                &#xA;                document.getElementById(&#39;generatedLink&#39;).innerHTML = `&#xA;                    &lt;a href=&#34;${permanentLink}&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;${permanentLink}&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;                `;&#xA;            } else {&#xA;                alert(&#34;Please enter a valid URL&#34;);&#xA;            }&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        // Store token and encoded URL mapping (to be accessed globally)&#xA;        const permanentLinks = {&#xA;            &#34;abc123&#34;: &#34;&#34;,&#xA;            &#34;xyz456&#34;: &#34;&#34;,&#xA;            &#34;pqr789&#34;: &#34;&#34;,&#xA;            &#34;rst111&#34;: &#34;&#34;,&#xA;            &#34;mno222&#34;: &#34;&#34;,&#xA;            &#34;uvw333&#34;: &#34;&#34;&#xA;        };&#xA;    &lt;/script&gt;&#xA;&lt;/body&gt;&#xA;&lt;/html&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Home Search</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/quick/search-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/quick/search-form/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Date Reminder</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/last-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/last-date/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loader</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/download/loader/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/download/loader/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;title&gt;Base64 URL Loader&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;    &lt;style&gt;&#xA;        body {&#xA;            font-family: Arial, sans-serif;&#xA;            text-align: center;&#xA;        }&#xA;        iframe {&#xA;            width: 100%;&#xA;            height: 500px;&#xA;            border: 1px solid #ccc;&#xA;            border-radius: 8px;&#xA;            margin-top: 20px;&#xA;        }&#xA;    &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;h2&gt;Base64 URL Loader&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div id=&#34;statusMessage&#34;&gt;Loading...&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;iframe id=&#34;pdfFrame&#34; src=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;script&gt;&#xA;        window.onload = function() {&#xA;            const urlParams = new URLSearchParams(window.location.search);&#xA;            const encodedUrl = urlParams.get(&#39;url&#39;);&#xA;&#xA;            if (encodedUrl) {&#xA;                try {&#xA;                    const decodedUrl = atob(encodedUrl);&#xA;                    document.getElementById(&#39;pdfFrame&#39;).src = decodedUrl;&#xA;                    document.getElementById(&#39;statusMessage&#39;).innerText = &#34;PDF Loaded Successfully&#34;;&#xA;                } catch (e) {&#xA;                    document.getElementById(&#39;statusMessage&#39;).innerText = &#34;Invalid Base64 Format&#34;;&#xA;                }&#xA;            } else {&#xA;                document.getElementById(&#39;statusMessage&#39;).innerText = &#34;No URL Provided&#34;;&#xA;            }&#xA;        };&#xA;    &lt;/script&gt;&#xA;&lt;/body&gt;&#xA;&lt;/html&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pdf</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/download/pdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/download/pdf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &lt;title&gt;Redirecting...&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;    &lt;script&gt;&#xA;        // Predefined token and encoded URL mapping (same as in generate.html)&#xA;        const permanentLinks = {&#xA;            &#34;abc123&#34;: &#34;&#34;, &#xA;            &#34;xyz456&#34;: &#34;&#34;,&#xA;            &#34;pqr789&#34;: &#34;&#34;,&#xA;            &#34;rst111&#34;: &#34;&#34;,&#xA;            &#34;mno222&#34;: &#34;&#34;,&#xA;            &#34;uvw333&#34;: &#34;&#34;&#xA;        };&#xA;&#xA;        // Get token from URL parameters&#xA;        const urlParams = new URLSearchParams(window.location.search);&#xA;        const token = urlParams.get(&#39;token&#39;);&#xA;&#xA;        if (token &amp;&amp; permanentLinks[token]) {&#xA;            const decodedUrl = atob(permanentLinks[token]); // Decode Base64 URL&#xA;            window.location.href = decodedUrl; // Redirect to original URL&#xA;        } else {&#xA;            document.body.innerHTML = &#34;&lt;h2&gt;Invalid or Expired Link!&lt;/h2&gt;&#34;;&#xA;        }&#xA;    &lt;/script&gt;&#xA;&lt;/body&gt;&#xA;&lt;/html&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Anything</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/quick/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/quick/search/</guid>
      <description>&lt;head&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;Search anything , find Schemes, find Jobs, find tools, everything , you want  : Yojna Portal&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;title&gt;Search : Gajab Jobs&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search- Yojna Portal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yojna Portal Whatsapp Group Link</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/social-media/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yojna Portal Whatsapp Stutus- Quotes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/status/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:23:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/status/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
