<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Calendars on Gajab Jobs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Calendars on Gajab Jobs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:17:09 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/calendar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/bpsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:17:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/bpsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>BPSC Exam Calendar 2026 में बिहार लोक सेवा आयोग द्वारा आयोजित होने वाली सभी प्रमुख परीक्षाओं की तिथियाँ जारी की गई हैं। इसमें 70th व 71st CCE, Assistant Engineer, Assistant Section Officer, LDC, Motor Vehicle Inspector, Assistant Professor सहित विभिन्न पदों की Prelims, Mains, Interview और Result की संभावित तिथियाँ शामिल हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/ssc-exam-calendar-2026-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:25:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/ssc-exam-calendar-2026-27/</guid>
      <description>Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the SSC Exam Calendar 2026. The calendar includes notification dates, last dates to apply, and exam months for CGL, CHSL, MTS, GD, JE, Stenographer, Hindi Translator and other SSC exams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rpsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:00:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rpsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>RPSC Exam Calendar 2026 has been officially released by the Rajasthan Public Service Commission, Ajmer. The calendar provides the tentative schedule of various recruitment examinations to be conducted in 2026, including Deputy Commandant, Lecturer, Sub Inspector, Veterinary Officer, Assistant Engineer, Senior Teacher, Junior Legal Officer, Statistical Officer and other posts. The exams will be held between January 2026 and December 2026, with some examinations conducted in CBRT (Computer Based Recruitment Test) mode. Detailed exam programmes, admit cards and shift information will be issued separately by RPSC as per schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rrb-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:00:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rrb-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has released the official RRB Exam Calendar 2026 outlining the recruitment planning schedule for various railway posts. The calendar includes major categories such as Assistant Loco Pilot (ALP), Technicians, NTPC (Graduate and Under Graduate), Junior Engineer (JE), Paramedical, Ministerial &amp;amp; Isolated posts, Section Controller, and Level-1 (Group D). It provides a clear timeline for vacancy assessment, OIRMS assessment, indenting process, and draft CEN preparation across different quarters of 2026. This calendar helps candidates understand the expected recruitment cycle; however, actual notifications and exam dates will be released separately through individual CENs by the respective RRBs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:40:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Union Public Service Commission (UPSC) has released the official Programme of Examinations / Recruitment Tests (RTs) Calendar 2026. The calendar includes the complete schedule of major UPSC examinations such as Civil Services (Preliminary &amp;amp; Main), NDA &amp;amp; NA (I &amp;amp; II), CDS (I &amp;amp; II), CAPF (ACs), IES/ISS, Combined Medical Services (CMS), Indian Forest Service, Engineering Services, Geo-Scientist Exams, and several Reserved Recruitment Tests. It provides important details including notification dates, last dates to apply, exam commencement dates, and duration of each examination. Candidates preparing for UPSC exams in 2026 are advised to regularly check official updates, as dates are subject to change based on administrative requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:01:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Madhya Pradesh Public Service Commission has published the MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 to inform candidates about the tentative schedule of upcoming examinations. According to the calendar, important exams such as State Service Main Examination 2025, Assistant Professor Examinations 2025 and 2026, State Engineering Service Examination 2025, and State Service and Forest Service Preliminary and Main Examinations 2026 will be held from January 2026 to September 2026. This exam calendar helps aspirants plan their preparation in advance, though exam dates may be revised due to administrative reasons or court orders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:21:02 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The MPESB Exam Calendar 2026 lists the expected timeline of examinations conducted by MPESB for government recruitment and professional entrance courses. According to the calendar, exams for various groups, police, nursing, technical and teaching posts are proposed between February and October 2026. Aspirants can refer to this calendar to organize their study plan, while official notifications will confirm exact dates and further details.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
