<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Calendars on Gajab Jobs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Calendars on Gajab Jobs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:40:30 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/calendar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:40:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Union Public Service Commission (UPSC) has released the official Programme of Examinations / Recruitment Tests (RTs) Calendar 2026. The calendar includes the complete schedule of major UPSC examinations such as Civil Services (Preliminary &amp;amp; Main), NDA &amp;amp; NA (I &amp;amp; II), CDS (I &amp;amp; II), CAPF (ACs), IES/ISS, Combined Medical Services (CMS), Indian Forest Service, Engineering Services, Geo-Scientist Exams, and several Reserved Recruitment Tests. It provides important details including notification dates, last dates to apply, exam commencement dates, and duration of each examination. Candidates preparing for UPSC exams in 2026 are advised to regularly check official updates, as dates are subject to change based on administrative requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:01:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Madhya Pradesh Public Service Commission has published the MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 to inform candidates about the tentative schedule of upcoming examinations. According to the calendar, important exams such as State Service Main Examination 2025, Assistant Professor Examinations 2025 and 2026, State Engineering Service Examination 2025, and State Service and Forest Service Preliminary and Main Examinations 2026 will be held from January 2026 to September 2026. This exam calendar helps aspirants plan their preparation in advance, though exam dates may be revised due to administrative reasons or court orders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:21:02 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The MPESB Exam Calendar 2026 lists the expected timeline of examinations conducted by MPESB for government recruitment and professional entrance courses. According to the calendar, exams for various groups, police, nursing, technical and teaching posts are proposed between February and October 2026. Aspirants can refer to this calendar to organize their study plan, while official notifications will confirm exact dates and further details.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
