<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Otrs on Gajab Jobs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/otr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Otrs on Gajab Jobs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 10:08:19 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/otr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UPPRPB One Time Registration 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/otr/upprpb-otr-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 10:08:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/otr/upprpb-otr-online/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Police Recruitment and Promotion Board (UPPRPB) has launched the One Time Registration (OTR) 2025 process for all aspiring candidates. This OTR is mandatory for those who wish to apply for any upcoming UP Police recruitment exams. By completing the OTR once, candidates will not need to repeatedly enter their details for each application. This system ensures a faster, more transparent, and convenient application process. Interested candidates can register online at uppbpb.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Candidate Profiling / Profile Panjiyan Form Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/profile/mpesb-candidate-profile-panjiyan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 12:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/profile/mpesb-candidate-profile-panjiyan/</guid>
      <description>To apply for any government recruitment under the Madhya Pradesh Employees Selection Board (MPESB), all candidates must complete the Candidate Profile Registration process. This is a one-time mandatory step where applicants register using Aadhaar eKYC, upload personal and academic details, and receive a unique Profile ID. This ID is required for all future MPESB applications. The process is simple, online, and essential for anyone seeking government jobs in Madhya Pradesh.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
