<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eligibilities on Gajab Jobs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eligibilities on Gajab Jobs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:10:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/eligibility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC SET Exam 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/mp-set-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/mp-set-2025/</guid>
      <description>The MP State Eligibility Test (MP SET 2025) is a state-level examination conducted by the Madhya Pradesh Public Service Commission for determining eligibility for Assistant Professor recruitment in colleges and universities of Madhya Pradesh. The online application process will begin on 25 October 2025 and close on 20 November 2025. The written examination is scheduled to be held on 11 January 2026. Candidates are advised to review eligibility conditions, syllabus and subject list as per the official notification before submitting the application form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTA UGC NET December 2025 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/nta-ugc-net-december-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:35:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/nta-ugc-net-december-2025/</guid>
      <description>The UGC NET December 2025 Notification has been released by the National Testing Agency (NTA) for determining the eligibility of candidates for Assistant Professor and Junior Research Fellowship (JRF) in Indian universities and colleges. Candidates with a Master’s degree (55% marks for General and 50% for reserved categories) can apply online from 07 October to 07 November 2025 at ugcnet.nta.nic.in. The exam will be conducted in Computer Based Test (CBT) mode across multiple subjects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTET February 2026 Registration - Reopen Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/ctet-february-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:28:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/ctet-february-2026/</guid>
      <description>The CTET February 2026 notification has been released, and the online application process is open from 27/11/2025 to 18/12/2025. Candidates can apply for Paper I (Class 1–5) and Paper II (Class 6–8) based on NCTE eligibility norms. The exam will be conducted on 08 February 2026 in offline OMR mode across multiple exam centers. The application fee is ₹1000 for General/OBC (single paper) and ₹500 for SC/ST/PwD candidates. The CTET certificate is valid for a lifetime, and all important details regarding syllabus, exam pattern, eligibility, and fee structure are provided in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTET Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/htet-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 17:29:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/htet-2025/</guid>
      <description>HTET 2025 is conducted by the Board of School Education Haryana to determine the eligibility of candidates for Primary Teacher (PRT), Trained Graduate Teacher (TGT), and Post Graduate Teacher (PGT) posts in Haryana. Candidates can apply for Level-1, Level-2, or Level-3 based on their educational qualification. The HTET certificate is valid for a lifetime, there is no limit on attempts, and the examination is conducted in offline (pen and paper) mode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPCT Exam Jan-2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/cpct-exam-jan-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:19:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/cpct-exam-jan-2026/</guid>
      <description>The CPCT Exam 2026 is scheduled on 16, 17 and 18 January 2026. The online application window will remain open from 15 to 29 December 2025. Applicants need to upload scanned photograph, signature and relevant marksheets. Mock test facility is available, candidates with 12th or 10th plus Polytechnic Diploma are eligible and the CPCT T Scorecard will remain valid for 7 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar STET Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/bihar-stet-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:44:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/bihar-stet-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar School Examination Board (BSEB) will release the BSTET / STET 2025 Answer Key soon on the official website. The exam was held on 14 October 2025, and the application process closed on 05 October 2025. Candidates can check their Answer Key by logging in with their Enrollment Number, Registration Number, or Date of Birth. A direct link to download the Answer Key is available below.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
