<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Admissions on Gajab Jobs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Admissions on Gajab Jobs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:23:33 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/admission/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UP RTE Admission 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/up-rte-admission-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:23:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/up-rte-admission-2026/</guid>
      <description>Under RTE Admission 2026, children from disadvantaged and weaker sections will get free admission on 25% seats in entry-level classes (Nursery, LKG, UKG, Class 1) in recognized private schools. The application process is fully online, and parents can select up to 10 neighbourhood schools. Selection will be done through a transparent lottery system. Age criteria, eligibility conditions, document verification, BSA locking process, and admission orders will follow the official schedule. The government will reimburse school fees and also provide financial support for books and uniforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTA NCET 2026 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/ncet-exam-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:13:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/ncet-exam-2026/</guid>
      <description>NCET 2026 is conducted by the National Testing Agency (NTA) for admission to the 4-Year Integrated Teacher Education Programme (ITEP). Candidates who have passed or are appearing in Class 12 can apply. The exam is held in CBT mode and covers Language, Teaching Aptitude, General Test and Domain subjects. Admission is granted through counselling based on exam performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP B.Ed. Admission 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/upbed-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:01:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/upbed-2026/</guid>
      <description>UP B.Ed. Joint Entrance Examination (JEE) 2026 is conducted by Bundelkhand University, Jhansi for admission to the two-year Bachelor of Education (B.Ed.) programme for the 2026–28 session. General and OBC candidates must secure at least 50% marks in Graduation or Post-Graduation, while Engineering candidates require 55% marks. SC/ST candidates are eligible without any minimum percentage requirement. Admission is based on entrance exam performance followed by counselling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUET (UG) 2026 Online Correction Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/cuet-ug-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:38:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/cuet-ug-2026/</guid>
      <description>CUET (UG) 2026 is an all-India entrance examination conducted by the National Testing Agency for admission to undergraduate programs in Central and other participating universities for the 2026–27 session. Students who have passed or are appearing in Class 12 are eligible to apply. The test is conducted in computer-based mode, permits selection of up to five subjects, and follows a uniform marking scheme. Final admission is offered by universities based on CUET scores, cut-off lists, and course-specific eligibility requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar RTE Admission 2026–27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/bihar-rte-admission-2026%E2%80%9327/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/bihar-rte-admission-2026%E2%80%9327/</guid>
      <description>RTE 25% Admission 2026–27 is offered under the Right to Education Act to ensure free education in private schools for children belonging to EWS, SC, ST, OBC, minority and orphan categories. Children aged 6 years or above as on 01 April 2026 who satisfy the income criteria can apply online through the Gyandeep Portal. Admission is done after document verification and online school allotment through a transparent random selection process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super 100 Examination Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/super-100-examination-form-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 11:04:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/super-100-examination-form-2026/</guid>
      <description>Super 100 is a state-level admission examination conducted for meritorious students studying in government schools of Madhya Pradesh and is administered by the Madhya Pradesh State Open School. Through this examination, students are granted admission into Class 11 residential schools, where selected candidates receive free coaching for competitive examinations like JEE, NEET, and CLAT, along with free accommodation, meals, and study materials. This scheme has been launched to provide quality education and better career opportunities to economically weaker but talented students. Selection is based on the entrance examination and merit, ensuring equal opportunities for deserving students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Excellence &amp; Model School Class 9 Admission 2026–27 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/soe-som-class-9-admission-2026%E2%80%9327/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:34:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/soe-som-class-9-admission-2026%E2%80%9327/</guid>
      <description>MP Excellence School Entrance Exam 2027 is a joint selection test for admission to Class 9 in Excellence Schools (SOE) and Model Schools (SOM) across Madhya Pradesh. MP resident students who have passed or are appearing in Class 8 can submit the online application between 30/12/2025 and 16/01/2026. Admission will be based on the entrance examination, with reservation benefits applicable as per state government norms. The application fee for all categories is ₹200 including portal charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shramodaya Admission Test Online Form 2026–27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/shramodaya-admission-test-2026%E2%80%9327/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:20:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/shramodaya-admission-test-2026%E2%80%9327/</guid>
      <description>Shramodaya Admission Test 2026–27 is an entrance examination conducted in Madhya Pradesh for admission to Shramodaya Awasiya Vidyalaya for Class 6, 7, 8 and 9. The admission is exclusively for children of registered construction workers under the MP Building and Other Construction Workers Welfare Board. The online application window will remain open from 24/12/2025 to 20/01/2026. Candidates will be selected through a written entrance test and final admission will be done on the basis of merit and seat availability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eklavya Model School Class 6 Admission 2026-27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/eklavya-model-school-class-6-admission-2026-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:03:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/eklavya-model-school-class-6-admission-2026-27/</guid>
      <description>Eklavya Model Residential School (EMRS) has released the notification for Class 6 admission for the 2026–27 academic session. Scheduled Tribe (ST) students studying in or passed Class 5 can apply online. Admission will be through an entrance examination followed by document verification. Selected students will receive free residential education with hostel, food, books, uniforms and other facilities under the CBSE curriculum. The application window is open from 10 January 2026 to 10 February 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTA NCHM JEE 2026 Admission Test</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/nta-nchm-jee-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:07:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/nta-nchm-jee-2026/</guid>
      <description>NCHM JEE 2026 is a national level entrance examination conducted by the National Testing Agency (NTA) for admission to the B.Sc. Hospitality &amp;amp; Hotel Administration (B.Sc. HHA) course. Candidates who have passed or are appearing in 10+2 with English as a subject are eligible to apply. The examination is conducted in Computer Based Test (CBT) mode, and admission to Central, State, and Private Institutes of Hotel Management is offered based on rank, counselling, and seat availability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya Selection Test - 2026 Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/jnv-navodaya-admission-6th-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 11:04:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/jnv-navodaya-admission-6th-2026/</guid>
      <description>Apply for Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya Selection Test (JNVST) 2026 for Class 6 admission. Last date is 29 July 2025. Check eligibility, exam date, prospectus PDF &amp;amp; online application link.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
